{"id": "search_qa_0", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm looking for a green camera case but I don't want all those extra pockets. Find me the simplest one you got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_0", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Will this camera case remain secure while hiking or navigating rough terrain?", "long_answer": "This camera case is fitted with a handy belt loop for simple attachment; however, it might not fulfill the durability and protection needs of individuals participating in intense activities such as hiking. It is advisable to look at cases with different carrying methods that cater to the demands of harsh settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop fail to meet the requirements for those who need to carry their camera case in a rugged or challenging environment that would benefit from alternative carrying methods.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_0", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Are the zippers on the Fastpack 200 known to be durable and reliable?", "long_answer": "The zippers on the Fastpack 200 are generally perceived by customers as durable and smooth-running, with reports of malfunctions being rare.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_1", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does this camera case offer a way to carry it effortlessly without sacrificing too much style?", "long_answer": "This camera case comes with a shoulder strap that offers ease and comfort for daily use. Nonetheless, it should be pointed out that although it is utilitarian, the design prioritizes functionality over a sleek or luxurious aesthetic that some consumers may prefer.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap fail to meet the requirements for users seeking a fashionable accessory, as the strap's primary focus is on functionality and comfort over luxury aesthetics.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_2", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can a Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens fit in this backpack?", "long_answer": "I'm sorry, but it wouldn't be a good fit. I have a Nikon D3500, which fits, but your Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm lens is larger and likely wouldn't fit comfortably.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_3", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the case durable enough to endure repeated use outdoors?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is fashioned from nylon fabric, renowned for its exceptional tensile strength. As such, it boasts resistance to tearing and stretching, guaranteeing long-lasting durability even with substantial outdoor usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_4", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can this bag fit my d3300? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The bag is designed to fit Canon 70D with a 18-200mm lens, and your d3300 is similar in size, so it should fit without problems.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the d3300 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the d3300 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_5", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can it hold a T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits perfectly in this case. Your camera and lens are of similar size to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_1", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the bag have an attachment feature for securely fastening a tripod?", "long_answer": "The bag comes equipped with tripod loops at the bottom, enabling the secure attachment of a tripod to the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_2", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is this sling bag suitable for photographers who are active in hiking or bicycling?", "long_answer": "The sling bag is designed with quick access in mind and provides a comfortable cross-body fit, which makes it highly suitable for active photography tasks like hiking or bicycling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_1", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm not into bulky stuff, so I'm looking for a camera case without any extra pockets. Can you list the most affordable one you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_3", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 backpack suitable for daily use?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 backpack, while well-suited for storing and transporting a large amount of camera gear, may not be the most convenient choice for daily use due to its potentially cumbersome size and weight when fully packed.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_4", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "What is the percentage increase in carrying capacity provided by the expansion compartment?", "long_answer": "The expansion compartment allows the bag to increase its carrying capacity by around 30%, enabling additional storage for items such as a light jacket or various personal effects.", "short_answer": "30%", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_6", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm really into macro photography; does this case accommodate that type of precise work?", "long_answer": "Macro photography typically necessitates a stable camera to capture the intricate details without any blur. Unfortunately, this camera case lacks a tripod attachment feature, which is crucial for achieving such stability.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_7", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "If I don't use the camera case, can it be easily stored without occupying a lot of space?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is crafted from a material that enables it to collapse when not in use, making it easy to tuck away without taking up significant space.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_8", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is this case appropriate for photographing scenarios where holding the camera is not possible, such as when operating a remote shutter?", "long_answer": "In instances where hands-free camera operation is necessary, such as using a remote shutter, the absence of a tripod mount on this camera case renders it incapable of providing sufficient stability on its own. Therefore, a case with tripod compatibility is recommended for such situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_9", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can I hike with this camera case without it hindering me?", "long_answer": "Undoubtedly, the backpack straps on the camera case are perfect for hikers because they enable secure transportation of camera gear on your back, allowing for more effortless navigation across diverse landscapes without the case being a hindrance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are known for facilitating hands-free operation, thus enabling photographers to move more freely and focus on capturing images without the encumbrance of holding onto their case.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_2", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm not looking to spend over 50 dollars and I don't want any extra pockets. What's the cheapest camera case you have that meets my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_5", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can I rapidly access my camera using the hammock system when an unexpected photo opportunity occurs?", "long_answer": "The hammock system is specifically designed to allow photographers to quickly and easily access their cameras, providing a significant advantage for capturing those sudden and unexpected photo opportunities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_3", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Listen, I'm only interested in the USA Gear brand, and I need a camera case with locks. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND closure_type = 'locks' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_6", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the camera bag have features to help prevent the camera from falling out?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is equipped with a zippered hatch for the main compartment, along with secure compartments for accessories, which collectively work to minimize the risk of the camera or other items accidentally falling out.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_7", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag accommodate an iPad along with a smaller camera setup?", "long_answer": "The bag comes with an expandable compartment that can increase its carrying capacity by roughly 30%, potentially providing enough space for a small tablet like an iPad, specifically when carrying a minimal camera setup. Nevertheless, fitting an iPad could be challenging with a larger DSLR and multiple lenses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_8", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the Case Logic SLRC-202 camera bag compatible with a Canon 5D equipped with an attached battery grip?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLRC-202 camera bag can fit most SLRs with a zoom lens, but might be too small for the Canon 5D with an attached battery grip, leading to a tight fit. In some cases, removing the battery grip may be necessary for a suitable fit, and it's worth noting that the bag won't accommodate larger DSLR bodies such as the Canon 1D series.", "short_answer": "tight fit", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_4", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I'm not interested in any flashy red cases or anything that can't handle a little water. So, what's the cheapest camera case you got that's not red and is water resistant?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"red\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"red\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"red\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'red' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_5", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Listen, I ain't got time for fancy pockets. Just find me the simplest camera case from either Altura Photo or Pelican. Got it?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Pelican\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Pelican\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'Altura Photo' OR brand = 'Pelican') AND pockets = 0\nORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_10", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Will this bag fit the Canon G15? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it for a Canon L-series 100-400 and it fits perfectly. Your Canon G15 is about the same size, so it will also fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon G15 has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon G15 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_11", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I require a case that can withstand the demands of outdoor work and accommodate all of my photography gear. Would this be an appropriate option?", "long_answer": "The camera case might not be adequate for extensive fieldwork involving diverse equipment due to the absence of an essential tripod attachment feature. This is vital for safely transporting and swiftly setting up standard professional photographic gear, such as tripods and additional lighting.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_9", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Lowepro Fastpack 200 designed to accommodate a DSLR with a mid-range zoom lens and additional lenses or flash units?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Fastpack 200 is specifically tailored to house a DSLR with a mid-range zoom lens affixed, with additional capacity for 2-3 extra lenses or flash units. The design takes into account the size variations in lenses and flash units, ensuring a protective fit for a range of photography equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_10", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this bag an appropriate gift for a photographer?", "long_answer": "The bag, designed with a sturdy build and ample storage space, is an excellent choice for individuals interested in photography, catering to the varying needs of both novice and experienced photographers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_11", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is there room in the bag for storing additional personal items such as a phone or wallet, along with camera gear?", "long_answer": "The bag does include compartments intended for smaller items such as memory cards and batteries which can potentially accommodate personal items like phones and wallets. However, due to the limited space, the design mainly focuses on storage for camera gear, which should be given priority.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_12", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is the Soft Pouch designed to be lightweight and non-bulky for camera protection?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch is specifically designed to be lightweight and streamlined, providing protection for your camera without the unnecessary bulk commonly associated with oversized bags.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_6", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Look, I want a purple camera case with less than two pockets. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND pockets < 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND pockets < 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' \n      AND pockets < 2 \nORDER BY price \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_13", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the Case Logic SLRC-202's hammock system prevent the camera from touching the bottom of the case?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLRC-202 features a hammock system specifically designed to keep your SLR camera suspended above the case's bottom, thereby offering enhanced protection against impact and ensuring that the camera does not make contact with the bottom surface of the case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_14", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the waist strap of the bag adjust to fit all body types comfortably?", "long_answer": "The waist strap on the bag is adjustable and can fit many different body sizes. However, there have been instances where larger individuals found the waist strap too small, indicating that it may not accommodate every body type comfortably.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_15", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera bag designed to be compact for casual, everyday use?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is somewhat bulkier than what some might consider ideal for casual day trips; however, it remains a suitable option due to its ability to carry essential camera gear, offering a compromise between space-saving design and adequate storage capacity.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_16", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG large enough to accommodate a Canon EOS-10D with a long zoom lens attached?", "long_answer": "Based on customer feedback, the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG is designed to hold one or two camera bodies along with several lenses or accessories. However, placing a Canon EOS-10D with an attached long zoom lens inside the bag may be difficult due to space constraints, suggesting that a larger bag would be a more appropriate choice for such equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_7", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm not too keen on the whole water-resistant thing and I only use Canon. Get me the first non-water resistant Canon camera case you see.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand = \"Canon\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand = \"Canon\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Canon' AND water_resistance = 'no' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_12", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I am looking for an elegant camera case to give as a gift; would this one be suitable?", "long_answer": "When selecting a gift that radiates sophistication, take into account the camera case's aesthetic. Crafted from nylon, it typically presents a more casual and practical style, potentially falling short of the upscale, refined look you may desire in a present.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_13", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for me when aiming to reduce movement and sound during photography sessions in tranquil settings?", "long_answer": "In environments requiring minimal movement and noise, opt for a camera case with a handle or the ability to secure snugly to your body, avoiding loose-hanging straps that can sway and generate sound, rather than a case with a shoulder strap.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not recommended for situations where stealth is necessary, as the motion of a dangling strap might draw unwanted attention or noise, unlike a case that is carried by a handle or secured closer to the body.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_14", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can a Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fit into this bag?", "long_answer": "Yes, this bag should fit your Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime. I have a Nikon D3500 which is a similar size and it fits perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_15", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is it reasonable to anticipate that this camera case will protect my gear from moisture during a kayaking excursion?", "long_answer": "Certainly, a waterproof camera case is perfect for water-based activities such as kayaking because it keeps your camera dry. Yet, if you anticipate needing to access the case frequently during your journey, remember that the waterproof seals might require extra effort to open each time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof property are not suitable for situations where quick access and multiple openings of the case are necessary, as their protective seals can make them less convenient to open frequently.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_16", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this case comfortable to carry around for prolonged periods during a city tour?", "long_answer": "This camera bag could be convenient for long-duration city tours, as its backpack straps facilitate balanced weight distribution across your shoulders, although it's not the slimmest choice for navigating through bustling urban settings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps fail to meet the requirements for a low-profile carry option in crowd-intensive settings due to their bulkier design when compared to more streamlined cases or bags.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_17", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is it safe to submerge the camera case in water when transporting it across a river?", "long_answer": "The camera case's material is not intended for submersion. It provides elementary water resistance, so it can withstand slight moisture but cannot tolerate complete submergence. To safely ford a river, you'll require a case expressly crafted for submersion or extra waterproofing measures.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_18", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can this pouch fit my Canon Rebel T5i with a macro lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I own a Nikon D90 and it fits perfectly. As far as I know, the Canon Rebel T5i with a macro lens is similar in size to the D90.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the canon rebel t5i with macro lens has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the canon rebel t5i with macro lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_17", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Lowepro Fastpack 200 have a dedicated compartment for a laptop?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Fastpack 200 is not equipped with a compartment specifically designated for a laptop, which suggests that users searching for a bag to securely accommodate a laptop alongside camera equipment should consider alternative models that offer this feature.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_18", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the backpack provide separate compartments for personal items apart from the camera gear?", "long_answer": "The backpack features an upper compartment and smaller pockets specifically designed to accommodate personal items, ensuring that there is dedicated space for items other than camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_19", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this camera bag suitable for professional cameras with 'white L' lenses?", "long_answer": "The bag is specifically designed to accommodate consumer-grade DSLR cameras, including those in the Canon Rebel series, and is not intended for larger professional camera bodies or 'white L' lenses, which usually demand more space than the bag can offer.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_20", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the pack include a feature for carrying a tripod?", "long_answer": "The pack is equipped with a Hideaway Tripod Mount that allows a tripod to be attached securely. Nevertheless, a few customers have pointed out that the tripod attachment could be snug and might be improved with an extra strap for enhanced stabilization.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_19", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for use on a boat or in proximity to water sources?", "long_answer": "Certainly, thanks to its waterproof construction featuring sealed zippers and roll-top closures, this camera case is perfectly suited for aquatic settings, safeguarding your camera in the vicinity of water.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a waterproof design are known for incorporating sealed zippers or roll-top closures that prevent water intrusion, ensuring that the camera remains dry in challenging weather or aquatic environments.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_8", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I hate products with too many pockets. It confuses me. Get me the Lowepro camera case that has the least amount of pockets, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack` with asin: B000YA33DC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Lowepro' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_21", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the camera case designed to endure extreme conditions for heavy-duty use?", "long_answer": "The camera case is constructed to withstand everyday use; however, it may not be adequate for extreme conditions that require heavy-duty protection. For such scenarios, it is recommended to consider specialized heavy-duty camera case options.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_22", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 backpack designed to be worn comfortably for long durations?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack features breathable, contoured shoulder straps that are crafted to evenly distribute weight, thereby ensuring the user can wear the backpack comfortably throughout an extended period.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_20", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm concerned about the potential damage to my camera equipment during travel. Does this case provide a robust structure to protect my belongings?", "long_answer": "For travel where it's essential to keep camera equipment undamaged, a case with a sturdy build would be advantageous. The flexibility of the nylon material in this camera case may not offer the structural rigidity desired to shield your gear from potential impacts while on the move.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_21", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "As an amateur photographer, I'm wondering whether this case would impose any restrictions on me during outdoor photo sessions?", "long_answer": "Although the case may be suitable for a hobbyist's everyday needs, the lack of a tripod mount might be restrictive during outdoor photography sessions where a tripod is essential. This becomes particularly relevant as your interest in photography expands to situations where camera steadiness is vital for achieving the perfect capture.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_23", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "How practical is the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG for photographers who travel?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG is designed to be compact yet spacious enough internally to accommodate a photographer's essential equipment, thus making it a viable choice for travel purposes where carrying extensive gear is not necessary.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_24", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack capable of accommodating a 100-400 superzoom lens?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is designed with enough space to accommodate larger lenses, such as a 100-400 superzoom lens, along with additional photography equipment based on customer experiences.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_25", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is an instruction manual provided with the AmazonBasics Sling Backpack?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Sling Backpack does not come with an instruction manual, as it is shipped with \"no-frustration packaging,\" assuming that customers can discover its features without additional guidance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_22", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The case is designed to accommodate a Nikon D3500 and since the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime has similar dimensions, it will fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_26", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack have a feature to securely hold a tripod?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is designed with a Hideaway Tripod Mount system, which ensures that a tripod can be securely attached to the pack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_23", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can a Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens fit into this case? ", "long_answer": "I don't believe it would. I tried to fit my Nikon D5000 with battery grip and it fitted perfectly but your camera is larger than that.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "search_qa_9", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I need a waterproof camera case, but I ain't paying through the nose for it. Get me your cheapest waterproof case.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_10", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I don't have money to burn, and I absolutely don't want any Ape Case. What's the cheapest camera case you can find that suits me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand <> 'Ape Case' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_24", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can I easily remove the camera case when I'm in dense areas such as concerts or festivals?", "long_answer": "Actually, if the camera case features a belt loop as a carrying option, it might not be the ideal selection for crowded venues. Swift detachment of the camera case from a belt can be impractical in such packed circumstances, thus making it a less advisable choice for professionals in these environments.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop are not recommended for professional use in environments where quick removal of the camera case from the belt is not practical, such as densely packed crowd events where reaching down consistently might not be feasible.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_27", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can the adjustable shoulder and waist straps comfortably fit individuals with smaller body frames?", "long_answer": "The shoulder and waist straps of this product are designed to be adjustable to accommodate various body types. However, it has been reported by some users with smaller frames that achieving a comfortable fit can sometimes present a challenge.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_28", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Does the backpack provide enough space for personal items in addition to camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with multiple storage options, such as a large upper pocket and various compartments, which are ample to accommodate personal items as well as camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_25", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "As a professional photographer, ought I to consider this camera case for my fieldwork?", "long_answer": "As a professional who often operates in diverse shooting environments and requires exact camera positioning, this camera case may not be ideal since it doesn't include a tripod attachment. This feature is commonly advised for professionals to achieve the best outcomes in specialized photographic situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_11", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm looking for a mica-colored camera case, but I don't need the water-resistance feature. Can you find such a product for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'mica' AND water_resistance = 'no';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_29", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the case comfortable and not overly bulky when attached to a belt?", "long_answer": "The case is designed to have a medium profile, ensuring that it does not feel overly bulky, hence making it comfortable for most users to wear attached to a belt.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_12", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Listen, I don't need any of those fancy pockets on my case. Just give me a simple one made by either Sony or Lowepro, okay?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Lowepro\") AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Lowepro\") AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'Lowepro') AND pockets = 0;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_30", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does this bag have designated pockets for small items such as memory cards and lens cloths?", "long_answer": "This bag is equipped with padded easy-access side pockets specifically designed to hold and organize small items, including memory cards and lens cloths. It also features additional zippered pockets for further organization.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_26", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is this case appropriate for extreme sports photography, where my equipment may be subject to rough handling?", "long_answer": "No, if you're engaged in extreme sports photography, you require a camera case that can endure the rugged handling your gear is likely to face. Given that the case is made of neoprene, it lacks the essential structural integrity to shield your camera from the harsh impacts commonly found in such settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with neoprene material lack the capability to offer rigid, structural protection, which is sometimes necessary for extremely hazardous environments where equipment could be subjected to heavy impacts or pressures.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "neoprene", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_31", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "How reliable are the Canon 200DG bag closures in securing its contents?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG bag is designed with double-clasp closures and velcro, which collectively provide a strong and secure method of sealing the bag. User feedback commonly highlights the durability and effectiveness of these closures in safeguarding the items inside.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_13", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I fancy something from OP/TECH USA and particularly like yellow or mica. Can you sort out the most affordable of their camera cases in these colors for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"mica\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"mica\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"mica\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' AND (color = 'yellow' OR color = 'mica') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_27", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I frequently shoot in windy conditions; would this case still be effective for me to use?", "long_answer": "Under blustery conditions, maintaining camera steadiness is crucial, notably in disciplines such as landscape photography, where slight motion can result in blurry photos. Regrettably, this case lacks a tripod attachment, potentially rendering it less efficient in securing camera stability amid such settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_28", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Canon 70-200 F4 lens? ", "long_answer": "No, this case can comfortably fit a Nikon D3500 which is smaller than the Canon 70-200 F4 lens. Therefore, your lens would not fit in this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_32", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster designed to be fully waterproof?", "long_answer": "The SHC-101 Holster is constructed with a material that provides some resistance to moisture, but it is not completely waterproof. The design, particularly the flap closure, has potential gaps that might permit water infiltration, making it susceptible to water damage under certain conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_33", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is there a built-in locking mechanism included with the bag for security purposes?", "long_answer": "According to the product metadata, the bag does not come equipped with any built-in locking mechanisms.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_34", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is there a designated area on the bag to secure a tripod?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with tripod loops on the bottom, providing a dedicated space to securely attach a tripod, facilitating the convenience of carrying it alongside other photographic gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_14", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Not a fan of black and don't need a million pockets, just give me your cheapest camera case with less than two pockets and some other color.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT color = \"black\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT color = \"black\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'black' AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_35", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Does the case include a polymer o-ring for waterproof sealing?", "long_answer": "The case incorporates a tongue-and-groove closure mechanism that uses a polymer o-ring to create a waterproof seal.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_36", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the top compartment of the backpack designed to accommodate additional camera lenses or flash units?", "long_answer": "The backpack's top compartment is specifically designed to hold extra camera accessories such as lenses or flash units, with many customers reporting successful storage of their additional gear, although the snugness of the fit can vary based on the dimensions of these items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_15", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I only got a tenner on me and I only deal with drawstrings and locks. What's the camera case with the least pockets you have that matches what I've got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'locks') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_29", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for maneuvering through crowded environments such as festivals or bustling urban areas?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case isn't optimal for crowded places as it includes backpack straps, contributing to its bulkiness and a less discreet profile in contrast to sleeker alternatives that are more appropriate for these scenarios.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps fail to meet the requirements for a low-profile carry option in crowd-intensive settings due to their bulkier design when compared to more streamlined cases or bags.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_16", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm working with a skimpy wallet here, only got about 10 bucks. Can you find me a camera case with either a zipper or drawstring within that price?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'drawstring');"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_30", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon 70D with 70-250mm lens and it fits perfectly. Since the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G lens is of similar size, it should fit in this bag too.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_31", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I require a case that can securely hold my tripod as I navigate various shooting locations. Would this be a suitable option?", "long_answer": "Although the camera case includes a tripod attachment feature via its hook-and-loop fastener, be aware that the stability of the tripod will rely on its mass. The attachment should suffice for standard tripods, as you transition between different sites, but it's not advisable for excessively heavy tripods, given the fastener's limited capacity to bear weight.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with tripod attachment using hook and loop fastener cannot be used for extremely heavy tripods or in situations where a fail-proof, mechanical locking mechanism is required due to the relative strength limitation of the hook and loop system.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "hook and loop fastener", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_37", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this bag designed to fit two camera bodies along with several lenses?", "long_answer": "The product is advertised as being capable of holding one or two camera bodies and several lenses. However, user feedback often indicates that it more comfortably accommodates just one camera body with an attached lens and maybe one or two small lenses or accessories, suggesting that fitting two camera bodies and multiple lenses could be a tight fit.", "short_answer": "possibly tight fit", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_38", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the Lowepro backpack come with a lifetime warranty?", "long_answer": "Lowepro provides a lifetime warranty for this backpack, ensuring that any issues with the product are dealt with efficiently and satisfactorily by the company.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_17", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I don't need any fancy pockets or that mica color thing. I want the cheapest basic camera case you've got, capisce?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT color = \"mica\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT color = \"mica\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND color != 'mica' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_32", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Will this camera bag fit my A-99 with vertical grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Nikon D3500, which is similar in size to the A-99 with vertical grip, and it fits perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the A-99 with vertical grip has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the A-99 with vertical grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_33", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this bag fit a Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, no. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens which fits perfectly but the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens is larger so it wouldn't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_39", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is there a feature in the backpack that allows for rapid retrieval of the camera?", "long_answer": "The backpack includes a quick access side opening designed specifically to enable the user to quickly and easily reach for the camera and other gear without needing to take off the backpack entirely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_18", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I can't stand purple and I'm a bit clumsy around water. I need a camera case, but nothing pricey. What's the cheapest option you've got that's not purple and is water-resistant?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color <> 'purple' AND water_resistance = 'yes' AND price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases WHERE color <> 'purple' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1)"}}
{"id": "search_qa_19", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I need a black camera case and I don't fancy those fancy latches. Just give me the simplest one you've got with velcro or zipper fastenings.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"black\" AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"zipper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"black\" AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"zipper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'black' AND (closure_type = 'velcro' OR closure_type = 'zipper') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_40", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Are the latches on the Pelican 1200 Case difficult to open?", "long_answer": "There have been customer reports that suggest the latches on the Pelican 1200 Case might be stiff or challenging to open, which is a deliberate aspect of the design aimed at providing a secure seal. Nonetheless, this means that some extra effort may be necessary when opening and closing the latches.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_20", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I like Lowepro but I hate cases with pockets. Can you find me a product that's got none?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Lowepro' AND pockets = 0;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_34", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can this bag accomodate a 70-200/2.8 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to accommodate the 70-200/2.8 lens. I know it fits the Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens which is of similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the 70-200/2.8 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the 70-200/2.8 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_21", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I have my preferences and I'm not changing. I need a camera case with a velcro closure. Oh, and it should be either a Pelican or a Sony. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Sony\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Sony\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'velcro' AND (brand = 'Pelican' OR brand = 'Sony');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_41", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can the interior Velcro in the bag scratch items such as camera lenses?", "long_answer": "Some customers have reported that the Velcro inside the bag is coarse and can potentially scratch sensitive items like camera lenses. It is advised to use protective covers or avoid direct contact with the Velcro to prevent damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_35", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "My camera gear occasionally suffers bumps and jostles during transport. Will this case offer sufficient protection under those circumstances?", "long_answer": "Selecting nylon for the fabrication of this camera case renders it perfect for these situations. Its robust abrasion resistance allows it to handle some impact and harsh handling while in transit, aiding in the protection of your camera gear from possible harm.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_42", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the DSLR Day Holster have space to accommodate accessories such as chargers and cables?", "long_answer": "The DSLR Day Holster is designed to be streamlined and minimizes bulk by primarily accommodating the camera and its attached lens; it does not offer additional space for accessories such as chargers and cables.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_22", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Listen, I ain't got more than 10 bucks to spend and I'm not a fan of USA Gear. Give me the cheapest camera case you got that's not from them.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand != 'USA Gear' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_43", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the backpack spacious enough to hold two full-sized DSLR cameras with attached lenses?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with customizable dividers, allowing it to accommodate multiple cameras and lenses, although the fit for two full-sized DSLR cameras with lenses may be tight depending on the actual dimensions of the cameras and lenses and how they are arranged within the bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_36", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this camera case crafted for travel photographers requiring swift setup in diverse locales?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this case is especially suitable for travel photographers who require the ability to quickly maneuver and seize moments without the added effort of setting up tripods. Without a tripod mount, the case appeals to those who prioritize convenience and swiftness above the stabilizing benefits offered by tripods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_23", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I don't want anything yellow and I like zippers and drawstrings on my cases. Find me the cheapest camera case that has either of those closures, as long as it's not yellow.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND NOT color = \"yellow\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND NOT color = \"yellow\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND NOT color = \"yellow\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') AND color != 'yellow' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_24", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Look, I've got a hundred to burn and I want a red camera case. Find me the best one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND price <= 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND price <= 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND price <= 100 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_44", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this Pelican case withstand extremely harsh conditions?", "long_answer": "Pelican cases have a robust reputation for durability and are confirmed by customer experiences to endure very tough conditions, including military use and outdoor adventures.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_37", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this camera case suitable if I need one that can also function as an independent tripod holder?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case lacks the free-standing feature needed for tripod compatibility. Its design prioritizes being worn as a backpack, meaning it does not possess the necessary rigid external framework to hold a tripod independently.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps lack the capability to stay upright on their own when set down due to their design focused on back wear-ability, unlike hard cases which can be free-standing.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_38", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case fit my T3i/600D with a battery grip? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I own a Nikon D90 and it fits perfectly. Considering the T3i/600D with a battery grip is a similar size to the Nikon D90, it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the T3i/600D with a battery grip has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the T3i/600D with a battery grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_45", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the backpack's bright orange interior make it easier to locate dark-colored gear?", "long_answer": "Many users appreciate the bright orange interior of the backpack as it enhances visibility, thereby making it notably easier to find items, especially dark-colored gear that would otherwise blend in with darker interiors.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_46", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Does the backpack itself have waterproof features without the rain cover?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with a rain cover that offers water-resistant protection, but without this cover, the backpack is not inherently waterproof.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_47", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 bag within the size restrictions for carry-on luggage on most airlines?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 bag is generally acceptable as carry-on luggage for most airlines, though due to its substantial size, there may be issues fitting it into overhead bins on smaller aircraft. It is advisable to verify the size compatibility with the individual airline's restrictions before travel.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_48", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "How reliable is the tripod carrying system without additional support?", "long_answer": "The reliability of the tripod carrying system varies among customers; while some report successful usage without any problems, others suggest the necessity of extra support, such as a bungee cord, especially when handling larger tripods.", "short_answer": "mixed reviews", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_39", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will this backpack fit my Nikon D7100 with a 55-300mm VR lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits perfectly. And your camera with the lens is similar in size to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Nikon D7100 + 55-300mm VR lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Nikon D7100 + 55-300mm VR lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_40", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "If I inadvertently spill a beverage on my camera case, will my camera remain protected?", "long_answer": "The case material features a degree of water resistance capable of safeguarding your camera from small spills. Nonetheless, it is not fully waterproof; hence, promptly cleaning spills is advisable to prevent any possible damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_49", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is there a rain cover included with the purchase of this backpack?", "long_answer": "The backpack includes a built-in rain cover which provides enhanced water-resistance, allowing it to be used effectively in a variety of weather situations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_25", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I don't want my camera case to just pop open and I'm a bit of a green lover. What do you have that has either a velco or lock closure?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"locks\") AND color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"locks\") AND color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (closure_type = 'velcro' OR closure_type = 'locks') AND color = 'green';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_41", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Does the camera case provide suitability for outdoor photography across diverse weather conditions?", "long_answer": "The casing is made from a material that endures a variety of outdoor elements, offering a level of water resistance. Nevertheless, in the face of severe weather conditions, particularly those with substantial water involvement, the case may not provide full protection unless further waterproofing steps are taken.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_26", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I’m quite clumsy and I'm always around water, so I need a red camera case that's water resistant. But I'd love it if it had the least number of pockets. Can you find me something that fits these requirements?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"red\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"red\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"red\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_27", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm partial to yellow and black and Pelican is my go-to. Get me the product ID of a case that fits these color and brand preferences.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)` with asin: B0002INQT2", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"yellow\", \"black\") AND brand = \"Pelican\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"yellow\", \"black\") AND brand = \"Pelican\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Pelican' AND (color = 'yellow' OR color = 'black');"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_42", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for photo shoots that last an entire day with me mostly standing?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is suitable for day-long shoots; its lightweight nylon construction helps minimize shoulder and back strain over prolonged usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_28", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I can't stand dealing with all the bells and whistles. Show me the simplest camera case you have that doesn't have any damn pockets and isn't water-resistant.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_50", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Does the Pelican 1120 case come equipped with padlock protectors?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1120 case is fitted with stainless steel reinforced padlock protectors that enhance the case's strength and offer additional protection against cutting and theft.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_43", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this case withstand daily use in a professional photography environment?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is designed to endure the rigors of everyday use, particularly in professional environments. Its nylon make-up provides superior abrasion resistance, ensuring it retains its structure and safeguards your camera amidst regular usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_51", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the bag feature dedicated pockets for storing small items like batteries and memory cards?", "long_answer": "The bag does indeed come with specific storage solutions for small items. It includes padded, easy-access side storage pockets designed to hold extra memory cards and also features a zippered flat pocket on the front to accommodate additional accessories, which provides quick access to essential items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_29", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm looking to add a pop of color to my gear. What's the cheapest camera case you have in yellow or mica?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"yellow\", \"mica\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"yellow\", \"mica\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"yellow\", \"mica\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('yellow', 'mica') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_52", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the case designed to be lightweight and easy to carry despite its rigidity?", "long_answer": "The case is designed to be lightweight to ensure comfortable portability, although some users consider it somewhat heavy, likely because of its rigid structure aimed at protecting the contents inside.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_44", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "As a wildlife photographer, I often encounter rain while in the field. Would acquiring this camera case be advisable for my outdoor photography sessions?", "long_answer": "Certainly, a waterproof camera case would be advantageous for your outdoor wildlife photography endeavors, shielding your camera from the elements such as rain. Nonetheless, bear in mind that repeatedly opening your case in rapid succession may render the waterproof seals less practical, given the additional time needed to securely reseal each time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof property are not suitable for situations where quick access and multiple openings of the case are necessary, as their protective seals can make them less convenient to open frequently.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_45", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this bag fit a Canon EOS 5Ds?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Canon EOS 5Ds should fit as it is similar in size to the Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens which is known to fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS 5Ds has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS 5Ds fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_46", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I need a case that allows for rapid setup prior to filming; does this one facilitate that requirement?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case enables swift setup as it lacks the watertight seals found in waterproof cases, which often require extra time to open or seal properly. Consequently, you spend less time preparing and more time taking those perfect photographs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_53", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the padded laptop compartment suitable for a 17-inch laptop?", "long_answer": "The padded laptop compartment is specifically designed for laptops up to 15.6 inches. Therefore, it is unlikely to accommodate a larger laptop, such as one that is 17 inches.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_30", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I need a camera case that's yellow, but it doesn't need to be water-resistant. However, it should have as many pockets as possible. So, can you find me such a product?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color='yellow' AND water_resistance='no' ORDER BY pockets DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_54", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the Case Logic SLRC-202 camera bag compatible with a Nikon D80 equipped with a 55-300 mm zoom lens?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLRC-202 camera bag is crafted to accommodate most SLRs with a zoom lens attached. It is likely that your Nikon D80 camera with a 55-300 mm zoom lens will fit inside the bag when the lens zoom is fully retracted. To ensure compatibility, it is recommended to compare the size of your camera and lens with the interior measurements of the bag, which are 7.5 inches by 6.5 inches by 4.25 inches.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_47", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "No, this case is designed to fit a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens. I believe the Canon 70-200 F4 lens is larger and would not fit in this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_48", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does this camera case provide a means to securely fasten my tripod during travel?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case features a specialized pocket for a tripod, designed to keep your tripod safe during transit. However, it should be mentioned that this feature adds to the case's weight, a consideration for those who favor a lightweight and minimalistic travel configuration.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket are not suitable for photographers who prioritize the most lightweight and minimalist gear setup, as this feature may add to the bulk and weight of the case.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_55", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the bag include specialized pockets for small items such as batteries and memory cards?", "long_answer": "The bag has various pockets designed for organization, including side and front pockets, and a mesh zipper pocket under the lid, specifically suitable for storing small items such as batteries, memory cards, and cables.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_31", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I need a camera case that can handle a splash, but I do not want a bunch of pockets. Give me the one with the least pockets that still is water resistant.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_49", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this case fit my Nikon D7100 with a 55-300mm VR lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits well, and your Nikon D7100 with a 55-300mm VR lens is of similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Nikon D7100 + 55-300mm VR lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Nikon D7100 + 55-300mm VR lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_50", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Will this case contribute significant bulk to my photography equipment when I aim to pack minimally for a hike?", "long_answer": "No, the camera case won't significantly increase bulk since it's made of nylon, a material that ensures it remains lightweight and perfect for when you need to lighten your load, such as while hiking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_32", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm looking for an orange camera case from either Pelican or Case Logic. What’ve you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Case Logic\") AND color = \"orange\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Case Logic\") AND color = \"orange\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'orange' AND (brand = 'Pelican' OR brand = 'Case Logic');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_56", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Are the padded dividers in the bag's main compartment adjustable or removable?", "long_answer": "The padded dividers inside the main compartment of the bag are designed to be fully adjustable, allowing them to be both repositioned and removed, enabling the user to customize the interior layout to fit their specific camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_57", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the camera sling offer secure storage for small items such as memory cards and batteries?", "long_answer": "The camera sling includes three zippered compartments and pockets on the strap specifically made for small items like memory cards and batteries, ensuring they can be stored securely. However, there have been reports from some users that these smaller pockets are not easily accessible when needed swiftly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_58", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "How durable are the hinge and handle pins on the case?", "long_answer": "The hinge and handle pins on this case are made of stainless steel, a material recognized for its strength and durability, hence contributing to the overall longevity of the case's moving parts.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_51", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case accommodate my Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens? ", "long_answer": "I'm afraid it won't. I have a Nikon D90 which fits just perfectly, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens is considerably bigger than the D90.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Nikon D90, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "search_qa_33", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm only interested in an orange camera case, no pockets needed. Which one do you have that fits this description?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'orange' AND pockets = 0;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_52", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. The product fits with a Nikon D3500 and the Canon Rebel T3 is similar in size to that model, so it should seamlessly fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_59", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is the foam interior of the Pelican 1120 case customizable to hold specific items securely?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1120 is equipped with Pick N'Pluck foam, which enables the user to tailor the case's interior to the unique contours of their items, ensuring a secure and custom fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_53", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Will this backpack fit my Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens and it fits perfectly, and your Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens is similar in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_60", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 backpack comfortable for extended use and travel?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack generally receives positive feedback for its comfort during extended walks and its suitability for travel. Its design features contoured shoulder straps that are effective at distributing weight. Nonetheless, a few users have mentioned that the backpack can become less comfortable when overpacked, particularly if a laptop is included, which isn't its intended purpose.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_34", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm kind of picky when it comes to colors and I don't have more than 50 bucks to spare. Give me the least pocketed camera case in either mica or green.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND color IN (\"mica\", \"green\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND color IN (\"mica\", \"green\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND color IN (\"mica\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND (color = 'mica' OR color = 'green') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_61", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Does this camera backpack meet the needs of travel photographers in terms of space, durability, and storage for additional equipment like laptops and tripods?", "long_answer": "The camera backpack simultaneously provides ample space, high durability, and the convenience of specialized compartments for laptops and tripods, making it particularly suited for the requirements of travel photography.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_35", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I don't need any of that fancy water resistance stuff, just give me a simple mica-colored camera case. What's the product ID for that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND color = \"mica\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND color = \"mica\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'mica' AND water_resistance = 'no';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_36", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I've only got a $10 bill and I'm just tired of black. Give me the cheapest non-black camera case that has the fewest pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND NOT color = \"black\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND NOT color = \"black\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND NOT color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND color != 'black' ORDER BY pockets ASC, price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_54", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can I use this case for my Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be fine. I use it with my Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and your lens has a very similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_55", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to. I use it with a Canon 10-22mm lens which has a similar size to the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_62", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is there a dedicated tripod attachment point on the Lowepro Fastpack 200?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Fastpack 200 backpack lacks a built-in, dedicated attachment point for securing a tripod. Users who require the ability to carry a tripod may have to find creative or improvised solutions for attaching it to the backpack.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_37", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case either in red or black, but I'm tight on cash. Point me to the most affordable one you've got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"black\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"black\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('red', 'black') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_63", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 comfortable to wear for lengthy periods of time?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 is considered comfortable for extended wear by most users, thanks to its breathable, contoured shoulder straps that help evenly distribute the bag's weight across the shoulders.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_38", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I want a case from Ape Case or Canon, but I don't want to break the bank. What's the cheapest one you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Canon\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Canon\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Canon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Ape Case', 'Canon') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_39", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I only have a tenner to spend and I'm only interested in a velcro closure. What's the cheapest camera case you got that checks those boxes?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND closure_type = \"velcro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND closure_type = \"velcro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type = 'velcro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_56", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Based on my experience, it might not. I have the Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses and it fits just right. It seems that your Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens is larger, so it probably won't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_57", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'd like to have my camera case at my hip while hiking. Can it be attached to my hiking equipment?", "long_answer": "Should your hiking gear feature a belt of standard width, the camera case ought to comfortably fit at your hip. Yet, be mindful that if your gear's belt is considerably broader than typical belts, the case may not fit because the loop is too small.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop lack the capability to accommodate very wide belts if their loops are designed only for standard-sized belts, which could limit the options for how they are worn.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_40", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm not into carrying a ton of extra crap in my case. Give me the simplest camera case from Sony or OP/TECH USA, with no more than one pocket.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'OP/TECH USA') AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY pockets LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_58", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can a Canon Rebel T3 fit in this case? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it can. I keep my Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens in this case, and your camera has a similar size to it. You should be able to use this case without any problems.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_41", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Look, I don't want to drop more than 30 dollars and I'm sick and tired of black. Gimme the first camera case you can find that meets these conditions.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND NOT color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND NOT color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND color != 'black' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_64", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this bag suitable as carry-on luggage on most airlines?", "long_answer": "While the dimensions of the bag generally meet the carry-on criteria for most airlines, it is recommended to verify with the particular airline's size restrictions to ensure compatibility. Each airline has its own set of regulations, and confirming beforehand can prevent any travel inconveniences.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_65", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Can the camera case accommodate a camera with an attached wrist strap?", "long_answer": "The camera case is intentionally designed to be compatible with cameras that have wrist straps attached, ensuring that cameras can be securely placed within the case while still keeping the wrist strap easily accessible.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_59", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I plan to film in the Arctic; can this case protect my camera against the frigid temperatures?", "long_answer": "When photographing in the Arctic, it's essential to use a case that offers superior thermal insulation. This current camera case, crafted from nylon, isn't tailored for extreme temperature conditions. It would be advantageous to choose a case engineered with specialized materials that shield against the intense cold characteristic of those environments.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_66", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "How useful do customers find the built-in belt loop on the camera case for carrying the device?", "long_answer": "The majority of customers consider the built-in belt loop on the camera case to be a convenient feature that enhances the ease of carrying the camera.", "short_answer": "very practical", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_42", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I hate buckles and zippers on my camera cases, always sticking or breaking. What's the first product you have that uses either a velcro or drawstring closure?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('velcro', 'drawstring') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_43", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I once lost my stuff because a zipper broke, thus I need a green camera case that doesn't fasten with a zipper. Can you find me one?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' AND closure_type != 'zipper';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_67", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is there a customer service available to assist with the backpack's strap degradation issues?", "long_answer": "In the event of strap degradation or any other issues with the backpack, customer service can be contacted for support as per the included satisfaction guarantee.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_44", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I gotta store a lot of stuff, but I'm picky about style too. I want a red camera case with locks. What's the one with the least pockets you got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND closure_type = 'locks' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_45", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm not into too many pockets and fancy colors. Give me the cheapest camera case you have with less than two pockets in either yellow or teal.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"teal\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"teal\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"teal\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND (color = 'yellow' OR color = 'teal') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_68", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the internal dividers in the main compartment be repositioned to accommodate different camera and lens sizes?", "long_answer": "The main compartment of the camera bag comes equipped with padded dividers that are indeed adjustable, allowing for customization to different sizes of cameras and lenses based on the user's specific requirements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_60", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does this camera case facilitate easier transportation while I'm often on the go?", "long_answer": "Indeed, with the inclusion of backpack straps, this camera case is designed for people who are frequently traveling, offering a significant level of comfort via efficient ergonomic weight distribution, which makes carrying your camera equipment easier and more comfortable.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps typically mean that the user can anticipate a high degree of ergonomics and comfort due to the even distribution of weight across the shoulders, reducing fatigue and strain during extended use.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_46", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I don't want any surprise holes in my expensive gear, show me your cheapest camera case with a lock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'locks' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_61", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon EOS 7D?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Nikon D3500 which fits perfectly and the Canon EOS 7D has similar dimensions to the D3500.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS 7D has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS 7D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_62", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can I use this backpack for a small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E camera? ", "long_answer": "Yes, the product fits with the Nikon D3500, and the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E camera has similar dimensions so it should fit perfectly in this backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_69", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Are the zippers on this product durable enough to withstand frequent use?", "long_answer": "The zippers are made of reinforced metal and come with soft rubber pullers to enhance grip and durability. However, it is worth noting that a minority of customers recommend handling them carefully to prevent snagging.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_70", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can the interior dividers of the backpack be adjusted or removed to accommodate different gear?", "long_answer": "The backpack's interior is designed with fully customizable padded dividers that users can adjust or remove as needed to securely fit a wide range of equipment, offering flexibility in organizing the contents.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_71", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the storage compartment accommodate extra lenses?", "long_answer": "The storage compartment certainly does accommodate extra lenses, featuring two large side compartments specifically designed for this purpose, with each compartment measuring 6 inches in length, 4 inches in width, and 3.5 inches in height.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_72", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "How visible is the Lowepro logo on their products?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro logo on their products is designed to be subtle and not overly conspicuous, catering to the preferences of individuals who desire a discreet appearance for their gear.", "short_answer": "subtle and subdued", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_63", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can I use this with a Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will work. I use a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits perfectly and I believe your camera is similar in size to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_64", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for safely transporting my costly camera gear while flying?", "long_answer": "Although our camera cases are crafted for convenience and accessibility, models equipped with shoulder straps might not offer the utmost security for highly valuable equipment when flying. It is advisable to opt for a lockable carry-on or a robust hard case to bolster security during air travel.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap lack the capability to offer the same level of security as a locked carry-on or hard case, so they might not be the primary choice for transporting extremely valuable or sensitive equipment.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_47", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I want a change of style with a red camera case from Lowepro. Do you have any? What's the product ID?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND brand = \"Lowepro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND brand = \"Lowepro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND brand = 'Lowepro';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_73", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the bag designed with a built-in waist strap to allow it to be worn as a fanny pack?", "long_answer": "The bag is indeed designed with a built-in waist strap, making it versatile enough to be worn as a fanny pack for those who opt for that style or functionality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_74", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the product case available in multiple colors?", "long_answer": "The available information, including product metadata and customer feedback, does not indicate the availability of the case in different colors, suggesting that it likely comes in only one standard color.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_65", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "When not in use, can the camera case be conveniently stored without occupying too much space?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is crafted from a material that enables it to collapse when not in use, making it easy to tuck away without taking up too much space.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_48", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I've got a thing for purple and I like the easy access that velcro provides. Can you find me the cheapest purple camera case with a velcro closure?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND color = \"purple\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND color = \"purple\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND color = \"purple\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' AND closure_type = 'velcro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_75", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the bag's interior provide adequate protection against scratches on camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The interior of the bag is fully padded, which means it provides sufficient cushioning designed to safeguard camera equipment from scratches as well as from impact damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_66", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm somewhat clumsy and concerned about the case tearing. Is this one durable enough to reduce that risk?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the nylon fabric used to craft this camera case is particularly appreciated for its tear resistance. Its durability renders it a superior option for those worried about damage due to unintentional mishaps.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_67", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case accommodate the Pentax K-2 with a Sigma 18-125 lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to. I use it with my Nikon D90 which is about the same size as the Pentax K-2 with that particular Sigma lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_76", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the bag design allow for airflow between the bag and the user's body?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with an air mesh on the back panel, which facilitates air circulation between the user's body and the bag, ensuring better comfort during prolonged use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_68", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon 5DII camera?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it for my Nikon D3500 which is similar in size to the Canon 5DII.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5DII has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5DII fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_49", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I don't want a bulky case with too many pockets, and I'm short on cash too. What's the cheapest camera case you have with less than two pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_50", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm not dealing with too many pockets. Get me the cheapest camera case from OP/TECH USA or Canon with 1 pocket or less.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Canon\") AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Canon\") AND pockets <= 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Canon\") AND pockets <= 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('OP/TECH USA', 'Canon') AND pockets <=1 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_77", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the built-in rain cover effectively keep the backpack's contents dry during rainfall?", "long_answer": "The built-in rain cover enhances the water-resistance of the backpack, offering protection for the contents inside and keeping them dry when it rains unexpectedly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_78", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the bag designed to allow quick access to camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The design of the bag includes clasps that some users find challenging to open, potentially causing delays in accessing camera equipment quickly. This could be a drawback for those who prioritize swift retrieval of their gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_51", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I'm just a simple guy who likes zippers. Do you have any camera cases with zippers? What's the first one that comes up?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'zipper' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_69", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the camera case be stored easily without occupying much space when it's not in use?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is crafted from a material that enables it to be collapsed when not in use, facilitating compact storage and conserving space.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_70", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it can. I have a Nikon D5000 with a battery grip which fits well and it has a similar size to your Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_71", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is this camera case a suitable option for those who prioritize convenience over robust protection against the elements?", "long_answer": "Certainly, if you prioritize convenience and ease of access above safeguarding against water and harsh environmental conditions, this camera case is a fitting option. It forgoes waterproof capabilities to allow for more straightforward and user-friendly access to your camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_72", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can I fit my Canon 70-200 F4 lens into this case?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, this case may not fit your Canon 70-200 F4 lens. It fits my Nikon D90, which is smaller in size compared to your lens.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Nikon D90, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_73", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is this case a suitable option for professional photographers seeking robust support for their equipment?", "long_answer": "Professional photographers typically need robust support for their equipment to avoid damage. Given the inherent pliability of nylon, this camera case might not provide the rigid structure commonly preferred for protecting professional photography equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_79", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the main compartment of the Canon SLR Gadget Bag for EOS or Rebel Cameras customizable to fit a camera with its lens attached?", "long_answer": "The Canon SLR Gadget Bag possesses an adaptable main compartment featuring adjustable dividers, allowing for the accommodation of a camera with the lens still attached. It also offers the capacity to hold extra lenses and accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_52", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm kind of specific with colors. Find me a camera case that comes in teal.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras` with asin: B001I3X3HU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'teal';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_74", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Will the ACPRO2000 fit the 50-500 Sigma lenses? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it with my Canon 70D with a 70-250 mm lens and it fits just fine. Considering your 50-500 Sigma lens is of similar size, it should fit as well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_80", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the camera bag ensure the safety of an SLR camera from impacts and scratches?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is equipped with a suspension hammock system which securely holds the SLR camera above the case's bottom, offering a high level of protection against impacts. Additionally, the compartment lid is lined with scratch-resistant memory foam, which serves to safeguard the camera's screen from potential damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_53", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Look, I only have 10 dollars and I want a camera case from Sony or AmazonBasics. What's the cheapest you got from those brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND brand IN (\"Sony\", \"AmazonBasics\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND brand IN (\"Sony\", \"AmazonBasics\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'AmazonBasics') AND price <= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_75", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Will this case fit a Pentax K-2 with a Sigma 18-125 lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, the case should fit your Pentax K-2 with a Sigma 18-125 lens. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and they are pretty much the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_81", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG camera bag compatible with non-Canon SLR camera bodies?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag is designed to be versatile and can accommodate various SLR camera bodies, including those not manufactured by Canon.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_82", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can the camera strap be stored easily in the bag without getting snagged?", "long_answer": "Users have had varying experiences with the camera strap and its compatibility with storage in the bag; while some have faced issues with it getting snagged, particularly when using the hammock system of the bag, a majority of customers have successfully found sufficient space to store the strap without such problems.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_76", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will this case fit my Nikon D3200 with a Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes it should. I use it for a Nikon D5000 with battery grip and they're similar in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_83", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the Canon 200DG camera bag come with a warranty?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag includes a warranty as indicated by the product metadata. However, to understand the specific terms and duration of the warranty, it would be necessary to consult with the seller or refer to Canon's official warranty documentation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_77", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this camera case remain secure while I'm hiking or traversing difficult terrain?", "long_answer": "This camera case features a handy belt loop for straightforward attachment, yet it might not fulfill the robustness and protection needs for individuals participating in strenuous pursuits such as hiking. It would be wise to look at cases offering different carrying solutions tailored for demanding settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop fail to meet the requirements for those who need to carry their camera case in a rugged or challenging environment that would benefit from alternative carrying methods.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_84", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the backpack have space for items other than camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed primarily for photographic equipment; however, it permits the storage of small personal items in the top compartment, although space for such items is limited.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_78", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this case designed to be used in environments with high levels of humidity, such as close to waterfalls or beaches?", "long_answer": "The absence of waterproofing in this camera case prevents it from fully blocking moisture or water droplets from seeping into the case. In areas with high humidity, like close to waterfalls or on the beach, the risk of moisture getting to your camera is higher, thus opting for a waterproof camera case would be a more secure option for such environments.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_54", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Look, I need a yellow camera case that can handle a splash or two. Sort out the cheapest one for me, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)` with asin: B000WH86BQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'yellow' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_85", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the Canon SLR Gadget Bag have the capacity to carry a tripod?", "long_answer": "The Canon SLR Gadget Bag is equipped with tripod straps, specifically designed to secure a tripod and enable convenient transportation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_55", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm rather fond of USA Gear's stuff but steer clear of anything mica-colored. Can you find me their cheapest camera case that isn't that color?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR` with asin: B005J09OXU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND color <> 'mica' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_79", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can it fit a Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "I don't believe so. I use it with a Nikon D5200 with two lenses and it just fits. Your camera and lens take up more space than my setup.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_80", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can this case hold a Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately no, I am using it for my Nikon D5000 with a battery grip which just fits this bag. The Nikon D800 with a 300 mm lens is larger, so it wouldn't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "search_qa_56", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I don't need a bunch of pockets to fuss with. Just give me a Sony or Altura Photo case with 2 or fewer pockets. What's the product number of the first one you find?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Altura Photo\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Altura Photo\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = \"Sony\" OR brand = \"Altura Photo\") AND pockets <= 2 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_57", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I've got something against green and zippers just rub me the wrong way. What's the first camera case you got that doesn't have either?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'green' AND closure_type != 'zipper' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_86", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Are the provided instructions for adjusting and using the straps and handle easy to understand?", "long_answer": "The clarity of the instructions for adjusting and using the straps and handle is considered insufficient by some customers. Proper guidance on manipulating these components is deemed necessary to improve the overall user experience and satisfaction with the product.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_81", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this case appropriate for photography in scenarios where holding the camera isn't feasible, such as when utilizing a remote shutter?", "long_answer": "In scenarios requiring hands-free camera operation, such as using a remote shutter, the absence of a tripod attachment on this camera case will not offer the required stability on its own. It is recommended to use a case compatible with a tripod for such situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_82", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can the camera case be stored easily without occupying much space when not in use?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is crafted from a material that enables it to be collapsibly folded when not in use, making it easy to stow away without taking up significant space.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_87", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the Ape Case ACPRO2000 comfortable to carry when fully loaded?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack is typically found to be comfortable for carrying due to features such as its adjustable harness and sternum strap that evenly distribute weight. However, user comfort can decrease with extended use, especially if the bag is overloaded.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_83", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I occasionally feel discomfort when I carry bags. Could this camera case be carried comfortably for long durations?", "long_answer": "Should you suffer from a medical condition or pain that exacerbates with uneven weight distribution, a camera bag with a shoulder strap might cause discomfort over extended periods. It is advisable to look into alternative carrying methods that more equally disperse the weight throughout your body.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not suitable for users who may have medical conditions or pain that is exacerbated by carrying weight on one side of the body; other carrying options may be better in these cases.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_84", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can I comfortably carry the camera case for extended periods?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case features an ergonomic hand grip designed to enhance comfort and minimize hand fatigue during extended periods of carrying, as it is molded to align with the natural shape of your hand.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with an ergonomic hand grip typically mean that users will experience increased comfort and reduced hand fatigue, especially during prolonged carrying sessions, due to the grip's design shaped to fit the natural contours of the hand.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_85", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit just fine. I have a Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens which fits perfectly. The Nikon D750 with the AF-S NIKKOR lens is about the same size so it should fit in this bag without any problems.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_86", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can this case fit my Nikon D5000? ", "long_answer": "Yes, the Nikon D3500 and Nikon D5000 have similar size dimensions, so your Nikon D5000 should also fit in this case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Nikon D5000 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Nikon D5000 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_88", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Does the case have a stylish and modern design?", "long_answer": "The style of the case is subjective and varies from person to person. It has been described as having a casual and lightweight design, suggesting a functional and simple aesthetic rather than a focus on high fashion or modern trends.", "short_answer": "subjective", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_89", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does this backpack have a dedicated feature to secure a tripod?", "long_answer": "The backpack includes a Hideaway Tripod Mount designed specifically for securing either a compact or medium-sized tripod to the pack, ensuring that photographers can carry their tripods safely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_87", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Would this case fit a Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens and it fits well in this case. The Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G is similar in size so it should also fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_88", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be okay. I use it with my Canon 70D with a 70-250mm lens which is a very similar size to a 70D with a 135mm lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_58", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm only looking at AmazonBasics and Case Logic, but I don't need any of that water resistance nonsense. What's the first product you got that matches that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras` with asin: B005VTIMEQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Case Logic\") AND water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Case Logic\") AND water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'AmazonBasics' OR brand = 'Case Logic') AND water_resistance = 'no' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_90", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the backpack designed to meet the needs of professional videographers for equipment storage and organization?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with a customizable interior and multiple storage pockets, enabling professional videographers to organize and store their equipment efficiently, rendering it highly suitable for their specific needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_59", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm into vibrant stuff, and I need a camera case. Got something in teal or red? What's the cheapest one you can show me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras` with asin: B001I3X3HU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"red\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"red\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"red\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('teal', 'red') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_91", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is there a designated space for a charger in the Canon PSC-85 camera case?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 camera case lacks a dedicated space specifically for storing a charger. It is primarily designed to house the camera itself along with smaller accessories, such as batteries and memory cards.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_92", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Does the Canon PSC-85 case have a soft exterior as implied by its name?", "long_answer": "The exterior of the Canon PSC-85 case is constructed from a type of nylon that is somewhat stiff. While the case is considered a \"soft bag\" and not hardshell, the stiffness actually lends it some rigidity which serves to enhance the level of protection it offers to the camera inside.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_89", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case accommodate a Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, I don't believe it will. I use it with my Nikon D90 and it fits just right. The Rebel xsi with a 55-250mm lens is considerably larger than the D90, so I doubt it would fit properly.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Nikon D90, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "search_qa_60", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I need a camera case with a lock, but I don't want to go over a hundred dollars. Plus, I hate too many pockets. Find me one that meets these conditions.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND price <= 100 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND price <= 100 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND price <= 100 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'locks' \nAND price <= 100 \nAND pockets < 3;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_61", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm pretty hooked on Sony stuff. Can you tell me the product id of a Sony camera case you carry?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Sony\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Sony\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Sony';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_93", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the sling strap of this backpack be adjusted to fit various body types?", "long_answer": "The sling strap of this backpack is designed to be adjustable, allowing users to modify it for a comfortable fit across different body sizes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_90", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Should a sudden shift in weather catch me outside, will my camera remain safe in this case?", "long_answer": "The degree of weather change is crucial. Canvas camera cases aren't entirely waterproof nor do they offer full insulation against extreme temperatures. Thus, should the weather shift involve intense rain, or particularly high or low temperatures, your camera might not be adequately shielded unless the case receives extra weatherproofing.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with canvas material are not suitable for extreme weather conditions without proper treatment since canvas is not inherently completely waterproof or insulated against severe temperatures.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "canvas", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_62", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I can't stand the color yellow and I need a camera case with a velcro closure type, what's the cheapest option I got except for the annoyingly yellow ones?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND NOT color = \"yellow\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND NOT color = \"yellow\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND NOT color = \"yellow\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'yellow' AND closure_type = 'velcro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_91", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Will this case significantly increase the bulk of my photography equipment when I aim to pack lightly for a hike?", "long_answer": "No, the camera case won't significantly increase bulk since it's made of nylon, which ensures it remains lightweight and perfect for situations requiring a lighter load, such as hiking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_94", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the case explicitly described as waterproof or weather-resistant?", "long_answer": "The case's description does not specifically mention waterproof or weather-resistant features. Although it's constructed from high-quality materials that offer some level of protection against the elements, it's not designed to withstand extreme conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_63", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm all about the teal, but I can't stand lots of pockets. Give me the least pocketed teal camera case you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras` with asin: B001I3X3HU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color ='teal' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_95", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera sling designed to accommodate telephoto zoom lenses?", "long_answer": "The camera sling has a designated compartment that can hold an SLR with a standard lens and provides extra space for additional lenses, including some telephoto zoom lenses. However, it may not be suitable for very large lenses or those with attached hoods, as they might not fit through the sling's opening or could be a tight fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_96", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "What is the durability of the backpack's materials based on customer feedback?", "long_answer": "The backpack is constructed with a black polyester/nylon exterior, and customer feedback indicates that these materials are robust and tend to maintain their quality over extended periods of use.", "short_answer": "durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_64", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm a little clumsy so I require a water resistant camera case. Preference is for AmazonBasics. Which ones are available?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"AmazonBasics\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"AmazonBasics\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'AmazonBasics' AND water_resistance = 'yes';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_65", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm not looking to spend over 30 dollars and I want a camera case with locks, not zippers. Find me the one with the fewest pockets.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND closure_type = 'locks' AND closure_type != 'zipper' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_97", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the closure method of this camera case considered secure by customers?", "long_answer": "The camera case employs Velcro for its closure mechanism. While Velcro is recognized for providing a reasonably secure seal, there are customers who believe that alternatives such as zippers or locking clips offer a higher level of security.", "short_answer": "generally yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_98", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is there a designated area in the backpack to store personal items separate from camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with a separate space in the top area specifically for storing personal items, apart from the main compartment intended for camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_99", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Does the bag's shoulder pad design provide comfort for extended wear?", "long_answer": "The bag features a removable, padded shoulder pad with a non-slip patch, which is recognized by customers as contributing to the bag's comfort when worn over extended periods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_66", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Listen, I need a case that's both water resistant and either from Pelican or Canon. Oh, and it better not have too many pockets. Can you find something like that for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Canon\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Canon\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Canon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND (brand = 'Canon' OR brand = 'Pelican') AND pockets < 2;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_67", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Hey, I don't need anything fancy - no pockets or water resistance. Just find me the simplest camera case you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_100", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the stitching on the case durable over time, particularly around the zipper?", "long_answer": "The case is generally well-constructed, but durability concerns have arisen from a handful of customers, especially regarding stitching around the zipper area, which may become a weak point and unravel after significant usage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_68", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm partial to \"USA Gear\" and \"AmazonBasics\". Toss me the first product ID you got from either one of those brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"AmazonBasics\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"AmazonBasics\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'AmazonBasics') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_69", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I can't stand those water-resistant cases, but I still need something secure. Can you find me a camera case that uses a lock or a zipper but isn't water-resistant?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras` with asin: B005VTIMEQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('locks', 'zipper') AND water_resistance = 'no';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_101", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can the internal padded dividers of the product be adjusted with ease?", "long_answer": "The internal dividers, which are padded, can be adjusted easily as per the feedback from users who have found them both thick and pliable.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_102", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack capable of accommodating a professional DSLR with a large attached lens?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack is specifically designed to accommodate a professional DSLR camera with a large lens attached, catering to lenses as substantial as an 80-200mm f/2.8. In addition to a large lens, the backpack can also hold 2-4 additional lenses or flash units, plus various other accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_103", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the backpack known for its durability over extended periods of regular use?", "long_answer": "The backpack is considered to have a durable build quality, as the majority opinion suggests that it can endure regular usage over an extended timeframe without significant wear and tear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_92", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I require a camera case that offers rapid attachment and detachment to my tripod; will this model facilitate such functionality without succumbing to premature wear?", "long_answer": "This camera case has been specifically engineered for swift attachment and detachment, thanks to its hook and loop fastener, proving handy for photographers who require rapid mobility. Nonetheless, caution is advised if it's to be used in settings with regular exposure to abrasive substances, as such contact may hasten the wear of the fastener and could subsequently diminish its durability.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with tripod attachment using hook and loop fastener are not recommended for photographers who frequently work in abrasive environments, as the hook and loop material is prone to wear, and its reliability could be compromised when attached to tripods that constantly scrape against rough surfaces.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "hook and loop fastener", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_104", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the ACPRO2000 camera bag offer protection against water-related elements?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 is constructed using water-resistant nylon material, providing an inherent level of protection against water. Additionally, it comes equipped with a built-in rain cover to further safeguard against adverse weather conditions, ensuring enhanced protection from the elements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_93", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Does this camera case come with an integrated feature that enables me to secure it to my tripod?", "long_answer": "Regrettably, the camera case does not come with an integrated option for direct tripod attachment. Should a tripod be a crucial component of your photographic work, it may be necessary to explore alternative cases or implement an additional camera support system in conjunction with this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_70", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm all about convenience, mate. Show me the camera case with the least amount of pockets from either USA Gear or Canon.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Canon\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Canon\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Canon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'Canon') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_94", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Will this case accommodate a Canon t5i with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Nikon D5000 with a battery grip, and it fits well. The size of your Canon t5i with a 300mm lens is similar to mine, so it should fit in this case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "search_qa_71", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I don't carry many accessories and I fancy security, find me a camera case with less or average pockets and with a lock. Most importantly, one that doesn't make me look like a walking storage unit.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND closure_type = \"locks\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND closure_type = \"locks\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'locks' AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_105", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this bag capable of holding a DSLR camera with an attached zoom lens and extra lenses?", "long_answer": "Yes, the bag is designed to accommodate a DSLR camera with a zoom lens attached to it, as well as additional lenses. The bag's storage compartments and protective padding provide sufficient space for carrying a camera setup that includes an extra zoom lens among other camera accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_72", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I need a camera case with a velcro closure and I prefer AmazonBasics or USA Gear products. Can you find one for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"USA Gear\") AND closure_type = \"velcro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"USA Gear\") AND closure_type = \"velcro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'velcro' AND (brand = 'AmazonBasics' OR brand = 'USA Gear');"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_95", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can I use this case for my Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "No, it won't fit. I have a Nikon D90 that perfectly fits in this case and it's fairly certain that the size of your lens is larger than the D90.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Nikon D90, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "search_qa_73", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm quite picky with brands - I only want a camera case from Sony or Lowepro. What's the first one that pops up in your system?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Lowepro\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Lowepro\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'Lowepro') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_96", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this case accommodate a 6D with a 24-105mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I own a Nikon D90 and it fits just fine. The 6D with a 24-105mm lens is quite similar in size to the Nikon D90, so it should work.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the 6D w/24-105mm lens has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the 6D w/24-105mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_106", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Does the bag feature a specific pocket designed to hold a water bottle?", "long_answer": "The bag comes with an exterior pocket that is designed specifically to accommodate a water bottle or items of similar shape, thus providing dedicated space for hydration storage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_107", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the Sony LCS-CST carrying case designed with a shoulder strap?", "long_answer": "The Sony LCS-CST carrying case is specifically designed with a belt loop for carrying convenience. It does not include a shoulder strap, as there is no mention of such a feature in the product description or metadata.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_97", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is this case designed with the minimalist style that is suitable for discreet photography assignments?", "long_answer": "No, since the camera case features d-ring or clip attachments, it does not present the minimalist design desired for discreet scenarios, because these components are visible and contribute to the case's overall profile.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with d-ring or clip attachments fail to meet the requirements for users who demand a highly discreet or low-profile case, as the attachment points, despite being aesthetically integrated, are still visible and potentially add to the case's silhouette.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "d-ring or clip attachments", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_98", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I have a tendency to be somewhat clumsy, and my concern is that the case may tear. Is this particular one durable enough to reduce that likelihood?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the nylon fabric used to construct this camera case is particularly prized for its tear-resistant properties. Its durability renders it an outstanding option for those wary of damage due to inadvertent mishandling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_74", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm looking to add a pop of color to my gear. Do you have a yellow camera case that has a lock? Find me the best one.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'yellow' AND closure_type = 'locks' ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_108", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is there a designated compartment in this bag for safely storing memory cards and small items?", "long_answer": "The bag contains two interior pockets equipped with hook-and-loop closures, specifically designed to offer secure and easily accessible storage for minor accessories, including memory cards.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_75", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I don't need any pockets, just a simple teal-colored camera case. What's the product ID for that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND color = \"teal\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND color = \"teal\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND color = 'teal';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_99", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can this case fit Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime?", "long_answer": "Yes. I am using this case for a Nikon D3500, and it fits fine. Your Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime is a similar size, so it should work.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_76", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I can't be dealing with multiple pockets, so I need a camera case that has none. It should either be a Pelican or Lowepro, so find me one of those.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Lowepro\") AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Lowepro\") AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND (brand = 'Pelican' OR brand = 'Lowepro');"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_100", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera case's tripod attachment system sturdy enough to withstand adventure photography in harsh environments?", "long_answer": "For adventure photography in harsh environments, the hook and loop mechanism used to attach the tripod to the camera case may not be the most reliable option. Exposure to vigorous activity can compromise the fastener's ability to maintain a secure grip on the tripod, potentially endangering your gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with tripod attachment using hook and loop fastener are not suitable for extreme weather conditions or rough handling, as the fastener's grip may diminish when exposed to elements like rain or mud, which can adhere to and degrade the fastener material.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "hook and loop fastener", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_101", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I worry about how long my camera case will last, as I'm somewhat harsh with my equipment. Would purchasing this be a wise investment?", "long_answer": "Given your concerns, investing in this camera case would be a smart decision. The case is crafted from nylon, a material celebrated for its durability and abrasion resistance, suggesting that it is capable of withstanding rough usage and is likely to extend the protective lifespan of your equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_102", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does this camera case feature a convenient carrying option that doesn't sacrifice style significantly?", "long_answer": "This camera case comes with a shoulder strap that offers convenience and comfort for daily use. It is important to mention, though, that although it is pragmatic, the design emphasizes functionality over a sleek or luxurious appearance that some users may prefer.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap fail to meet the requirements for users seeking a fashionable accessory, as the strap's primary focus is on functionality and comfort over luxury aesthetics.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_103", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG accommodate an A-99 with a vertical grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, this bag should be able to accommodate an A-99 with a vertical grip. I use it to carry my Nikon D3500, and they are roughly the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the A-99 with vertical grip has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the A-99 with vertical grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_109", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "What is the duration of the warranty provided with this bag?", "long_answer": "This product is distributed by Amazon.com and comes with a one-year warranty under the AmazonBasics brand.", "short_answer": "one-year", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_104", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can this bag hold a Canon T3i with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits well. Your Canon T3i with a 300mm lens is of similar size, so it should fit too.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon T3i with 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon T3i with 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_110", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the bag's design with its adjustable straps contribute to wearer comfort and ease of movement?", "long_answer": "Users often report that the bag's adjustable shoulder and waist straps, along with its sling design, significantly contribute to the overall comfort when worn. Additionally, these features enhance the ease of accessing the bag's contents and the wearer's ability to move freely without restriction.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_111", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the case come with a belt loop for attachment?", "long_answer": "The case has a belt loop stitched on its back, enabling belt attachment. However, it is important to note that attaching the case to a belt may necessitate the belt's removal for threading the case onto it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_105", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is this case suitable for protecting my camera from dust when it’s not in use?", "long_answer": "Although a canvas camera case provides protection from general dust, it isn't the ideal choice for situations demanding complete dust prevention. The canvas fabric may not possess the necessary impermeability for specific professional or scientific contexts, where even minimal levels of contamination can pose a problem.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with canvas material fail to meet the requirements for high-tech or specialized environments (like cleanrooms or scientific labs) where materials need to prevent dust, lint, and fibers from contaminating sensitive equipment.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "canvas", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_112", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is there dedicated storage space in the bag for a charger and extra batteries?", "long_answer": "The bag features compartments that customers often use for storing their chargers and extra batteries, indicating that it can accommodate these items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_113", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 backpack large enough to accommodate extra equipment for extended hikes?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack is designed to be suitable for short to medium hikes; however, when it comes to longer excursions requiring additional gear such as coats or a tripod, a larger backpack may be necessary to comfortably carry everything.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_114", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can this bag be considered waterproof?", "long_answer": "The bag features a durable, water-repellent nylon exterior which offers a degree of resistance to water exposure. However, it is not designed to be fully waterproof, and thus, while it can protect against light rain and moisture, it shouldn't be relied upon to keep contents dry under all wet conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_115", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is there a designated area in the sling backpack for storing personal items such as a cell phone or keys?", "long_answer": "The sling backpack provides additional storage specifically for personal items, including a zippered pocket located at the top of the bag, making it convenient to store small essentials.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_116", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the camera bag capable of standing upright unassisted?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is designed with a square bottom that enables it to stand upright on its own, ensuring stability and preventing it from tipping over.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_117", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG camera bag typically deemed adequate for the needs of professional photographers?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag is often considered appropriate for professional photographers due to its generous size and robust protective features. However, the suitability can vary as it largely depends on the specific requirements of a professional, including the volume and type of equipment they need to carry for their assignments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_106", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to. I use it with a Canon 10-22mm lens and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens is around the same size, so it should fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_77", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I don't need any fancy water resistance or any of that. Just get me your cheapest drawstring or velcro camera case that doesn't have it.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('drawstring', 'velcro') AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_118", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the holster case come with its own strap for carrying without the camera's strap?", "long_answer": "The holster is specifically designed to attach to the camera's strap and does not include a separate strap for independent carrying, making it less convenient to carry on its own.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_119", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the Ape Case ACPRO2000 bag constructed to withstand extensive and rugged trips?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 is crafted with a strong, water-resistant nylon exterior specifically to endure rugged use, as reported by a majority of users who have experienced its durability during extensive trips.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_78", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I don't need a camera case with too many pockets, and I quite like the Ape Case brand. Can you tell me what's their cheapest case with less than two pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND brand = \"Ape Case\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND brand = \"Ape Case\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND brand = \"Ape Case\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Ape Case' AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_120", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack's design prevent equipment from falling out when opened?", "long_answer": "The backpack is specifically designed with body-side access to reduce the chance of equipment falling out, ensuring that items remain secure inside the backpack even when accessing gear while standing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_121", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the design of this backpack contribute to comfort during prolonged use?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with features such as padded straps and breathable material, contributing to user comfort during extended periods. Comfort levels may differ from person to person and also depend on the load being carried in the backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_107", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is it safe to bring this camera case to the shore without concern for water damage?", "long_answer": "The camera case's fabric provides a degree of moisture resistance, yet it isn't entirely waterproof unless further treated. It's advisable to implement extra protective measures when exposing it to harsher elements such as sand and saltwater.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_108", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens fit in this backpack?", "long_answer": "No, this case is compatible with a Canon 10-22mm lens. The Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens is larger and may not fit properly.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_79", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm only looking for Sony brand camera cases with a velcro closure, but don't quote me any high prices. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Sony\" AND closure_type = \"velcro\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Sony\" AND closure_type = \"velcro\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Sony\" AND closure_type = \"velcro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Sony' AND closure_type = 'velcro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_122", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the Canon SLR Gadget Bag designed to resist weather conditions?", "long_answer": "The Canon SLR Gadget Bag is specifically designed to resist adverse weather conditions. It is made from rugged, water-repellent nylon material and includes an overlapping weather cover, providing additional protection for photographic equipment against rain or other elements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_109", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the camera case designed for prolonged travel and capable of withstanding heavy loads?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the backpack straps on the camera case are designed for comfort even when carrying heavier loads. These straps enable ergonomic weight distribution, making the case ideal for prolonged travel.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps typically mean that the user can anticipate a high degree of ergonomics and comfort due to the even distribution of weight across the shoulders, reducing fatigue and strain during extended use.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_123", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the camera case advertised as being waterproof?", "long_answer": "The camera case is not advertised as waterproof. It is constructed from durable nylon material which can provide certain levels of moisture resistance, yet it is not engineered to withstand submersion in water or to protect the contents from heavy rain.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_80", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I don't like lugging around a big bag, so I need a camera case with no more than 2 pockets. And, make it orange. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND color = \"orange\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND color = \"orange\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND color = \"orange\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND color = 'orange' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_81", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm only eyeing stuff from Ape Case or Case Logic. What's the cheapest camera case you have from either of these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Case Logic\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Case Logic\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Case Logic\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Ape Case', 'Case Logic') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_110", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will my 6D w/24-105mm lens fit in this Pelican 1200 case?", "long_answer": "Yes, your 6D w/24-105mm lens should fit. I successfully fit my Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens into it, and based on the similar dimensions, your lens should fit as well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the 6D w/24-105mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the 6D w/24-105mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_82", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I don't care about water resistance, but I want a yellow camera case. What's the first one you got that fits my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"yellow\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"yellow\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'yellow' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_124", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is this camera bag suitable for storing a Canon T4i along with several lenses and accessories?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is specifically designed to accommodate a smaller SLR camera body like the Canon T4i, multiple lenses, and other accessories. It features adjustable padded dividers that enable the secure organization and protection of the camera and its accompanying equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_125", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this bag suitable for carrying a laptop?", "long_answer": "The bag is primarily designed to hold cameras and their accessories, and given the size constraints, it is not intended to carry a laptop.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_111", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can this case fit the Canon EOS Rebel SL1? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it can. The case is suitable for Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens and the size of your Canon EOS Rebel SL1 is similar to Canon 70D, so it should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_126", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "What is the current price of the Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case is listed with a retail price of $17.00.", "short_answer": "$17.00", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_112", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for swift equipment swaps in changing weather conditions?", "long_answer": "Indeed, when operating in erratic weather that necessitates quick adjustments to equipment, this camera case, featuring D-ring or clip attachments, enables rapid detachment and attachment of your camera. This provides the essential versatility to adapt swiftly to varying conditions, ensuring you capture every moment seamlessly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with d-ring or clip attachments are ideally used for location shooting and outdoor photography where stability and quick setup are essential, augmenting the capabilities of adventure and landscape photographers.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "d-ring or clip attachments", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_113", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for me when I aim to reduce motion and sound during photography in serene settings?", "long_answer": "In tranquil settings where minimizing motion and sound is essential, a camera case designed for hand-carrying or snug attachment to your body, free from dangling straps, proves more suitable than one with a shoulder strap prone to swinging and generating noise.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not recommended for situations where stealth is necessary, as the motion of a dangling strap might draw unwanted attention or noise, unlike a case that is carried by a handle or secured closer to the body.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_127", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is the camera pouch design compatible with using a neck strap simultaneously?", "long_answer": "The case is specifically designed to accommodate a camera's neck strap, allowing it to remain functional and accessible while the camera is enclosed in the pouch.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_128", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack designed to accommodate a substantial amount of photographic equipment?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 is indeed designed to cater to photographers who require a spacious backpack, featuring ample room and customizable padding, allowing it to hold a large amount of gear.", "short_answer": "Yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_114", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can the Ape Case fit Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I'm using this backpack for a Canon 70D with a 70-250mm lens, which is roughly the same size as your Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G. So, it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_115", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is this case a suitable option for professional photographers in search of robust support for their equipment?", "long_answer": "Professional photographers typically need robust support for their equipment to avoid damage. Given nylon's inherent flexibility, this camera case might not provide the solid structure usually preferred for the protection of professional photographic equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_129", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the bag suitable for carrying equipment during hiking and outdoor photography activities?", "long_answer": "The bag is explicitly designed for outdoor activities, including hiking and photography, as it provides ease of access and comfortable carrying. However, one must take into account the bag's space when planning to carry various equipment, suggesting that while it is suitable, the space may not accommodate all gear needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_130", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the inner lining of the camera compartment offer scratch-resistant protection for the camera's screen?", "long_answer": "Yes, the inner lining of the camera compartment includes scratch-resistant memory foam which serves to safeguard the camera's screen from potential damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_83", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I'm only interested in Pelican and AmazonBasics brands for my camera case. Can you tell me which one is the cheapest between these two?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"AmazonBasics\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"AmazonBasics\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Pelican', 'AmazonBasics') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_84", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm only interested in \"Case Logic\" and \"USA Gear\" brands and I don't want a bunch of pockets on my camera case. Tell me the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"USA Gear\") AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"USA Gear\") AND pockets < 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"USA Gear\") AND pockets < 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'USA Gear') AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_116", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for safe transportation of my expensive camera equipment during air travel?", "long_answer": "Our camera cases are crafted for convenience and ease of access; however, those equipped with a shoulder strap might not offer the utmost security for highly valuable equipment during air travel. You may want to explore a lockable carry-on or a rigid case option for increased security in these situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap lack the capability to offer the same level of security as a locked carry-on or hard case, so they might not be the primary choice for transporting extremely valuable or sensitive equipment.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_85", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I don't have time for complicated closures. Find me the cheapest camera case, either with a drawstring or a zipper.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('drawstring', 'zipper') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_131", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is there space for personal items in addition to camera equipment in the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is primarily designed for carrying camera gear but does include a limited amount of space for small personal items. However, it may not be suitable for carrying larger personal items or a laptop, for which a bigger backpack would be recommended.", "short_answer": "limited space", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_132", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the backpack provide a side-entry compartment for quick camera access without full removal?", "long_answer": "The backpack offers a convenient side-entry compartment designed specifically for camera users, which allows for swift retrieval of the camera and its accessories without the necessity of taking the backpack off entirely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_133", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is a rain cover included with the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG does not come with a dedicated rain cover as part of its accessories.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_86", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I can't stand the color mica, don't even show it to me. What's the camera case with the least pockets that comes in any other color?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'mica' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_87", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I don't need any fancy waterproof stuff or loads of pockets. Just find me the simplest camera case you have, okay?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets < 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets < 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_134", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is a separate strap or belt loop included with this camera case?", "long_answer": "The camera case is designed to be attached to the camera's existing strap and does not include a separate strap or a belt loop of its own.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_117", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Will this case fit a Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "No, I don't believe so. I have a Nikon D3500 and it just fits in this case. The Canon 70-200 F4 lens is larger than my Nikon D3500, so it probably won't fit in this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_118", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens fit in this case?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not. I have a Canon 70D with a 18-55mm lens, which perfectly fits in this case. Given that the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense is larger, it would not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_135", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the backpack suitable for carrying a mirrorless camera system?", "long_answer": "Yes, the backpack is designed to accommodate different types of camera systems, including mirrorless cameras, thanks to the adjustable dividers that can be tailored to fit various camera sizes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_119", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Will the camera case become burdensome to carry during prolonged journeys?", "long_answer": "No, the camera case won't be overly burdensome since it's crafted from nylon, known for its lightweight design. This is especially advantageous for photographers who frequently travel and must transport their gear for extended durations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_88", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Listen, I'm trying to save some bucks here, so find me your cheapest camera case under 10 dollars, but make sure it's not yellow, okay?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND NOT color = \"yellow\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND NOT color = \"yellow\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND color <> 'yellow' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_136", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is a shoulder strap included with this case for carrying?", "long_answer": "The case comes with a built-in shoulder strap that facilitates easy transportation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_120", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I frequently hike with my camera; is this case durable enough to endure persistent rubbing against coarse surfaces such as rocks or twigs?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is crafted from nylon, a material selected for its durability against frequent rubbing against coarse surfaces. Its robustness to abrasion ensures it can withstand the challenges of hiking, including interactions with elements like rocks or branches.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_137", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the case's interior material prevent scratches on the contents inside?", "long_answer": "The interior of the case is designed with a soft material that serves to protect the contents from being scratched during transport.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_121", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Will this camera case prove easy to transport on extended treks?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is designed to be both lightweight and compact, making it an ideal selection for extended treks where carrying extra weight or bulk is undesirable. It is engineered to provide simplicity and practicality, without significantly increasing your load, perfectly suiting the demands of active and on-the-go photography.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_122", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens which is around the same size as the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G and it fits perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_123", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can I use this case for my Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid it won't fit. I use this case for my Nikon D3500 and its size is smaller than your Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_89", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm trying to minimize bulk, what's the Canon camera case with the least amount of pockets that you guys sell?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Canon' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_90", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I don't have a lot to spend and I can't stand the brand \"Case Logic\". Show me the least pocketed camera case under 30 dollars, but any brand except that.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND brand <> 'Case Logic' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_138", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does the bag have waterproof or water-resistant capabilities?", "long_answer": "The product description does not clearly state that the bag is waterproof or water-resistant. It offers some degree of moisture protection, yet for comprehensive safeguarding against substantial rain, the use of an additional rain cover is advised.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_139", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "What type of fastener is used on the Canon PSC-85's top flap?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 utilizes velcro as the fastening mechanism for its top flap, providing users with a convenient and quick means to access their camera.", "short_answer": "velcro", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_124", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can I swiftly access my camera from this case to capture a shot in the moment?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is structured for enhanced accessibility, owing to the absence of complex sealing systems such as watertight zippers or locks commonly included in waterproof cases. This feature facilitates the rapid removal of your camera, perfect for capturing those spontaneous, fleeting moments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_140", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the compact size of this backpack accommodate air travel as a carry-on item?", "long_answer": "The backpack's compact size is highly conducive to air travel, as it has been found by users to be convenient for carrying on an airplane without any hassle.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_91", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Velcro just ain't my thing and I don't need any extra pockets. Get me the cheapest camera case you have without any of those features.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'velcro' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_141", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera sling from Case Logic considered durable by its users?", "long_answer": "The camera sling is generally regarded by users as well-constructed and durable, although there have been instances where isolated reports pointed out premature wear or damage. Nonetheless, Case Logic's customer service has shown responsiveness in resolving any such reported issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_142", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the camera gear be accessed from the backpack without removing it?", "long_answer": "The backpack features a specifically designed quick-access side opening that enables you to retrieve your camera gear swiftly and effortlessly without the need to take off the backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_92", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm tired of messing with annoying latches. Get me your cheapest camera case that zips up, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'zipper' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_143", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the comfort sling design of this bag suitable for comfortably fitting individuals with larger body sizes?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with an adjustable comfort sling to fit a variety of body sizes. However, reports from some larger individuals indicate that while it can be adjusted to fit, the bag may look small when worn on a larger frame.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_93", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm not into fancy closures. Just give me the cheapest camera case you have that either closes with a drawstring or velcro.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('drawstring', 'velcro') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_94", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Look, I need a camera case with either a zipper or velcro, nothing fancy. And less pockets, the better. What's the best match for this?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'velcro') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_95", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I hate carrying bulky stuff, so I need a camera case that's under 50 bucks and has no more than one pocket. What's the best you can offer?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_125", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this case alleviate the tension in my wrist while transporting my professional photography gear?", "long_answer": "Indeed, using a camera case with a hand grip could exacerbate wrist strain when transporting heavy professional camera equipment. Concentrating the weight in the hand can intensify strain and discomfort rather than alleviate it. A case that more evenly disperses weight would be advantageous for hefty gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip fail to meet the requirements for heavy-duty use where substantial weight distribution across the torso is necessary, as they concentrate the camera's weight onto one point of the hand.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_144", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the main compartment of the Case Logic SLRC-205 large enough for a Canon T3i with a 55-200mm lens attached?", "long_answer": "The main holster compartment of the Case Logic SLRC-205 is specifically designed to house most SLR camera bodies with their attached standard lenses. Hence, it should have no issue fitting a Canon T3i with a 55-200mm lens attached.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_96", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I can't spend over a hundred and I absolutely hate too many pockets. Show me your least expensive camera case with not more than 2 pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND pockets <= 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND pockets <= 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_145", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the price of this item remain constant over time?", "long_answer": "The item's price is subject to change and can vary due to different influencing factors. Although there is an effort to maintain competitive pricing, the cost is not guaranteed to be stable, and customers are advised to verify the price when considering a purchase.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_97", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I don't need a bunch of pockets, just something that locks or has velcro. What's your least pocketed case with those types of closures?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('locks', 'velcro') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_126", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "At times, carrying bags can be uncomfortable for me; would this camera case be suitable for prolonged carrying without causing discomfort?", "long_answer": "Should you suffer from a medical condition or pain that could be exacerbated by bearing weight on one side, a camera case with a shoulder strap might become uncomfortable over long periods. It would be wise to explore alternative carrying solutions that more evenly distribute the weight across your body.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not suitable for users who may have medical conditions or pain that is exacerbated by carrying weight on one side of the body; other carrying options may be better in these cases.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_98", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I've got a ton of stuff to carry and can't be dealing with a case with tons of pockets. And it needs to be 50 bucks or less. So what's the cheapest camera case you have with one pocket or less?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_99", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm eyeing a teal camera case from either Ape Case or Canon. Get me the cheapest one you have in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras` with asin: B001I3X3HU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Canon\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Canon\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Canon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color='teal' AND brand IN ('Ape Case', 'Canon') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_146", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can I easily access my camera with just one hand using this sling bag?", "long_answer": "While the sling's design facilitates swift rotation for accessing the camera, managing it single-handedly might be difficult, as users often need to stabilize the bag with the other hand to unzip it. Thus, one-handed operation isn't always straightforward in every situation.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_147", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the PSC-85 camera case designed to fit inside a larger bag for additional protection?", "long_answer": "The PSC-85 camera case boasts a sleek design that enables it to be conveniently placed within a larger bag, providing an extra layer of protection while still accommodating the camera inside.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_127", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag hold a Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "No, it wouldn't fit. I have a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens and it just fits the case just right. The Canon 70-200 F4 lens is larger and would not fit into this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_128", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this case accommodate a T2i with a grip and an 18-130 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The case fits my Nikon D3500 perfectly and the size of your T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens is similar to my camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_129", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I favor snapping photos rapidly without the fuss of assembling gear; would this camera case suit my needs?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is perfect for photographers such as yourself who prioritize speed and simplicity. Lacking a tripod attachment, it is crafted to be lightweight and handy, catering to those rapid, spur-of-the-moment shots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_100", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I need a cheap camera case, preferably with a velcro or drawstring closure. And I ain't looking to spend more than 10 dollars. Can you find the one for me with the fewest pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND price < 10 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND price < 10 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND price < 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type IN ('velcro', 'drawstring') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_130", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can I fit a Rebel xsi with a 55-250mm long lens in this case?", "long_answer": "Based on the size of the Nikon D3500 which fits perfectly, I believe the Rebel xsi with a 55-250mm long lens would be too big for this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_148", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the upper compartment of this backpack suitable for carrying essentials beyond camera gear for daily use?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with an upper compartment that allows it to function effectively as a daypack, accommodating items that are not camera gear, thereby showcasing its versatility for everyday essentials.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_131", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Would this camera case provide enough protection for my camera when taking photographs in snowy environments?", "long_answer": "In snowy environments, where the case could encounter damp snow or thawing ice, its lack of waterproofing could pose an issue. It provides only minimal protection, and the case could be infiltrated by moisture from the snow, jeopardizing your camera's security. To safeguard your camera in snowy conditions, opting for a case that is specifically designated as waterproof would be more prudent.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_132", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "In street photography, having quick access to my camera is essential. Does this camera case allow for such easy reach?", "long_answer": "A camera case equipped with backpack straps offers comfort and is well-suited for transporting your equipment over long durations, but it might not be the best option for street photography, wherein effortless camera retrieval is essential. Sling bags or other designs that allow for faster and more convenient access are more appropriate for the fluid demands of street photography.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps do not have a function of instant accessibility compared to certain sling bags which can provide faster access to equipment for those who need to switch gear quickly and frequently.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_149", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can the camera case stretch to accommodate a camera slightly larger than the interior dimensions?", "long_answer": "The camera case is not designed with significant stretchability, which means it's essential for your camera's dimensions to be within the case's internal dimensions to guarantee that the camera will properly fit inside the case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_101", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I like to keep things simple, give me a camera case that's either black or teal and has a zipper. Just make sure it's the first one you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)` with asin: B00WUIIH8W", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"teal\") AND closure_type = \"zipper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"teal\") AND closure_type = \"zipper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('black', 'teal') AND closure_type = 'zipper' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_133", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm fond of scuba diving and am interested in capturing underwater photographs. Can this case safeguard my camera during extensive dives?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case is unsuitable for scuba diving since it's crafted from canvas, a material that lacks the necessary waterproof properties. Treatment for water resistance may be applied, but the canvas still won't hold up against the pressure and conditions associated with deep underwater photography that entails full submersion.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with canvas material cannot be used for underwater photography as the material is not inherently waterproof and, even with water-resistant treatments, the protection offered is inadequate for full submersion.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "canvas", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_102", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I gotta have a purple camera case, and I only do Case Logic or OP/TECH USA. Find me one with the fewest pockets.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"OP/TECH USA\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"OP/TECH USA\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' AND (brand = 'Case Logic' OR brand = 'OP/TECH USA') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_134", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "May I bring this case on my desert photography excursion to shield my camera from the heat?", "long_answer": "Since the case is made of nylon, it is not suitable for extremely high-temperature environments. Nylon does not possess the capacity to offer adequate insulation against intense heat, an important factor to bear in mind for settings such as deserts. For your requirements, a case designed with thermal protection may be more appropriate.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_135", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is it necessary to purchase extra accessories for carrying my tripod, or does this camera case come with an integrated feature for that purpose?", "long_answer": "No need for extra accessories, as the camera case comes with integrated external straps for your tripod. This design offers a secure and convenient method to transport your tripod together with your camera, ensuring a smooth travel experience free from the burden of additional carrying gear.", "short_answer": "unnecessary, yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with external straps for tripod attachment are known for increasing the convenience and portability of carrying tripods, particularly beneficial for photographers on the move who need to set up and dismount their equipment quickly.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "external straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_150", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the DSLR Day Holster case marketed as being able to protect a camera from water damage?", "long_answer": "The DSLR Day Holster case is not advertised with features for water protection and is designed mainly to shield against impacts, such as bumps and scratches, rather than preventing water damage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_136", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is it safe to trust this camera case to protect my equipment in congested areas?", "long_answer": "The camera cases are handy for transport, particularly with their shoulder straps, yet in congested areas where the risk of damage or theft increases, opting for a more secure choice such as a hard case with locks might be prudent.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap lack the capability to offer the same level of security as a locked carry-on or hard case, so they might not be the primary choice for transporting extremely valuable or sensitive equipment.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_137", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "May I rely on this case to maintain my camera's form while in my bag?", "long_answer": "If preserving your camera's form within your bag is essential, bear in mind that the nylon fabric of this camera case possesses inherent pliability and may not sustain a solid shape when compressed, potentially permitting slight alterations to your camera's configuration.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_151", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can the camera be accessed from the bag while wearing the backpack?", "long_answer": "The backpack's sling design facilitates the ability to rotate it to the front of the body for swift access to the camera, negating the need to remove the backpack completely, though it is important to exercise caution to avoid dropping any gear during such access.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_138", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this bag fit a Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "No, it likely wouldn't. The bag fits my Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and that lens is smaller than the 70-200 F4. Therefore, I don't think the 70-200 F4 lens would fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_139", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can I use this with my Canon EOS 5Ds?", "long_answer": "Yes, this product is designed to accommodate a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens. Given the similar size of your Canon EOS 5Ds, it should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS 5Ds has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS 5Ds fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_152", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "What kind of closure mechanism does the pouch have?", "long_answer": "The pouch uses non-marring snaps located at the bottom as its closure mechanism to provide secure storage and easy access for the contents while protecting them, such as a camera.", "short_answer": "non-marring snaps", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_153", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the compartment suitable for a 17-inch laptop?", "long_answer": "The compartment is built to accommodate laptops and tablets that measure up to 16 inches in size. Therefore, a 17-inch laptop is unlikely to fit properly in the compartment, especially if it has larger-than-average width and depth dimensions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_103", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm not into too many pockets and prefer locked closures. Can you find me a camera case that matches these preferences?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets < 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets < 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'locks' AND pockets < 3;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_104", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "No black and it needs to be water resistant. What's my best option for a camera case?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'black' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_154", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can the Flipside 300 backpack be used as a carry-on personal item on most airlines?", "long_answer": "The Flipside 300 backpack is generally compatible with the size restrictions for personal items on most airlines, as reported by user experiences, and can typically be placed under the seat in front of the passenger.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_105", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I can't afford any water damage to my camera and I hate fiddling with locks. Find me a case that's water resistant and quick to open, just make sure it's not too pricey.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND closure_type != 'locks' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_140", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a Nikon D5000?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The bag is designed to accommodate a Nikon D3500, and the Nikon D5000 is similar in size to the D3500, so it should fit without any issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Nikon D5000 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Nikon D5000 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_106", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case in either red or green and I don't need many pockets. What's the option with the fewest pockets you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"green\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"green\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('red', 'green') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_141", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the case design assist in evenly distributing the weight of my camera equipment?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is equipped with D-ring and clip attachments, which not only permit the attachment of the case to external supports but also aid in distributing the weight of your equipment evenly. Such strategic positioning lessens strain and improves ergonomics for the photographer.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with d-ring or clip attachments feature strategic placement at reinforcement points on the case to accommodate accessibility, user balance, and weight distribution, enhancing the overall ergonomics for the photographer.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "d-ring or clip attachments", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_155", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Does Pelican provide larger case options than the 1120 model for increased space needs?", "long_answer": "Pelican has a variety of case sizes in their product lineup, which includes options that are larger than the 1120 model, catering to those who require more space.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_156", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can the backpack's laptop compartment accommodate a Dell XPS 15 laptop?", "long_answer": "The backpack is likely not suitable for carrying laptops that have a bulkier frame, such as some models of the Dell XPS 15, because the compartment designed for laptops may lack the necessary thickness.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_142", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is this case appropriate for daily use, or is it more suitable for those times when I need to pack lightly for special events?", "long_answer": "This case is perfect for daily use and is also suitable for those times when you need to travel light. Its construction material is not only lightweight but also provides a snug-fit protection, making it practical for regular carry and adaptable to your travel requirements.", "short_answer": "both", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with neoprene material are ideally used for situations requiring lightweight and snug-fit protection, making them convenient for photographers to carry without adding significant weight or bulk to their equipment.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "neoprene", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_157", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Does the bag feature a compartment specifically for holding a water bottle?", "long_answer": "The bag includes an exterior pocket tailored for carrying a water bottle, providing convenient access to it or items of similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_158", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "What is the composition material of the OP/TECH Soft Pouch for cameras?", "long_answer": "The OP/TECH Soft Pouch is constructed from neoprene, a material known for its flexible, weather-resistant, and lightweight qualities which offer protective benefits for cameras.", "short_answer": "neoprene", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_107", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm only interested in \"OP/TECH USA\" or \"Canon\" brands. Can you tell me which camera case from these brands has the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Canon\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Canon\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Canon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('OP/TECH USA', 'Canon') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_108", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm really not a fan of green. What's the first camera case you have that's not in that color?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'green' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_159", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the bag offer adjustable compartments for different camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The bag comes with velcro dividers that are designed to be repositioned or completely removed, allowing you to customize the interior layout to accommodate the dimensions of your specific camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_160", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this bag suitable for carrying both a laptop and camera equipment simultaneously?", "long_answer": "This bag is primarily designed for camera gear and may not accommodate a laptop due to its dimensions. While a small tablet might fit, the space is not tailored for a laptop, implying that the bag is not well-suited for carrying both items at the same time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_161", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the backpack designed to accommodate the comfort of individuals up to 6'5\" in height?", "long_answer": "The backpack caters to a variety of body types through its adjustable sternum strap, and customer feedback indicates that it is comfortable for individuals as tall as 6'5\".", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_109", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm not looking to break the bank, and I don't care about water resistance. Give me the camera case with minimal pockets that's priced less than or equal to the average price of the bunch.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND pockets = (SELECT pockets FROM camera_cases ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1) AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_110", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm tired of the same old black. What's the cheapest non-black camera case you have in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'black' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_111", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm in need of a Canon or OP/TECH USA camera case but drawstring closure isn't my thing. Can you hook me up with one that has the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Canon', 'OP/TECH USA') AND closure_type != 'drawstring' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_162", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does the bag have a designated compartment for small items like camera manuals or note pads?", "long_answer": "According to reviews, the bag includes an inside pouch located on the lid, which serves as a convenient compartment for storing small items such as camera manuals or note pads.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_143", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Will this case protect my camera during an outdoor shoot if I get caught in a downpour?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case features waterproof properties to safeguard your equipment against moisture. However, be aware that in the absence of extra cushioning or impact-resistant materials, it may not provide complete protection for your camera against significant impacts or unintended drops that can happen when you're outside.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof characteristics lack the capability to protect against substantial impacts or drops unless they also incorporate specific padding or shock-resistant materials.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_144", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this case designed to discreetly transport my tripod so that it doesn't appear to be a camera bag?", "long_answer": "Regrettably, cases that include a designated area for tripod storage frequently fail to provide such a discreet appearance. The noticeable bulge or outline required to fit a tripod can unintentionally reveal the presence of camera gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket lack the capability to remain sleek and inconspicuous, as the protrusion or shape of the pocket may reveal the storage of valuable equipment, potentially drawing unwanted attention.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_163", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is this bag suitable for carrying professional photography equipment?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to accommodate the needs of both professional and amateur photographers, providing ample space and organized compartments for various types of photography gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_112", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm looking for a yellow camera case, but I don't need it to be water-resistant. Can you fetch the product ID for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'yellow' AND water_resistance = 'no';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_164", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Are the interior dividers of this equipment case customizable to accommodate various gear layouts?", "long_answer": "The equipment case features interior dividers that are fully customizable, permitting users to reconfigure the layout to suit the particular needs of their gear, thus offering flexibility for different equipment arrangements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_145", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case work for my Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR? ", "long_answer": "Yes, I have a Nikon D90 and it fits perfectly. And the D750 with the AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR is of a similar size, so it should fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "search_qa_113", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I don't need any extra pockets and I'm only interested in OP/TECH USA or Canon brands. Give me the first camera case that meets these requirements.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Canon\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Canon\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND (brand = 'OP/TECH USA' OR brand = 'Canon') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_114", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm only interested in either Lowepro or AmazonBasics cases. Give me the cheapest one of those you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"AmazonBasics\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"AmazonBasics\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Lowepro', 'AmazonBasics') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_115", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I can't deal with buckle or clasp closures, just pisses me off. Tell me the first camera case you have that comes with a zipper or lock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'locks') ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_116", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I don't give a hoot about having extra pockets or water resistance. Just show me your cheapest camera case without those frills.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_146", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this case suitable for a wedding photographer to use?", "long_answer": "Given that a professional appearance is frequently expected at weddings, a camera case with backpack straps might not conform to the formal dress code, since it could be perceived as overly casual for such occasions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are not recommended for situations that demand rapid gear changes or a professional appearance that aligns with formal event dress codes, as a backpack might be viewed as too casual or cumbersome in such environments.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_117", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I’m not really looking for anything fancy or waterproof, and I definitely don't want a drawstring closure. Just give me your cheapest camera case that meets these criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'drawstring' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_147", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 55-250 usm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, the case should fit your Canon 55-250 usm lens. I have a Nikon D3500 and it fits perfectly and their sizes are quite similar.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 55-250 usm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 55-250 usm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_165", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the backpack designed with ergonomic sling strap and padded waistbelt comfortable for all-day use?", "long_answer": "Based on customer feedback, the backpack's ergonomic sling strap and padded waistbelt are designed to offer comfort for wearing throughout the day. Nevertheless, comfort is subjective and can depend on factors such as the weight of the contents in the backpack and individual body types or preferences.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_118", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I’ve got a Canon that can't afford to get wet. Dig up the first Canon camera case you have that's water resistant.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Canon' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_119", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm not a fan of those Velcro closures, way too noisy, but I do like AmazonBasics. Which is the cheapest one they got without Velcro?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND brand = \"AmazonBasics\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND brand = \"AmazonBasics\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'AmazonBasics' AND closure_type != 'velcro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_166", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "What material is the Canon PSC-85 case made from?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 case is crafted from a durable fabric material that has been noted by customers for its ease of cleaning.", "short_answer": "fabric", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_167", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera sling bag designed with enough padding to safeguard the camera and its accessories?", "long_answer": "The sling bag comes equipped with a suspended hammock system and a memory foam lining, which together offer ample cushioning and protection for both the camera and its accompanying equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_148", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case fit my Nikon D7100?", "long_answer": "Yes, your Nikon D7100 should fit in this case since its dimensions are similar to the Nikon D90 which is known to fit this case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Nikon D7100 has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Nikon D7100 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_149", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this backpack carry a Canon 1100D?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should work. I personally use it with a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens, which is around the same size as the Canon 1100D, and it fits perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon 1100D has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon 1100D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_168", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does this bag include dedicated straps for attaching a tripod?", "long_answer": "The bag comes equipped with special straps designed specifically to attach a tripod, ensuring easy transportation of your tripod along with the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_120", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I need a camera case under 50 dollars with either a drawstring or lock closure. Instead of all that fancy stuff, the less pockets the better. So, what's the simplest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND price < 50 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND price < 50 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND price < 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 50 AND (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'locks') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_169", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is there a dedicated compartment for personal items in this backpack?", "long_answer": "This backpack contains a removable accessory pouch specifically designed for organizing personal items and small accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_170", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can the interior layout of the bag be adjusted to fit various equipment?", "long_answer": "The bag comes with thick padded dividers that provide the ability to adjust the interior layout, ensuring different pieces of equipment can be securely accommodated according to individual needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_150", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Will this case contribute significant bulk to my photography equipment when I'm aiming to pack lightly for a hike?", "long_answer": "No, the camera case will not significantly increase bulk, as it is made from lightweight nylon material, making it perfect for scenarios where reducing your load is essential, such as hiking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_151", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will this backpack fit my Canon Rebel T3? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit perfectly. The Nikon D3500 fits in this backpack, and the Canon Rebel T3 is a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_171", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the bag's color and material considered unisex and suitable for all genders to carry?", "long_answer": "The bag comes in a neutral color and is designed with a casual style, making it suitable for all genders. It is constructed with durable fabric, and customer feedback confirms its appropriateness for anyone regardless of gender.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_152", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can this bag fit a Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not. The bag is a perfect fit for my Canon 10-22mm lens and I believe that the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens is larger in size, so it may not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_153", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "In a studio environment, can I seamlessly transition between using this camera case and other equipment?", "long_answer": "Although the camera case is crafted for convenient transport with backpack straps, its inability to remain upright independently means that it lacks the quick accessibility of a freestanding, easily opened hard case in a fixed studio environment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps lack the capability to stay upright on their own when set down due to their design focused on back wear-ability, unlike hard cases which can be free-standing.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_154", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon Rebel SL1?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon L-series 100-400 and it fits perfectly.  Your Canon Rebel SL1 has similar dimensions to my camera, so it should work well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon Rebel SL1 has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon Rebel SL1 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_172", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the bag's strap system capable of securing a tripod effectively?", "long_answer": "The bag comes equipped with a strap system on the front that is specifically designed to hold a tripod in place using industrial-strength hook-and-loop fasteners. However, the effectiveness of the securing mechanism may vary based on the dimensions of the tripod, with some users possibly experiencing a tight fit for larger tripods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_155", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this camera case accommodate frequent photo-taking while ensuring comfort during hikes, where both are crucial?", "long_answer": "A camera case featuring backpack straps is optimal for comfort when engaging in activities such as hiking, but it may not offer the ease you require for regular photography, owing to its limited immediate access compared to other options like sling bags, which allow for faster retrieval of your camera.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps do not have a function of instant accessibility compared to certain sling bags which can provide faster access to equipment for those who need to switch gear quickly and frequently.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_121", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I ain't interested in OP/TECH USA camera cases with locks. They're too complicated. Find me the cheapest one from the same brand but without locks.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' AND closure_type != 'locks' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_173", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the interior of the case utilize a bright color to aid in seeing the contents inside?", "long_answer": "The case features a lining with bright yellow material, which serves to increase the visibility of the items stored inside, aiding the user in quickly identifying the case contents.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_156", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon t5i with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case should fit your Canon t5i with a 300mm lens. I have a Canon 70D with a 70-250 lens and it fits well, and the sizes of our cameras are quite similar.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_174", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does this backpack have a dedicated compartment for carrying laptops?", "long_answer": "The backpack's product description lacks any mention of a dedicated laptop compartment, which suggests that if you require one, you should consider alternative backpack models designed with such a space.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_175", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can the Canon 200DG bag accommodate multiple camera bodies, lenses, and essential accessories for professional photographers?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG bag is considered suitable for professional photographers as it offers sufficient space to carry several camera bodies, various lenses, and other necessary photography equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_122", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Look, I can't stretch my budget past 50 dollars and I hate extra pockets. Find me a camera case like that, and make sure it’s the cheapest one.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 50 AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 50 AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_176", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the interior of the bag designed to protect an LCD screen from damage?", "long_answer": "The interior of the bag includes memory foam that provides protection specifically designed for the delicate nature of an LCD screen, cushioning it against potential impacts.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_157", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can this case fit a Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense?", "long_answer": "No, I don't think it will fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens which fits well, and it appears that the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens is larger than my camera setup.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_158", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is this camera case going to be easy to carry while I'm moving through different terrains during my photo sessions?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is designed for comfortable carrying, thanks to its backpack straps that enable easy and ergonomic transportation. It is particularly apt for photographers who frequently navigate various terrains as part of their regular photography sessions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are ideally used for applications that involve movement across varying terrain or travel, lending themselves to be particularly useful for adventure and travel photographers.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_123", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Look, I've got only 30 dollars and I hate zippers. So can you find me a non-zipper camera case with fewest pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND closure_type != 'zipper' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_159", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is it possible for me to bring this camera case on my kayaking journey to safeguard my gear against the water?", "long_answer": "Since this camera case is not waterproof, it cannot offer a watertight seal necessary to safeguard your camera in a moist setting. Hence, it is recommended to seek out a case with waterproof capabilities prior to embarking on a kayaking adventure.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_124", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case in mica or black color that won't break the bank. Point me to the cheapest one you have in these colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"black\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"black\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('mica', 'black') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_125", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case in mica or orange with a velcro closure. What's the cheapest thing you got that matches what I need?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"orange\") AND closure_type = \"velcro\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"orange\") AND closure_type = \"velcro\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"orange\") AND closure_type = \"velcro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('mica', 'orange') AND closure_type = 'velcro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_126", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm trying to find a mica camera case that's not too bulky. Help me pick out the one with two or fewer pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag` with asin: B009GYIKHQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND color = \"mica\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND color = \"mica\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'mica' AND pockets <= 2;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_160", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Might toting this camera case for extended periods lead to discomfort in my hip?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is crafted with ergonomic advantages, integrating a function that ensures an even distribution of weight while worn on the hip. This reduces stress and enhances comfort for prolonged usage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop feature unique ergonomic benefits, contributing to an even weight distribution that minimizes strain when carried on the hip for extended periods.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_177", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can the Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack be cleaned easily?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack, crafted from water-resistant nylon, facilitates easy cleaning due to its water-resistant properties, allowing for straightforward maintenance with the use of a damp cloth.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_127", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I don't want anything from Pelican. Show me the camera case with the least number of pockets from other brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Pelican\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Pelican\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Pelican\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Pelican' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_128", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I don't have time for a bunch of pockets and zippers. I just need a simple camera case with a drawstring or lock closure, no more than 2 pockets. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND pockets <= 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND pockets <= 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('drawstring', 'locks') AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_161", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "No, this case is designed for a Nikon D3500 - I've found that it won't fit larger models. Your Rebel xsi with a 55-250mm long lens would be too large for this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_129", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm strapped for cash and keen on simplicity. Dig up the least expensive camera case you have that's under 10 dollars and doesn't have more than one pocket.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_130", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I can't go over 50 dollars, and I don't need any of that fancy water resistance stuff. Just give me the cheapest camera case you've got that meets those conditions.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 50 AND water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 50 AND water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_162", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can I use this case with my Canon EOS Rebel T3i and my long lens?", "long_answer": "I don't believe your Rebel T3i with long lens will fit. I have a Canon L-series 100-400 and it fills the bag up completely. Your camera and lens combination is larger than mine, so I doubt it will fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "search_qa_131", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I've got a thing for mica colored cases with either locks or drawstring closure. And I'm not into many pockets, so show me the one that has the fewest pockets.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'mica' AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_132", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I've got a thing for teal camera cases but don't need it to be water resistant. Can you find me one like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'teal' AND water_resistance = 'no';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_133", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I don't need a bunch of pockets and I'm not willing to spend over a hundred. What's the simplest, most affordable camera case you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND price <= 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND price <= 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND price <= 100 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_134", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm interested in buying a case by Lowepro or AmazonBasics, but it's gotta have a velcro closure. Can you find me one?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND closure_type = \"velcro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND closure_type = \"velcro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Lowepro', 'AmazonBasics') AND closure_type = 'velcro';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_178", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can the waistbelt of the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack be detached?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 comes with a waistbelt that is designed to be detachable, offering users the option to remove it for enhanced comfort based on personal preference.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_135", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I don't have time to deal with a bunch of pockets or a drawstring. Find me the least expensive camera case you got with less than two pockets and no drawstring.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'drawstring' AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_136", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I've got a tight budget and can't spend more than 10 bucks on a camera case. Which one's the cheapest option you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_137", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm obsessed with purple and I hate bulk, so find me the purple camera case that has the least amount of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_163", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I intend to photograph in the Arctic; can this case protect my camera from the extreme cold?", "long_answer": "When photographing in the Arctic, it is essential to use a case that offers superior thermal insulation. This camera case, constructed from nylon, does not offer specialized protection against extreme temperatures. A case made with materials specifically designed to shield against the intense cold encountered in such environments would be more beneficial.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_179", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "How secure is the belt loop on this case when used with various belts?", "long_answer": "The case is designed with a belt loop intended for easy carrying, and many users report it as secure. Nonetheless, there are a few instances where individuals have found it to be too loose, suggesting that the loop's security may vary depending on the belt's width and thickness.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_164", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can I fit a Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens in this backpack?", "long_answer": "I doubt that would fit. I have a Canon 70D with 70-250 lens and it just fits. Your Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens seems to be larger than my setup.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_165", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is this camera case designed to protect my equipment in extremely cold conditions?", "long_answer": "Although the camera case is constructed from robust material, it's crucial to point out that its nylon makeup doesn't provide the best insulation against severe cold. In extreme temperatures, a case crafted with specialized insulating materials would be more appropriate for safeguarding your camera gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_166", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should work. I have a Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses that fits in the case perfectly, and they're similar in size to the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_180", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this bag suitable for carrying a laptop?", "long_answer": "This bag is not intended for laptop carriage as its design primarily supports camera equipment and personal items rather than electronic devices such as laptops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_181", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the case for Canon Powershot cameras an authentic Canon product?", "long_answer": "The case in question is an authentic Canon product specifically designed to accommodate select models within the Powershot series.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_167", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 55-250 usm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it with my Nikon D3500 which is similar in size to your Canon 55-250 usm lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 55-250 usm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 55-250 usm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_182", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the Soft Pouch add significant bulk to the camera when carrying it?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch is designed to be streamlined and lightweight, ensuring that it protects the camera without adding significant bulk, making it less cumbersome than an oversized bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_138", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I only have 50 dollars to spare and I specifically want a camera case with a velcro closure. What's the best option you can pull up?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND closure_type = \"velcro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND closure_type = \"velcro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND closure_type = 'velcro' ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_139", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I can't stand those drawstring closures on camera cases. What's the product ID of the case with the fewest pockets, just not a drawstring closure, got it?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'drawstring' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_140", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Between Pelican and Ape Case, which one's got a zipper closure camera case with the least amount of pockets? I really cannot stand too many pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)` with asin: B000WH86BQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Ape Case\") AND closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Ape Case\") AND closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Ape Case\") AND closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Pelican', 'Ape Case') AND closure_type='zipper' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_168", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Would this bag fit a Canon Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits fine. The Canon Rebel T3 and the Canon 70D have similar dimensions so it should work.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_169", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "As I frequently engage in street photography and require effortless mobility, would this camera case be appropriate for such activity?", "long_answer": "Absolutely, the design of this camera case caters to dynamic shooting contexts like street photography, ensuring mobility and swift access to your camera, as it lacks a tripod attachment that might otherwise impede your movements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_183", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the case compatible with the Canon SX700 HS camera?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback indicates that the case is designed well to accommodate the Canon SX700 HS camera, ensuring a good fit for the device.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_184", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is the Pelican 1200 Case large enough to accommodate a GoPro and its accessories?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case has been reported by multiple users to be customizable, allowing them to modify the foam interior to snugly accommodate both their GoPro camera and its various accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_170", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "As a hobbyist photographer, I wonder whether this case might restrict me in any way during outdoor photography sessions?", "long_answer": "Although the case might be suitable for a hobbyist's general use, the lack of a tripod attachment could be restrictive for outdoor photography sessions where the use of a tripod is essential. This limitation becomes particularly apparent as your interest in photography expands to situations where camera stability is imperative for achieving the intended shot.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_171", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can a Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens fit in this backpack?", "long_answer": "Based on the size, I doubt it. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens and it fits perfectly. I believe the Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens is larger than the Canon 10-22mm lens.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_141", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm not looking to go broke here. Find me a lower-than-average priced camera case with the least number of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) \nORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_185", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this backpack suitable for travel, particularly for carrying camera equipment securely?", "long_answer": "Customers often regard this backpack as ideal for travel due to its capacity to offer hands-free convenience while ensuring camera equipment remains close and secure.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_172", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for my professional photography shoots where I utilize a range of accessories?", "long_answer": "Incorporating equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods into your professional shoots means that this camera case might not be suitable, due to its absence of a tripod attachment feature—a key element for mounting accessories that guarantee ideal lighting and image steadiness.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_173", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can the case be compacted for more convenient storage when it's not in use?", "long_answer": "Indeed, thanks to the pliable nature of the canvas material, this camera case can be compacted more conveniently for storage compared to a hard case that retains its shape irrespective of what it holds.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with canvas material do not have a function of providing rigid structural support like hard cases, instead offering more flexibility which conforms somewhat to the internal contents, possibly providing less protection against strong impacts.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "canvas", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_174", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this case enable me to swiftly switch my camera from being carried to mounted on a tripod when I am out hiking and photographing landscapes?", "long_answer": "Lacking a tripod attachment feature on this camera case prevents the possibility of rapidly converting to a mounted camera configuration. If quick swapping is critical to your outdoor photography experiences, consider searching for a case that comes with a built-in tripod mounting mechanism.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_186", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is this camera sling designed to allow the attachment of a tripod?", "long_answer": "The camera sling comes with a front strap system designed for attaching tripods or other bulky gear, primarily through the use of industrial-strength hook-and-loop fasteners. However, the recommendation from users is to utilize this feature with lighter tripods or monopods instead of heavier gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_187", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is there a belt loop on the Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for carrying purposes?", "long_answer": "The Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case is designed with a belt loop, facilitating easy carrying for the user.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_175", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the camera case designed to withstand long-term travel and potential heavy use?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the addition of backpack straps to the camera case is designed for comfortable carrying of heavier loads, with the straps facilitating an ergonomic distribution of weight that makes the case appropriate for prolonged journeys.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps typically mean that the user can anticipate a high degree of ergonomics and comfort due to the even distribution of weight across the shoulders, reducing fatigue and strain during extended use.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_188", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can the camera bag's padded interior be adjusted to fit various camera sizes and additional lenses?", "long_answer": "The bag features a fully padded and removable camera box that allows for reconfiguration to support different camera sizes. It is primarily designed to fit a standard DSLR with an additional lens or flash. However, for very large lenses or professional gear, further adjustments or specific inserts might be necessary to ensure a proper fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_189", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can the shoulder straps on this item be adjusted to accommodate various body sizes?", "long_answer": "The shoulder straps are indeed designed to be adjustable, providing the ability to customize the fit comfortably for a range of different body sizes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_176", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can I use this with my Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens and it fits perfectly. Your Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 is similar in size so it should also fit well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_177", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Could the camera case become burdensome if I carry it throughout my extensive travels?", "long_answer": "No, the camera case won't be overly heavy since it's crafted from nylon, renowned for its lightweight design. This is especially advantageous for photographers who frequently travel and must transport their gear for extended durations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_142", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I don't like zippers, always getting stuck. Get me your cheapest camera case that either locks or has velcro.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('locks', 'velcro') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_190", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the camera case offer full waterproof protection?", "long_answer": "The camera case is designed to be water-resistant, meaning it can protect against light splashes and rain. However, the case is not suitable for underwater use or exposure to heavy wet conditions due to the non-waterproof zipper, thus it should not be considered fully waterproof.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_191", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this bag adequately sized for professional photographers who carry extensive gear?", "long_answer": "The bag is geared more towards hobbyists or photographers with a smaller amount of equipment. It is not designed to accommodate the needs of professional photographers who possess a large collection of gear, suggesting that they may need a more spacious bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_192", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the Caselogic SLRC-202 bag have waterproof features?", "long_answer": "The Caselogic SLRC-202 includes a water-resistant EVA base, allowing the bag to resist water and safeguard photography equipment from moisture, particularly when set down on wet surfaces.", "short_answer": "water-resistant EVA base", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_193", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is the Pelican 1120 Case large enough to fit a full-sized DSLR camera with a lens attached?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1120 Case has internal dimensions of 7.25 x 4.75 x 3.06 inches, which are likely insufficient for housing a full-sized DSLR camera with a lens attached. Before selecting this case, it would be advisable to measure the equipment or opt for a larger case to ensure proper fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_194", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the AmazonBasics Sling Backpack come with interior color options besides orange?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Sling Backpack is currently only available with a bright orange interior, which serves the purpose of making dark-colored gear easier to find, and no other color choices for the interior lining are provided.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_195", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG camera bag large enough to house a camera with an attached battery grip?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag is designed to carry not just one but up to two SLR camera bodies, along with multiple lenses, which means it possesses ample space to accommodate a camera with an attached battery grip as well as other additional photographic equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_143", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I'm only interested in \"Case Logic\" or \"Canon\" cases. And it has to have either a velcro or lock closure. So what's the best match you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Canon\") AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"locks\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Canon\") AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"locks\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'Canon') \nAND closure_type IN ('velcro', 'locks') \nORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_144", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I don't need any extra pockets in my camera case. Just show me the simplest one you got with either a drawstring or a zipper, will ya?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'zipper');"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_178", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this bag accommodate my Canon EOS 5Ds? ", "long_answer": "Yes, this bag should fit your Canon EOS 5Ds. I use it for my Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the size is quite similar.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS 5Ds has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS 5Ds fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_179", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will this camera case securely keep my tripod in place while I operate in bustling city settings?", "long_answer": "Although the camera case features a tripod attachment with a hook-and-loop fastener, it might lack the theft-resistant security necessary for professional photographers in high-risk urban settings, where safeguarding equipment is paramount.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with tripod attachment using hook and loop fastener fail to meet the requirements for professional photographers who might require a more robust, theft-resistant attachment option when working in high-risk areas or where gear security is paramount.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "hook and loop fastener", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_180", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is it advisable for me as a professional photographer to consider this camera case for my fieldwork?", "long_answer": "As a professional frequently working in diverse shooting environments, where precise camera positioning is paramount, this camera case may not suit your needs due to the absence of a tripod attachment—a feature often suggested for professionals to achieve the best outcomes in specialized photographic scenarios.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_196", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is camera gear at risk of sliding out of the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack when it is open?", "long_answer": "There is a potential risk of camera gear sliding out of the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack when it is open, especially if the bag is tilted. Users may need to take extra precautions or implement additional protective measures to secure the gear inside.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_197", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the Soft Pouch design allow for quick access to my camera?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch is specifically designed to enable easy access and fast retrieval of your camera, ensuring that photographers can quickly get their camera out when they need to take a shot without delay.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_198", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the sling backpack's strap suitable for individuals with larger body frames?", "long_answer": "The strap of the sling backpack is adjustable and has been found to fit comfortably on some larger-framed individuals, although fit can differ significantly between individuals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_199", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the sling strap design of this backpack effective in keeping it in place while in motion?", "long_answer": "According to user feedback, the backpack's sling strap design ensures that the bag remains securely in position when the wearer is moving.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_181", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I frequently engage in street photography and must keep my camera poised for immediate use. Would this case accommodate such a requirement?", "long_answer": "Certainly. Since you're involved in street photography where quickness is crucial, this camera case featuring a hand grip would be an ideal selection. It is designed for brief photography sessions that necessitate rapid and easy access to your camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip are ideally used for short-duration photography sessions or scenarios where the camera needs to be frequently accessed and then quickly stowed away again.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_200", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Does the bag provide full waterproof protection or is it only water-resistant?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to protect its contents against light rain, effectively keeping items like cameras dry, but it is not suitable for heavy rain or when submerged in water.", "short_answer": "water-resistant", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_145", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm on the lookout for a Pelican branded camera case that won't cost me more than a tenner. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Pelican' AND price <= 10;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_182", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I'm really passionate about macro photography; does this case provide any assistance for that type of precise work?", "long_answer": "Macro photography typically necessitates a stable camera for capturing intricate details without blur. However, this camera case lacks the functionality of a tripod attachment, which is crucial for achieving such stability.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_183", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Should my camera case inadvertently fall into a puddle, would the camera inside remain unscathed by moisture?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case's water-resistant properties are attributed to its construction from PVC or silicone, guaranteeing that should it be dropped in a puddle, your camera would be protected from water damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof capabilities typically mean they are constructed from materials such as PVC or silicone that inherently resist water penetration, thereby safeguarding the camera equipment in wet conditions.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_184", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can this case accommodate a small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. My Nikon D3500 fits in this case, and it is similar in size to a small prime lens like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_185", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Will this case accommodate a Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses and they fit perfectly. The dimensions of your lens is similar to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_186", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is this case suitable for protecting my camera during high-movement activities like biking or running?", "long_answer": "For activities involving significant movement, a camera case with a shoulder strap may not be advisable because it doesn't provide enough protection from the encountered forces. The camera could still experience movement and potential damage under these circumstances, making a more stable solution more suitable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap cannot be used for circumstances where a rigid case is necessary due to extreme conditions or when full immobility of the equipment is required, as the mobility afforded by straps may not provide sufficient protection in these scenarios.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_201", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack provide a convenient way to reach my gear without having to remove it completely?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with body-side access which allows for convenient retrieval of your equipment by swinging the backpack to the front of your body. However, there might be an initial adjustment period to become accustomed to this method of accessing your gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_202", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack permit rapid retrieval of equipment from the main compartment in field scenarios?", "long_answer": "The backpack's design includes secure storage for equipment, but the main compartment flap does not remain open autonomously, which can complicate quick access to the contents.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_203", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this backpack suitable for carrying all the equipment required by a professional photographer during a shoot?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed to hold substantial gear including a DSLR body, several lenses, various accessories, and a laptop, which should meet the needs of most professional photographers and serious enthusiasts. However, if the equipment is highly extensive, the capacity of the bag might be insufficient.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_204", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the zipper design considered durable and secure by users for ensuring gear safety?", "long_answer": "The zipper is strategically placed against the back, which users find to be a secure choice for gear safety. Despite this, some users have experienced issues with the zipper wearing out over time, suggesting that while generally reliable, the durability can vary.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_146", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I've had enough of Sony. What's the cheapest non-Sony camera case you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Sony\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Sony\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Sony\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Sony' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_205", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 camera bag designed for swift access to the camera?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 camera bag has a design that includes multiple zippers and clips, which may not be convenient for customers who require rapid access to their camera. To achieve quicker access, users might consider leaving some compartments partially unzipped while using the bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_206", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the interior layout of the camera case adjustable to accommodate various camera sizes and accessories?", "long_answer": "Yes, the camera case features interiors with adjustable partitions that use velcro panels, enabling you to customize the compartment sizes to securely fit your specific camera and accessory dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_187", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this camera case safeguard my equipment during inclement weather?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case provides superb protection in wet conditions, thanks to its construction from neoprene fabric which ensures superior water resistance. It's vital for photographers who frequently work in settings where exposure to moisture due to rain, accidental spills, or splashes could pose a threat.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with neoprene material typically mean that the case offers enhanced water resistance, providing essential protection from moisture in environments prone to rain, spills, and splashes, which is particularly beneficial for outdoor photographers.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "neoprene", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_207", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is this bag considered comfortable and practical for both travel and hiking activities?", "long_answer": "The backpack has received positive feedback from users who have affirmed its comfort and practicality, making it suitable for both travel and outdoor photography hikes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_188", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Can I swiftly switch my camera from being carried to mounted on a tripod for landscape photography with this case while hiking?", "long_answer": "Lacking a tripod attachment on this camera case, swiftly shifting to a mounted camera configuration would be impractical. If rapid transitions are critical for you during your outdoor shoots, consider seeking a case that comes with a built-in tripod mounting feature.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_208", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can the Canon 200DG Camera Gadget Bag accommodate two SLR camera bodies and multiple lenses?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG Camera Gadget Bag is specifically designed to carry two SLR camera bodies, along with three lenses and additional photography accessories, which customers find sufficient for their equipment storage needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_147", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm not a fan of zippers. Can you find me a camera case with either a velcro or drawstring closure? And make sure it's the cheapest one you've got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('velcro', 'drawstring') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_209", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the bag suitable for carrying non-electronic items, such as snacks, without compromising the safety of camera gear?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with multiple pockets and compartments that allow for the safe storage of non-electronic items including snacks, ensuring that they do not interfere with the camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_210", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the slimline camera case designed to protect the camera from severe impacts or drops?", "long_answer": "The slimline camera case is built to guard against minor bumps and scratches, but its basic cushioning is not designed to withstand major impacts or severe drops. It is not recommended for situations where the camera could suffer substantial damage due to a significant fall.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_148", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I don't need a lot of fancy pockets on my camera case. Just find me the cheapest one that has two or fewer pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 \nORDER BY price \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_211", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "How secure is the tripod mount on the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is equipped with a Hideaway Tripod Mount system that is specifically designed to ensure that a tripod attached to the backpack remains secure.", "short_answer": "especially stable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_189", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for me when I aim to reduce movement and sound while photographing in tranquil settings?", "long_answer": "In environments where quiet is essential, and minimal movement and noise are paramount, opt for a camera case that can be hand-carried or fastened snugly to your body, avoiding loose straps that could swing and generate noise, in contrast to a shoulder strap style that may not be as silent.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not recommended for situations where stealth is necessary, as the motion of a dangling strap might draw unwanted attention or noise, unlike a case that is carried by a handle or secured closer to the body.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_212", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the bag have designated storage for small items such as memory cards and batteries?", "long_answer": "The bag features dedicated zippered compartments both on the front and the rear, specifically designed for organizing and storing small accessories like memory cards, batteries, and cords.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_149", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm only interested in Canon or Case Logic cases with zippers or velcro. Give me the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Case Logic\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Case Logic\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Case Logic\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Canon', 'Case Logic') AND closure_type IN ('zipper', 'velcro') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_213", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can individuals over 6 feet tall and weighing more than 200 pounds comfortably use this bag?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed in a manner that accommodates individuals who are over 6 feet tall and weigh more than 200 pounds, suggesting that it can be suitable for larger body types. However, it is important to note that the fit may vary depending on the specific dimensions and shape of an individual's body.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_190", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I frequently experience wrist discomfort when transporting heavy bags. Could this camera case assist in reducing that pain?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case features an ergonomically designed hand grip tailored to offer a more comfortable carrying experience, aiming to reduce wrist pain often associated with bearing heavy loads over prolonged periods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with an ergonomic hand grip typically mean that users will experience increased comfort and reduced hand fatigue, especially during prolonged carrying sessions, due to the grip's design shaped to fit the natural contours of the hand.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_150", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm not a fan of zippers and don't need any extra pockets. What's the cheapest camera case you have that fits this description?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'zipper' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_151", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm all about the easy access, find me the first camera case you have that uses velcro, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'velcro' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_214", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the camera bag designed to remain upright independently without toppling over?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is equipped with a water-proof EVA base that provides it with the ability to stand upright on its own. However, it should be noted that user feedback indicates that there is a possibility of the bag tipping over if not positioned on an even surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_215", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG camera bag known to maintain its durability after prolonged use?", "long_answer": "User feedback indicates that the Canon 200DG camera bag is perceived as highly durable. Numerous users have reported that the bag continues to retain its quality and withstand regular usage over a considerable period of time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_216", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the bag designed to remain upright when placed on a flat surface?", "long_answer": "Due to the bag's flexible design prioritizing comfort and maneuverability, it typically lacks the structured support necessary to remain upright when placed down.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_217", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the bag capable of standing upright on its own when filled with items?", "long_answer": "Users have indicated that the bag has the capability to stand on its own when items are strategically packed inside, facilitating ease of access to the gear without additional support.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_218", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "What level of protection does the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG provide for camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG provides a high level of protection for camera equipment due to its full padding and reinforcement, which protects against moisture, dust, and general handling wear and tear.", "short_answer": "high level", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_219", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will the case provide a snug fit for a smaller camera model like the Fuji XT1?", "long_answer": "The case is specifically designed with the capability to stretch, which allows it to accommodate and provide a snug fit for most camera sizes, including smaller models such as the Fuji XT1.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_220", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is it possible to purchase replacement foam for the Pelican 1200 Case?", "long_answer": "Replacement foam for the Pelican 1200 Case is available for purchase, allowing for a renewed custom fit for the items you wish to protect inside the case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_221", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can this bag be adjusted to accommodate a micro four-thirds camera system?", "long_answer": "The backpack comes with adjustable dividers that enable the users to configure the interior compartments according to their specific equipment needs, which means it can be customized to snugly fit a micro four-thirds camera system.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_191", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can I store my Canon 70-200 F4 lens in this bag?", "long_answer": "I don't think it would fit. I have a Canon 70D with a 18-200mm lens and it fits just right. Your lens is larger than mine, so I'm afraid it won't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_192", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Would this case be able to fit my Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not, I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits perfectly. Given that your lens is longer, it most likely won't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_193", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I occasionally feel discomfort when transporting bags; is this camera case designed to be comfortable for prolonged carrying?", "long_answer": "Should you suffer from a medical condition or experience pain exacerbated by bearing weight on one side, a camera case equipped with a shoulder strap might become uncomfortable over extended periods. It is advisable to explore alternative carrying solutions that more equally disperse the weight throughout your body.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not suitable for users who may have medical conditions or pain that is exacerbated by carrying weight on one side of the body; other carrying options may be better in these cases.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_194", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this case fit my Nikon D7100? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Nikon D90 and it fits perfectly.  The dimensions of the D7100 are very similar to D90, so it should fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Nikon D7100 has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Nikon D7100 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_195", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is there cause for concern regarding moisture infiltration into the case when shooting in misty or humid environments?", "long_answer": "No need for concern, as the waterproof design featuring sealed zippers or roll-top closures provides substantial protection against moisture, ensuring your camera stays secure in misty or damp environments.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a waterproof design are known for incorporating sealed zippers or roll-top closures that prevent water intrusion, ensuring that the camera remains dry in challenging weather or aquatic environments.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_222", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Does the Pelican 1120 Case comply with TSA regulations for traveling with a firearm when properly locked?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1120 Case adheres to TSA guidelines for firearm transportation when it is properly secured with locks, fulfilling the TSA's stipulations for a locked hard-sided firearm case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_223", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is this backpack designed to protect camera equipment from impacts?", "long_answer": "The backpack has a padded interior which serves to protect camera gear and accessories against impacts. Moreover, the rugged exterior enhances the protection against external elements, ensuring a greater degree of safety for the contents.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_196", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can I use this backpack with my A-99 with a vertical grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, you can. Your A-99 with a vertical grip is similar in size to a Nikon D3500 which fits perfectly in this backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the A-99 with vertical grip has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the A-99 with vertical grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_224", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the backpack durable enough to withstand frequent use?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback suggests that the backpack maintains its good condition even after being used extensively, indicating its durability and suitability for frequent use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_197", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Will this camera case facilitate the transportation of a tripod for outdoor photography sessions?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case features a specialized tripod pocket, enabling photographers who often alternate between handheld and tripod-supported shots to swiftly retrieve their tripod. This proves especially advantageous for numerous photography styles that demand steadiness and accuracy.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket typically mean that the product is designed with the needs of photographers in mind who require quick and easy access to their tripods for capturing stable and precise shots across various photography genres.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_225", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can the main compartment layout of the backpack be personalized?", "long_answer": "The backpack's main compartment features internal dividers that are attached with Velcro, which can be rearranged or removed to customize the interior space based on the specific gear you need to carry.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_198", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "As a professional photographer, ought I to consider this camera case for use during my field assignments?", "long_answer": "As a professional who often operates in diverse shooting settings and requires exact camera placement, this specific camera case may not be ideal for you since it doesn't have a tripod attachment. A feature like this is widely suggested for professionals to secure the best outcomes in specialized photographic conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_226", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the camera case designed to accommodate additional lenses besides the camera?", "long_answer": "The camera case is designed with a compact size that primarily accommodates the camera itself and may fit small accessories such as a spare battery or an SD card, but it is not intended for holding additional lenses.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_152", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I've had enough of Canon's stuff. Show me the cheapest camera case you have from any other brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Canon' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_153", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm looking for a fun camera case, either purple or orange. But it's got to have a lock or velcro closure. What have you got that matches my taste?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND color IN (\"purple\", \"orange\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND color IN (\"purple\", \"orange\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (color = 'purple' OR color = 'orange') AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'velcro');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_227", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the backpack suitable for day trips in terms of size and bulkiness?", "long_answer": "The backpack is primarily designed to carry extensive equipment, which makes it quite large; hence, it might be considered too bulky for day trips where less gear is needed. Customers often choose smaller bags for such local outings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_199", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this camera bag appropriate for photo shoots that last all day, during which I'll mostly be standing?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is ideal for day-long shoots; its nylon fabrication makes it lightweight, minimizing the burden on your shoulders and back throughout prolonged use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_200", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm somewhat accident-prone and concerned about the case tearing. Is this particular one robust enough to mitigate that possibility?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the nylon fabric used for this camera case is highly prized for its tear resistance. Such durability renders it an outstanding option for those worried about damage due to inadvertent mishaps.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_228", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the camera bag have a designated compartment for storing a lens cap?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is equipped with an internal slip pocket intended explicitly to store a lens cap, guaranteeing that it is both secured and easily accessible.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_229", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the Canon SLR Gadget Bag designed for everyday use for photographers requiring to carry significant equipment?", "long_answer": "The Canon SLR Gadget Bag is on the larger side but is indeed suitable for daily use, especially for individuals who need to transport a substantial amount of photography equipment regularly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_230", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the AmazonBasics Sling Backpack large enough to accommodate an iPad or a device of similar size?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Sling Backpack is designed with additional space for personal belongings, and it has been reported by certain users to be capable of fitting an iPad Air, indicating that devices of similar dimensions can be stored without the need for modifying the bag's compartments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_201", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit just fine. This case is able to accommodate a Nikon D3500, which is similar in size to the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_231", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is this backpack secure and suitable for use in urban and crowded environments?", "long_answer": "The backpack comes highly recommended for use in urban settings, as its design includes a security feature where the zipper is placed against the wearer's back, offering enhanced security in crowded spaces.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_202", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this Lowepro Fastpack 200 fit my Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have used it with a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens and it fits well. Your Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens should be of similar size so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_154", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I've had enough of Lowepro's waterproof stuff. Give me their first non-water-resistant camera case.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Lowepro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Lowepro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Lowepro' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_155", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I want a camera case but I'm only into green or black ones. Show me the cheapest one you have in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"black\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"black\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('green', 'black') \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_203", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I require a case that can withstand the demands of fieldwork and accommodate all my photography gear. Is this the suitable option?", "long_answer": "The camera case might fall short for rigorous fieldwork that requires a range of gear, given its absence of an essential tripod attachment feature. This function is crucial for the safe transport and swift setup of standard professional photo equipment such as tripods and additional lighting.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_232", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 backpack suitable for use as an airline carry-on?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack can indeed be used as a carry-on for flights, and many customers have done so. It is recommended, however, to verify the backpack's dimensions against the size restrictions for carry-on items of the specific airline in question, particularly as a fully packed backpack might exceed some airlines' limitations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_233", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is there additional space for personal items in the backpack aside from the main camera compartment?", "long_answer": "The backpack offers supplementary space for personal items beyond the main compartment intended for camera equipment; however, the extent of space available is contingent on the dimensions of the camera gear stored.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_204", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this case offer sufficient protection for my equipment when I'm shooting in snowy environments?", "long_answer": "Although the case is built for use in dry surroundings, the presence of snow can bring in moisture that might jeopardize your equipment. This camera case isn't dedicated to waterproofing, an important factor if there's a chance your camera will encounter melting snow. In snowy settings, opting for a waterproof or weather-resistant case would be a smarter option to ensure total confidence in the protection of your gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_234", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Does the bag come with built-in locks for the zippers to enhance security?", "long_answer": "The bag lacks built-in locks for the zippers, a feature designed to enhance the security of the contents. Instead, customers have recommended using improvised methods such as key rings or adding separate locks to secure the zippers.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_205", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can this case fit my Canon EOS 7D?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Nikon D3500 and it fits perfectly. Your Canon EOS 7D has a similar size so it should fit too.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS 7D has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS 7D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_156", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm sick of all these boring black and white cases. Give me the cheapest camera case that won't get ruined in the rain, and make sure it's either orange or yellow.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND color IN (\"orange\", \"yellow\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND color IN (\"orange\", \"yellow\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND color IN (\"orange\", \"yellow\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' \nAND color IN ('orange', 'yellow') \nAND price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND color IN ('orange', 'yellow') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_235", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Does the laptop compartment provide adequate protection and fit for laptops up to 15.6 inches in size?", "long_answer": "The laptop compartment is specifically designed to ensure protection, featuring protective padding, and is capable of accommodating laptops up to 15.6 inches, thereby securing the device effectively.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_236", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Are there any common problems associated with the backpack's zippers?", "long_answer": "A few customers have indicated that the backpack's zippers can be stiff initially, but there is no indication of widespread or persistent zipper quality issues as the bag is used over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_157", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm not up for all that pocket bulk and I'm not looking to burn more than a hundred dollars. What's the cheapest camera case you got with less than two pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND price <= 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND price <= 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_237", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG camera bag suitable for carrying a mirrorless camera along with its accessories?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag is designed with adjustable dividers in the main compartment that allow it to securely accommodate a mirrorless camera and its related accessories, ensuring that different types of camera equipment can be organized and carried with ease.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_158", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I can't stand Pelican stuff and I fancy some colour in my life, maybe red or yellow. Find me the cheapest camera case that isn't made by Pelican and comes in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"yellow\") AND NOT brand = \"Pelican\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"yellow\") AND NOT brand = \"Pelican\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"yellow\") AND NOT brand = \"Pelican\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Pelican' AND (color = 'red' OR color = 'yellow') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_206", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 70-200 F4 lens? ", "long_answer": "I am afraid not. I have the Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens and it fits perfectly, but based on this your lens is larger, and thus it will not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_207", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can the camera case be conveniently stored without occupying too much space when it's not in use?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is crafted from a material that enables it to be collapsible when not in use, thereby facilitating convenient storage without taking up significant space.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_238", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does this backpack provide comfort during prolonged usage due to its design features?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with a removable waistbelt and an adjustable sternum strap, which are designed to distribute the weight evenly across the body. Users report that these features contribute to a comfortable experience when wearing the backpack for extended periods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_208", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 fit in this Lowepro Fastpack 200?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will fit. I have a Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, which has a similar size to your Canon EOS Rebel SL1, and it fits perfectly in this bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_159", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "No locks for me, too much hassle. What's the cheapest camera case you have under 30 dollars that doesn't include a lock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND closure_type != 'locks' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_239", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the design of the bag prevent the camera from falling out when the main compartment is opened?", "long_answer": "The bag's design focuses on security, although it requires the user's attention when opening the main compartment to ensure the camera does not accidentally fall out.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_160", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I don't want a yellow camera case and I don't need a bunch of pockets. Just one will do, anything more is overkill. What's the cheapest case you got that fits those requirements?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT color = \"yellow\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT color = \"yellow\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT color = \"yellow\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'yellow' AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_209", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can this case hold my Nikon D3200 with a Polaroid grip and a Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will provide an exact fit. I use this case for a Nikon D5200 with two lenses that are similar in size to yours.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_240", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG bag suitable for both storing and transporting camera equipment securely?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG bag is considered by customers to be a good option for both storing and transporting camera gear, providing security for the equipment inside.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_241", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the backpack's quick access side opening facilitate the rapid retrieval of equipment?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with a quick access side opening that our customers appreciate because it enables them to quickly and effortlessly access their camera and gear. The convenience of not having to remove the backpack entirely to get to the equipment is a feature that is generally well-received.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_242", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the Canon Rebel Digital SLR Camera Case capable of fitting a DSLR camera, several lenses, and additional photography accessories?", "long_answer": "The Canon Rebel Digital SLR Camera Case is specifically designed to accommodate a DSLR camera along with an attached zoom lens, and it provides space for up to four extra lenses, a flash, and various other photography accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_210", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for me if my aim is to reduce movement and noise when photographing in tranquil settings?", "long_answer": "In environments where minimizing movement and noise is essential, such as quiet settings, opting for a camera case with a handle or a design that secures snugly to your body—free from dangling straps—proves more suitable than a case featuring a shoulder strap that could swing and generate noise.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not recommended for situations where stealth is necessary, as the motion of a dangling strap might draw unwanted attention or noise, unlike a case that is carried by a handle or secured closer to the body.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_211", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a Canon T31 with a 250mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The size of Canon T31 with 250mm lens is similar to Nikon D3500, which is compatible with this backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon T31 with 250mm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon T31 with 250mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_243", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Have customers reported fitting issues with the camera case in relation to the recommended camera models?", "long_answer": "There have been reports from some customers about the camera case being smaller than anticipated, leading to issues with fitting even among the recommended camera models. It is advised to cross-check the camera's dimensions against the internal dimensions of the case prior to making a purchase to ensure compatibility.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_212", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I frequently photograph in various settings and must transport my equipment swiftly. Will this case facilitate a smoother transition between locations?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the inclusion of a dedicated tripod pocket in this camera case improves your capability to quickly relocate and position your equipment across different settings. The convenience provided by this attribute is priceless for mobile photography, where time is crucial.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket are known for their convenience in allowing for quick attachment and detachment of tripods, which is particularly beneficial in dynamic shooting situations where setting up the shot swiftly is crucial.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_213", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can I use this with my Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, this case may not be suitable for your camera. I have used it for my Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens, and it fit well. However, your Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens is larger, so it may not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_214", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is it possible to use this case for securing my camera during my whitewater rafting expedition?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the case is designed to prevent water ingress that could harm your camera during water-based activities such as rafting. Yet, for optimal protection, it's important to verify that the case includes adequate padding. This is because water resistance does not, by itself, provide complete protection against the potentially high impacts experienced in adventurous situations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof characteristics lack the capability to protect against substantial impacts or drops unless they also incorporate specific padding or shock-resistant materials.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_215", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can this camera case safeguard my equipment should I encounter rain during a hike?", "long_answer": "Given that the camera case isn't waterproof, exposing it to rain might result in water seeping in and potentially damaging your camera. It's intended to provide basic protection against moisture; therefore, if you plan to hike in adverse weather conditions, you may want to look into a waterproof option.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_161", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm heading for a shoot in the rainforest, so need a camera case with water resistance. But keep it under $100. What's my best option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price < 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price < 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND price < 100 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_162", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I need a camera case for my Sony or Canon, but I'm not looking to shell out more than 10 bucks. You find for me, mate?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Canon\") AND price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Canon\") AND price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'Canon') AND price <= 10;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_244", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will this camera bag fit an SLR camera body with an attached battery grip?", "long_answer": "The main compartment is designed to fit most SLR camera bodies with a standard lens, but larger bodies or those with attached battery grips might have a tight fit. It is advisable to compare the bag's dimensions with those of the camera and battery grip to ensure they will fit together.", "short_answer": "Check dimensions", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_245", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "How durable are the metal clips on the bag?", "long_answer": "The metal clips on the bag are regarded as high-quality, which enhances the bag's sturdiness and implies a level of durability suitable for regular use.", "short_answer": "highly durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_246", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can personal items be stored in the Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack along with photography equipment?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack features multiple pockets and compartments specifically designed to accommodate a variety of personal items in addition to photography gear, allowing for its use in diverse contexts that go beyond professional photography.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_247", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the backpack have specific compartments for storing keys and small items?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with several small pockets explicitly designed to securely hold items such as keys, wallets, and various small accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_248", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the velcro closure produce a noise level that is acceptable for discreet photography sessions?", "long_answer": "The velcro closure is designed to hold components securely, but it does create some noise when opened or adjusted. Therefore, it may not be ideal for scenarios where silence is paramount, such as during discrete photo shoots where a photographer needs to avoid drawing attention.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_249", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the case have a feature that allows it to be securely attached to a belt?", "long_answer": "The case is designed with a wide belt loop on the back, specifically made for secure attachment to a belt.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_216", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm seeking a camera case with a premium tactile experience. Would you suggest this particular one?", "long_answer": "If you're in pursuit of a 'premium touch', the tactile sensation of this camera case might fall short of your expectations, as it is crafted from nylon. While nylon is resilient and utilitarian, it lacks the sumptuous texture associated with high-end materials like leather.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_163", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Hey there, can you find the Pelican case with the fewest pockets for me? I like simple gear.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Pelican' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_250", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is there space in the backpack's top compartment to store additional personal items?", "long_answer": "The backpack features a top compartment specifically designed to accommodate extra personal items, making it convenient for carrying things like food, a jacket, or extra shirts during day trips.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_251", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the bag have a dedicated feature to secure a tripod?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with tripod loops on the bottom, which are specifically designed to secure a small tripod.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_217", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is it possible for this camera case to seamlessly integrate into an urban setting while avoiding undue attention?", "long_answer": "Given that this case comes with backpack straps, it might stand out rather than blend in urban contexts due to its bulkier and more noticeable design compared to smaller, more subtle carry options that tend to go undetected in these settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps fail to meet the requirements for a low-profile carry option in crowd-intensive settings due to their bulkier design when compared to more streamlined cases or bags.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_164", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm pretty stuck on wanting the case in black or purple. What's the most affordable option you got in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"purple\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"purple\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"purple\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('black', 'purple') \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_252", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can the camera section of the ACPRO2000 backpack be removed for alternative uses?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 backpack features a removable camera section which enables users to repurpose the backpack for other needs aside from carrying camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_253", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can the Soft Pouch - Digital D-Series accommodate a camera with an attached lens?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch - Digital D-Series has been thoughtfully designed to accommodate most film and digital cameras with their lenses attached. Moreover, the pouch provides additional space in the lens area, allowing for certain camera models to fit even with the lens hood inverted.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_254", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the Fastpack 200's mesh side pocket comfortably carry a standard water bottle?", "long_answer": "The mesh side pocket on the Fastpack 200 is designed to accommodate a water bottle, although it might be a snug fit for bottles that are on the larger side.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_218", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can I use this case with my Canon EOS Rebel T1i?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will fit your camera. I am using it for my Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens. As your camera has similar dimensions, it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T1i has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T1i fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_255", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the camera bag feature compartments for organizing accessories?", "long_answer": "The camera bag comes with multiple pockets and adjustable dividers, providing excellent organization options for your camera accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_256", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack have any features that enhance the security of the contents inside?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with body-side access, which provides enhanced security. The zipper that grants entry to the main compartment is positioned against the wearer's back, serving as an additional security measure to protect the gear inside while the backpack is being worn.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_257", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the SLRC-202 camera bag water-resistant and able to protect a camera when placed on a wet surface?", "long_answer": "The SLRC-202 camera bag is built with a semi-rigid, molded EVA base that is water-resistant. This design allows the bag to protect the contents, such as a camera and its accessories, from water damage when set on moist or wet surfaces.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_219", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Will this backpack fit a Canon t5i with a 300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes. It perfectly fits with Canon 10-22mm lens which is similar in size to your Canon t5i with a 300mm lens. So, it should be able to fit yours just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_258", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Are there provisions for adding locks to the Pelican 1200 Case to secure its contents during transport?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case comes with two small openings specifically designed to accommodate locks, which ensures you can secure the case's contents while transporting it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_165", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I can't stand camera cases with too many pockets and I only buy from Pelican or OP/TECH USA. Find me a case from these brands without any pockets.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"OP/TECH USA\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"OP/TECH USA\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Pelican', 'OP/TECH USA') AND pockets = 0;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_220", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will this backpack fit a Canon 5DII?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The bag fits my Nikon D3500, and I expect the Canon 5DII to be about the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5DII has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5DII fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_221", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can this case accommodate a 6D with a 24-105mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. This case is suitable for Nikon D90 and your 6D with a 24-105mm lens has similar dimensions so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the 6D w/24-105mm lens has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the 6D w/24-105mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "search_qa_166", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I only want a Canon camera case with either a velcro or drawstring closure. Give me your pick.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND brand = \"Canon\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND brand = \"Canon\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Canon' AND (closure_type = 'velcro' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_259", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is this case suitable for secure and TSA-compliant transportation of firearms during travel?", "long_answer": "This case comes highly recommended for the transportation of firearms owing to its secure design. When locked according to the requirements, it also meets TSA guidelines, making it an appropriate choice for travel purposes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_167", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm not really a fan of Lowepro and honestly, I don't need all the extra pockets. Find me the most affordable camera case from another brand with one pocket or less.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" AND pockets <= 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" AND pockets <= 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Lowepro' AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_260", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the case designed to stand upright independently when placed on a surface?", "long_answer": "The case is equipped with a semi-rigid, molded EVA base that provides stability and allows it to stand upright on its own when placed on a surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_168", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I don't wanna spend more than 30 bucks and I'm looking for something vibrant. Find me a yellow or teal camera case, and keep it cheap!", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"yellow\", \"teal\") AND price <= 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"yellow\", \"teal\") AND price <= 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND (color = 'yellow' OR color = 'teal') ORDER BY price ASC;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_222", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Will this case fit a Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not. I have a Canon 70D with 70-250 lens and it fits just right. Given that the Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens is larger, it will not fit in this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_261", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack have a dedicated compartment for carrying a tripod?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack includes a specialized feature known as the Hideaway Tripod Mount, which is specifically designed to secure a tripod to the backpack for convenient transport.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_223", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can the Canon 70-200 F4 lens fit in this bag?", "long_answer": "No, it can't. I have a Nikon D3500 and it fits just right. I think the Canon 70-200 F4 lens is larger than my device.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_224", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I worry about the durability of my camera case, as I am quite rough with my equipment. Would this be a wise investment?", "long_answer": "Considering your concerns, investing in this camera case would be prudent. The nylon fabric utilized for this case is celebrated for its durability and abrasion resistance, suggesting that it is capable of withstanding rough handling and is likely to provide extended protection for your equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_169", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I need a cheap camera case for less than 30 dollars and I only trust AmazonBasics or Ape Case. Plus, I hate too many pockets, show me the one with the least pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Ape Case\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Ape Case\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Ape Case\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND (brand = 'AmazonBasics' OR brand = 'Ape Case') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_262", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the backpack durable and reliable for long-term use?", "long_answer": "Customer reviews regarding the backpack’s long-term use reveal a mixed consensus. A considerable number of users have found the backpack satisfactory and durable over extended periods. However, there are reports from other users encountering durability problems, prominently with the zipper and the overall construction after prolonged usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_263", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is the OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 compatible with a Nikon D200 DSLR camera?", "long_answer": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 is designed to suit a variety of DSLR cameras and according to customer feedback, it fits the Nikon D200 DSLR camera well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_264", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the zipper on this bag have issues with durability or ease of opening?", "long_answer": "The zipper is typically of good quality and durability, although a few users have reported it may sometimes catch at the top because of the protective flap. Additionally, it does not unzip all the way to the bottom, potentially making it harder to reach items at the bottom of the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_265", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the backpack comfortable for long-term wear?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with padded shoulders and back to ensure comfort during prolonged use, and customer feedback indicates that it is suitable for extended wear, such as during long hikes or walks with gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_266", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the bag completely waterproof?", "long_answer": "The bag is constructed from durable, water-repellent nylon, which provides protection against light moisture; however, it is not entirely waterproof and may not withstand heavy or sustained exposure to water.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_267", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "What is the durability of the Case Logic SLRC-202 camera bag based on its construction materials?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLRC-202 camera bag is constructed from heavy-gauge (840D) nylon and other high-quality materials, which ensures its durability and capability to withstand long-term use.", "short_answer": "durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_268", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does this Case Logic product come with a manufacturer's warranty?", "long_answer": "Case Logic generally provides warranties for their products, but the exact warranty terms for this specific model can vary and should be verified with the manufacturer or the seller.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_170", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm after a simplistic camera case with either a zipper or drawstring, but it can't have any pockets. What's your cheapest option?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'drawstring') AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_269", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack capable of accommodating a professional DSLR with a 300mm lens attached?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack is primarily designed to house a professional DSLR with a lens up to 80-200mm f/2.8. Nevertheless, customer experiences suggest that it can also fit a camera body with a 300mm lens affixed, although this is beyond the advertised specification.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_270", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "What material is used to make the clips and rings on the bag?", "long_answer": "The clips and rings on the bag are crafted from metal, which contributes to the bag's enhanced durability and elevated quality perception.", "short_answer": "metal", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_271", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this bag suitable for carrying a DSLR camera with an attached 18-55mm lens?", "long_answer": "The bag is specifically designed to accommodate a DSLR camera that has an 18-55mm lens attached to it, ensuring that users can safely store and transport their camera with this particular lens. While the bag can fit the camera and the mentioned lens, fitting additional lenses could be challenging, depending on their dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_171", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I have a hundred dollars to spend on a camera case, but it's gotta be water resistant. Point me to the most affordable one you got that fits these criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_272", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Fastpack 200 backpack have dedicated attachment loops for a tripod?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 does not come with dedicated attachment loops for securing a tripod, necessitating alternative carrying solutions or the selection of a different backpack model that provides this specific feature.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_225", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Does this case reduce strain when carrying heavy camera equipment?", "long_answer": "A camera case with a hand grip is not suitable for minimizing strain when carrying heavy camera equipment. The grip centralizes the load in a single spot, potentially causing greater fatigue. Opt for a case that provides multiple carrying methods to evenly distribute the weight, like a shoulder strap or waist belt.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip cannot be used for evenly distributing the weight across the photographer's body which is essential when carrying heavy gear over long periods, as the grip focuses the entire weight on one hand or wrist.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_273", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the suspension hammock system effectively protect the camera from impact and screen damage?", "long_answer": "The suspension hammock system in the camera case is well-regarded by users for its ability to protect the camera from impacts. The system suspends the camera body above the case's bottom and utilizes memory foam in the compartment lid to help shield the screen from damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_226", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is it possible to transport the camera case without engaging my hands or employing a shoulder strap?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is designed with a feature that allows for secure attachment to your waist, offering a convenient hands-free carrying alternative that eliminates the necessity for a shoulder strap.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop feature unique ergonomic benefits, contributing to an even weight distribution that minimizes strain when carried on the hip for extended periods.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_172", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I can't stand the color green and I don't need more than 2 pockets. Get me the cheapest camera case you have that fits my needs.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND pockets <= 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND pockets <= 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'green' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_274", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the backpack heavy to carry?", "long_answer": "The backpack is engineered to be light, with a weight of only 1.5 pounds (0.68 kg), thus it should not cause significant strain or weight concerns for the user.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_173", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I fancy a camera case from USA Gear in either green or red. Don't show me any pricey stuff, just the cheapest you got in these colors.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"red\") AND brand = \"USA Gear\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"red\") AND brand = \"USA Gear\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"red\") AND brand = \"USA Gear\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'red') AND price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'red') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_227", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate two nikon d3200 cameras with normal lenses? ", "long_answer": "Yes, I have a Canon L-series 100-400 and it fits very well. The size of your two nikon d3200 with normal lenses should also fit without a problem.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the two nikon d3200 with normal lenses has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the two nikon d3200 with normal lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "search_qa_174", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm not looking to shell out more than a hundred. Find me a camera case under that price with the fewest pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_175", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I like to keep things organized, so pockets are a must for me. Whats the Altura Photo camera case with the least number of pockets you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND pockets > 0 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_228", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this camera case adequate for safeguarding my gear amidst strenuous outdoor adventures?", "long_answer": "When engaging in vigorous outdoor activities, you might opt for a camera case offering a solid structure for enhanced protection. Cases crafted from nylon tend to have a certain degree of flexibility, potentially lacking the structural rigidity desired for these conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_176", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I hate green and I don't need any pockets. So, what's the cheapest camera case you have that meets my requirements?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'green' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_229", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is it safe to rely on this case to maintain the shape of my camera while it's stored in my bag?", "long_answer": "If preserving your camera's form within your bag is important to you, be aware that the nylon fabric of this camera case is inherently flexible and may not hold a stiff shape under pressure, potentially permitting slight changes to the camera's configuration.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_177", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I've got nothing against USA Gear, but teal's just not my color. Pull up a USA Gear camera case that's anything but teal.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR` with asin: B005J09OXU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"teal\" AND brand = \"USA Gear\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"teal\" AND brand = \"USA Gear\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND color != 'teal';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_275", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is a dedicated rain cover included with the backpack for use during heavy precipitation?", "long_answer": "The backpack itself is weather resistant; however, it does not include a dedicated rain cover as per the customer reviews.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_276", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is there a protective padded compartment for an LCD screen in this camera bag?", "long_answer": "The camera bag includes a dense, scratch-resistant memory foam lining on the interior lid of the camera compartment, specifically designed to cushion and safeguard the camera's LCD screen.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_230", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Will this camera case possess a luxurious aesthetic that distinguishes it?", "long_answer": "Considering that this camera case is crafted from nylon, it might not exude the same sense of luxurious aesthetics as its counterparts made from more upscale materials such as leather. Nylon usually presents a casual and practical look, which may fall short of the expectations of those in search of a distinctive, opulent aesthetic.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_277", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can the shoulder strap on the camera bag be detached and adjusted?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is equipped with a padded shoulder strap that is designed to be both removable and adjustable, allowing for user customization in terms of comfort and fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_178", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case with a drawstring closing mechanism but I've had enough of AmazonBasics. Show me something else, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring' AND brand != 'AmazonBasics';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_179", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case that's both drawstring style and water resistant. Got any suggestions?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring' AND water_resistance = 'yes';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_180", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I don't want any yellow stuff. Do you have any water-resistant camera cases that aren't yellow? Show me the first one you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND color != 'yellow' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_278", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack come with compartments specifically for organizing small accessories?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with a removable accessory pouch that serves the purpose of neatly organizing small items and accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_279", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is the Soft Pouch - Digital D-Series manufactured in the United States?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch - Digital D-Series is indeed manufactured in the United States, confirming that production occurs within the country.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_231", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does this case offer sufficient security to safeguard my valuable photography equipment against possible theft?", "long_answer": "Camera cases outfitted with a shoulder strap offer protection and practicality for daily use; yet, they do not offer the same security against theft as a locked carry-on or a hard case could, making the latter options preferable for those prioritizing anti-theft measures.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap lack the capability to offer the same level of security as a locked carry-on or hard case, so they might not be the primary choice for transporting extremely valuable or sensitive equipment.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_181", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm tired of black and drawstring camera cases. Get me a suitably different and cheap alternative, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color <> 'black' AND closure_type <> 'drawstring' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_182", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm not a fan of anything from Lowepro. What's the cheapest camera case you have from a different brand?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases WHERE brand <> 'Lowepro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "search_qa_183", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm only interested in Lowepro and Case Logic cases, but I can't stand green ones. Give me your cheapest non-green case from these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"Case Logic\") AND NOT color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"Case Logic\") AND NOT color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"Case Logic\") AND NOT color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Lowepro', 'Case Logic') AND color != 'green' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_184", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm looking for a red camera case. Hook me up with the first one you got in that color.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color='red' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_280", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the bag's exterior likely to experience significant fading with normal use?", "long_answer": "The exterior of the bag is crafted from robust nylon, a material that is celebrated for its durability and color retention capabilities. Under normal usage conditions, the bag is not expected to undergo any noteworthy color fading.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_185", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Look, I'm only interested in \"Case Logic\" brand and velcro or drawstring closure type. Find me the least expensive one you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Case Logic' AND (closure_type = 'velcro' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_232", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is it possible for me to carry this camera case hands-free during a rock-climbing excursion?", "long_answer": "The camera case's belt loop design facilitates hands-free transport, yet it isn't designed for rigorous environments like rock climbing. For these demanding situations, a camera case equipped with a more durable carrying option, like a comprehensive harness system, would be more appropriate.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop fail to meet the requirements for those who need to carry their camera case in a rugged or challenging environment that would benefit from alternative carrying methods.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_233", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can I comfortably hike with this camera case without it becoming obtrusive?", "long_answer": "Undoubtedly, the camera case's backpack straps are perfect for hikers since they enable the secure carriage of camera gear on your back, promoting effortless navigation across diverse landscapes without the case posing a hindrance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are known for facilitating hands-free operation, thus enabling photographers to move more freely and focus on capturing images without the encumbrance of holding onto their case.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_281", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case compatible with a Nikon camera that has a 3\" screen?", "long_answer": "Based on customer feedback, the AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case is explicitly designed to house most medium-sized cameras, ensuring that a Nikon camera with a 3\" screen will fit within its dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_234", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is it feasible for me to comfortably transport my camera along with all its accessories in this camera case throughout the duration of an all-day event?", "long_answer": "During an all-day event that requires you to carry multiple accessories, the restricted carrying capacity of a camera case featuring a belt loop might not provide the necessary comfort or convenience. A case with additional carrying methods could be more suitable for such events.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop are not suitable for individuals who prefer to carry multiple heavy lenses and accessories due to the limited load capacity that a single belt loop may offer.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_282", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does the compactness of this bag make it a good choice for photographers who prefer to travel light?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to be compact and portable, which aligns with the preferences of photographers who seek to carry only essential gear without the bulkiness that hinders mobility.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_186", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I don't want any of those AmazonBasics cases, and I don't need a bunch of pockets. Just show me the simplest case you've got..", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'AmazonBasics' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_235", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can this case endure the pressure if I take it diving in the ocean?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the case can endure a degree of underwater pressure; however, it's crucial to confirm that its IP rating is sufficient for the intended dive depth. If the rating doesn't meet the required standard, the case may fail to withstand the intense pressure at deeper levels, potentially resulting in damage to your camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof protection cannot be used for extended deep-sea diving if they don't have a high enough IP rating or are not designed to withstand high pressure at depth.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_187", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I ain't got more than 10 dollars and prefer a case with either a zipper or drawstring. Got anything like that for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'drawstring');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_283", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the Ape Case designed to fit a mirrorless camera system with multiple lenses?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Ape Case is specifically designed to accommodate mirrorless camera systems, including the camera body and several lenses, which has been confirmed by users who have used it for similar camera setups.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_236", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this case accommodate a Canon EOS Rebel T1i?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case should fit your Canon EOS Rebel T1i just fine. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits perfectly in this case. Your camera is similar in size to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T1i has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T1i fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_284", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Are Pelican cases designed to protect their contents from damage when subjected to heavy impacts?", "long_answer": "Pelican cases feature a robust outer shell accompanied by cushioning foam interiors. This design ensures that the contents of the case are safeguarded against damage even when the case undergoes rough handling or heavy impacts.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_285", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the bag made of durable materials and designed to protect camera equipment effectively?", "long_answer": "The bag is constructed with durability in mind, using robust materials and is fully padded to provide a solid level of protection for camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_286", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the Velcro lid on this product allow for quiet and easy access?", "long_answer": "The use of Velcro on the lid of this product can lead to noise when opening, which may be deemed inconvenient in environments that require silence. There are users who find this characteristic irritating and believe that a zipper alternative could offer a more discreet experience.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_237", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this camera case designed for swift retrieval of my compact travel tripod while on hikes?", "long_answer": "Indeed, provided your collapsible travel tripod conforms to a standard shape and size, it ought to slide into the dedicated tripod pocket of the camera case, ensuring convenient retrieval for your outdoor escapades.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket do not have a function of accommodating very large or unusually shaped tripods that require more space or alternative attachment mechanisms than the pocket provides.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_287", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can the camera bag be accessed quickly when needed?", "long_answer": "The design of the camera bag, including the layout and zipper placements, is geared towards allowing rapid access to your camera and accessories, facilitating quick retrieval in time-sensitive situations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_288", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the bag come with padded compartments suitable for carrying an extra lens?", "long_answer": "The bag features a large additional compartment that allows for the storage of extra items including lenses or flashes. However, the compartment's default padding is minimal. Thus, users are advised to add extra padding to ensure the safety of the second lens during transport.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_188", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I got a thing against mica colored stuff, so pull up the cheapest camera case you have that isn't mica, would ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'mica' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_289", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Does the bag have designated internal compartments for storing personal electronics or items securely?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with two internal pockets featuring hook and loop closures, which offer secure storage spaces for small personal electronics or other items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_189", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm not into carrying a lot, so just a case with a pocket or less is fine. Preferably from OP/TECH USA. Show me the cheapest one you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_290", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the camera case's padding system provide sufficient protection against impacts from drops or rough handling?", "long_answer": "The camera case is designed with a padding system that suspends the camera on a hammock structure within the bag, offering protection against basic impacts such as bumps and shorter falls, which is generally considered to be adequate.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_238", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I favor capturing photos swiftly with minimal equipment setup; would this camera case suit my needs?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is perfect for photographers who prioritize quick access and simplicity. Designed to be lightweight and handy, it omits a tripod attachment to facilitate those fast, spontaneous shots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_239", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the camera case suitable for extended journeys and potentially heavy loads?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the integration of backpack straps onto the camera case suggests that it is designed for comfortable handling of heavier loads, since the straps promote an ergonomic distribution of weight, rendering it appropriate for prolonged journeys.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps typically mean that the user can anticipate a high degree of ergonomics and comfort due to the even distribution of weight across the shoulders, reducing fatigue and strain during extended use.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_190", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I just got a Sony camera and I'm looking for a case, but I ain't looking to spend more than 10 dollars. Can you find me a Sony case that won't break my wallet?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand = \"Sony\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand = \"Sony\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Sony' AND price <= 10;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_291", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is a strap included with the Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case is not manufactured with an included strap; however, it features a built-in belt loop designed to provide convenience in carrying.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_240", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this fit the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, the backpack would work fine. The size of the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens is similar to the Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens. So it should fit comfortably.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_241", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm concerned about my camera getting soaked on my hiking excursions. Will these cases keep my camera dry even in a downpour?", "long_answer": "Indeed, our camera cases are designed to protect your camera from water exposure, ensuring that they are highly effective in keeping your camera dry, even in heavy rain. However, due to the absence of gas exchange, while your equipment will remain dry from external elements, internal condensation may occur inside the case owing to restricted airflow.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof features do not have the function of gas exchange, meaning that while they keep water out, air circulation is generally limited, which could potentially cause issues with condensation.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_292", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG designed to be waterproof?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG is built with durable materials and features a top flap that covers the zipper to offer protection against rain. However, it is not officially classified as waterproof, implying it only provides limited resistance to moisture, not complete protection under all wet conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_191", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm particular about my brand and Ape Case is my go to. Can you find me the model with the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Ape Case' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_192", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm not a fan of water resistance and I prefer fewer pockets. Dig up the cheapest camera case you have that meets these specifics.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY pockets ASC, price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_193", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I don't need a bunch of pockets and I can't spend more than average on a case. Can you find me a camera case that's less coin than the average one and doesn't have a crazy amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_293", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "How durable are the zippers and hooks on the bag?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with large zippers and metal hooks, which enhance the bag's durability and contribute to its extended lifespan.", "short_answer": "very durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_242", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. This case perfectly fits the Canon 10-22mm lens, which I believe is similar in size to your Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8, so it should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_294", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Are the latches on the Pelican case durable and long-lasting?", "long_answer": "The latches on Pelican cases are constructed with durability in mind, ensuring longevity even if they may feel stiff or challenging to open according to some users. This robust design is a testament to the reliability that Pelican aims for in their product features.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_295", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can the Canon 200DG Gadget Bag hold Nikon SLR camera bodies and lenses?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG Gadget Bag is designed to hold SLR camera equipment and has a spacious and adjustable interior, making it capable of accommodating Nikon camera bodies and lenses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_296", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "How well does the Canon PSC-85 fit the Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS camera models?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 is specifically designed to accommodate the Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS camera models, ensuring a secure and snug fit with minimal excess space within the case.", "short_answer": "snugly", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_194", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I've got $100 to spare and I need a black camera case. What's my best option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND color = 'black' ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_243", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for my landscape photography outings where I typically rely on a tripod for stability?", "long_answer": "Given that this camera case lacks a tripod attachment, it is better suited for photographers who value mobility and seldom rely on tripods for techniques like long exposure or time-lapse photography. Should you frequently employ a tripod, consider exploring cases with that particular capability to meet your requirements.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_244", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is it suitable for someone who captures both video and still images, requiring varied setups?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case has been crafted for versatility, including a specialized pocket specifically for your tripod. This critical feature caters to photographers and videographers who alternate between still shots and motion footage, facilitating smooth switches among varying shooting arrangements and ensuring prompt retrieval of the tripod whenever needed.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket typically mean that the product is designed with the needs of photographers in mind who require quick and easy access to their tripods for capturing stable and precise shots across various photography genres.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_245", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the design of the camera case conducive to an efficient workflow for photographers who frequently utilize a tripod?", "long_answer": "It definitely does. The case provides a method for swiftly attaching and detaching your tripod, which is invaluable for photographers who must quickly transition between various locations or shots. This streamlined workflow tool aids in maintaining momentum in active shooting situations where time is of the essence.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a tripod attachment using hook and loop fastener typically mean that photographers can expect an expedited method for securing and releasing their tripods, contributing to a more efficient workflow in the field where speed can be critical.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "hook and loop fastener", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_246", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I need a carrying solution that allows me to swap my camera gear swiftly while at events. Would this be suitable for such a situation?", "long_answer": "In situations like events where timing is crucial and rapid equipment switches are necessary, a camera case with backpack straps may not be the ideal choice. Alternative bag styles, such as sling bags, are specifically designed for quicker retrieval of your gear, enabling more efficient changeovers.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps do not have a function of instant accessibility compared to certain sling bags which can provide faster access to equipment for those who need to switch gear quickly and frequently.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_247", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "If I bring this case on a snorkeling trip, will it keep my camera dry?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the case will protect your camera from water ingress while snorkeling provided you adhere to the advised depth constraints. However, it's crucial to recognize that, despite its waterproof capabilities, the case may not be adequate for prolonged deep-sea diving if it lacks the necessary IP certification or a design built to withstand high pressure.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof protection cannot be used for extended deep-sea diving if they don't have a high enough IP rating or are not designed to withstand high pressure at depth.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_248", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Should I bring my camera to the shore, will its case shield it from the corrosive marine breeze and any incidental splashes?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is crafted to shield against both water splashes and the corrosive effects of salty sea air. Be aware, however, that its waterproof features render the case non-breathable, which means you'll need to address potential internal condensation that may accumulate over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof features do not have the function of gas exchange, meaning that while they keep water out, air circulation is generally limited, which could potentially cause issues with condensation.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_297", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the bag designed to be worn in multiple ways for comfort?", "long_answer": "The bag has a primary design feature focusing on its use as a sling. It comes with adjustable shoulder and waist straps for a secure and comfortable fit. However, its use is not versatile beyond the cross-body sling style it is intended for.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_298", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is the Pelican 1120 Case effective in protecting electronics from temperature fluctuations?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1120 Case is engineered specifically to safeguard electronic devices against a variety of environmental conditions, including temperature changes. However, for extreme temperature variations, it is advised to supplement the case with extra insulation to ensure optimal protection.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_249", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can this bag fit Nikon D5000?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. This bag is compatible with the Nikon D3500, which is similar in size to the D5000.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Nikon D5000 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Nikon D5000 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_250", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can the Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster accommodate my Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. I have a Nikon D5200 with two lenses and they fit well. I believe the size of your Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens is similar to mine so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_251", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this bag fit a T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes! I have a Canon 70D with a 18-200mm lens that fits perfectly in this bag. Your camera should fit in this bag as well since T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens has similar dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_252", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Can I easily remove the camera case in crowded settings, such as concerts or festivals?", "long_answer": "No, if the camera case features a carrying method with a belt loop, it might not be ideal for those environments. Detaching the camera case swiftly from a belt might not be feasible in crowded events, rendering it a less advisable option for professional purposes in such contexts.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop are not recommended for professional use in environments where quick removal of the camera case from the belt is not practical, such as densely packed crowd events where reaching down consistently might not be feasible.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_195", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I don't want any AmazonBasics crap, nor am I interested in that teal color. Find me the cheapest camera case you've got that doesn't come from AmazonBasics and isn't teal-colored.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND NOT color = \"teal\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND NOT color = \"teal\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND NOT color = \"teal\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'AmazonBasics' AND color != 'teal' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_299", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "What color options are available for the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG, according to our latest product details, is exclusively available in its standard color design, with no additional color options offered.", "short_answer": "standard design", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_253", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can I use this bag for a 15 1/2 inches long lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, you can. The bag is designed to fit a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens. If your lens is around the same size, it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the 15 1/2 inches long lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the 15 1/2 inches long lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_196", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I can't stand the color purple. Show me your cheapest camera case under 100 dollars that's in any other color.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND price < 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND price < 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'purple' AND price < 100 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_254", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Will this camera case be comfortable to carry on extended hikes?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is designed to be both lightweight and compact, making it an ideal option for lengthy treks when you wish to avoid carrying extra weight or bulkiness. It aims to provide convenience and practicality without significantly increasing your load, aligning perfectly with the requirements of active and on-the-go photography.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_255", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can the case safeguard my camera if it ends up beneath other hefty equipment?", "long_answer": "If the camera case is made of EVA material, it's worth noting that such cases may not offer the necessary level of crush-proof protection in scenarios where heavy equipment might be stacked on top of it. Thus, a case with a sturdier construct might be a better option for these circumstances.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with material described as EVA are not recommended for situations where heavy equipment or other objects might be stacked on top of the case, as they may not be crush-proof to the same extent as harder cases.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "eva", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_256", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this bag accommodate a Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense?", "long_answer": "I don't think so, this product works well with the Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens. If your long lens is larger than this, then it is unlikely to fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_300", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the sling designed for quick camera access?", "long_answer": "The sling bag is praised by many users for its design, which facilitates a swift swing-around motion allowing for quick and effortless camera access, particularly useful for capturing spontaneous shots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_301", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the design of the camera bag likely to attract the attention of potential thieves due to its appearance?", "long_answer": "The camera bag, although practical and aesthetically pleasing, has a design that is likely recognizable as a camera bag. This could potentially catch the attention of thieves, especially in public areas, thus users should be cautious when transporting the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_257", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Could Canon EOS 5Ds fit into this bag?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens, which is similar in size to the Canon EOS 5Ds. It fits perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS 5Ds has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS 5Ds fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_302", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the case provide compartments for storing additional batteries and memory cards?", "long_answer": "The case features a zippered pocket specifically designed to store memory cards and small accessories such as extra batteries, thus catering to storage needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_258", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon 70-200 F4 lens? ", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, I don't think it will. I have the Canon L-series 100-400 and that just barely fits within the case and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens is larger than it.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_303", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the Hi-Vis yellow interior of the bag improve the visibility of items stored inside it?", "long_answer": "The bag's interior is designed with a high-visibility yellow color, which enhances the ability to see and locate smaller accessories, especially in conditions where lighting is poor.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_304", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the backpack durable and suitable for withstanding harsh outdoor conditions?", "long_answer": "The backpack is made from high-quality nylon material, which enhances its durability and ability to withstand harsh outdoor conditions. It also comes with a rain cover that provides extra protection against adverse weather.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_305", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG capable of accommodating a DSLR camera with attached lens and an extra lens?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG is designed to comfortably fit a DSLR camera with a lens attached as well as one additional lens, in addition to providing space for smaller camera accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_259", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is this camera case capable of resisting light rain during outdoor photography sessions?", "long_answer": "The camera case offers moderate weather resistance due to its canvas material, providing protection for your gear in light rain. Nevertheless, for heavy downpours or severe weather conditions, additional protective steps may be advisable.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with canvas material are ideally used for travel and outdoor photography where a balance between moderate weather resistance, comfort, and aesthetic appeal is desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "canvas", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_306", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the camera bag's shoulder strap provide comfort during extended use?", "long_answer": "The camera bag comes equipped with a removable, padded shoulder strap that can be customized for individual comfort. Customer reviews indicate that the strap typically provides a satisfactory level of comfort, though some users have expressed a preference for a wider strap for enhanced comfort during prolonged usage.", "short_answer": "generally yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_260", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does this camera case serve as a suitable option for those who prioritize convenience above robust protection against the elements?", "long_answer": "Certainly, should convenience and ease of accessibility be prioritized above defense against water and harsh environmental conditions, this camera case stands as an appropriate option. It forgoes waterproof capabilities to offer a more straightforward, accessible approach to handling your camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_261", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can I rapidly access my camera from this case should I need to take a quick shot?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is engineered for enhanced accessibility, owing to the absence of complex sealing mechanisms such as watertight zippers or locks typically seen in waterproof cases. This feature facilitates rapid access to your camera, which is perfect for capturing those unexpected, spur-of-the-moment shots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_197", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I need a camera case that has a lock and won't cost me more than 10 dollars. What do you have?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type = 'locks';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_307", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 backpack suitable for use as a hiking backpack in terms of comfort?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 backpack, although robust and comfortable, is designed for carrying camera gear and may not be as suitable for hiking when compared to backpacks specifically designed for that purpose.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_198", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I am not a big fan of zippers, mate. Can you check for camera cases with either drawstring or lock closures? And oh, I need the one with the least number of pockets. Prioritize that when you go hunt it down.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('drawstring', 'locks') \nORDER BY pockets ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_199", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm only interested in the brands Pelican and Case Logic. Can you pull up a camera case from either of these?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)` with asin: B00WUIIH8W", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Case Logic\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Case Logic\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Pelican', 'Case Logic') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_262", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "May I bring this camera case on a kayaking excursion to safeguard my gear from water damage?", "long_answer": "Because this camera case lacks waterproof capabilities, it cannot offer a watertight seal essential for safeguarding your camera in damp conditions. Hence, it is recommended to seek out a camera case equipped with waterproof properties prior to embarking on a kayaking adventure.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_308", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can the camera case be purchased independently without the camera?", "long_answer": "The camera case can be purchased on its own, without the necessity of buying it as part of a camera bundle. However, there are also options where the case is included with the camera as a bundle package.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_263", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is this case suitable for professional photographers seeking robust support for their equipment?", "long_answer": "Professional photographers typically need robust support for their equipment to avoid damage. Given nylon's inherent flexibility, this camera case might not provide the desired rigidity essential for protecting professional photographic equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_200", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I really don't need a ton of pockets on my camera case. Just give me the cheapest one you got that has less pockets than average.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases WHERE pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "search_qa_201", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Look, I don't want any Canon branded stuff, and I don't need a ton of pockets. Just give me a simple camera case with 2 or fewer pockets. What's my best option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" AND pockets <= 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" AND pockets <= 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Canon' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_309", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the entire bag waterproof?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with a waterproof EVA base that provides the capability to stand upright and offers resistance to elements. However, the remainder of the bag has not been designed to be waterproof.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_264", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Will this camera case boast a luxurious appearance that distinguishes itself?", "long_answer": "Since the camera case is made of nylon, it might not exude the same luxurious aesthetic as other premium materials such as leather. Nylon typically presents a casual, functional look, which may not satisfy those in search of a distinctive, upscale aesthetic.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_310", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can the Lowepro Passport Sling comfortably fit a standard DSLR with a 135mm zoom lens attached?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Passport Sling is designed to house a standard DSLR and an attached zoom lens. While it is capable of fitting the camera and lens, it is important to note that longer lenses may not fit as comfortably within the designated padded compartment. Therefore, a 135mm zoom lens should be within the size limits that the bag can accommodate.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_265", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Should I opt for this case to ensure that my camera and its accessories remain immobile within the bag?", "long_answer": "To ensure the camera remains stationary inside the bag, it may be necessary to choose a case with less flexibility than nylon offers. Nylon's elasticity could permit the camera and its parts to move slightly, contradicting the need for the camera to be completely secure and immobile in its case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_202", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I only trust Pelican and USA Gear brands, and I'm only looking for drawstring closure types. Can you point me to a product like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"USA Gear\") AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"USA Gear\") AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Pelican', 'USA Gear') AND closure_type = 'drawstring';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_266", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case fit my a77 with a vertical grip and heavy zoom?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The case is designed for cameras of similar size like the Nikon D90, and the a77 with a vertical grip and heavy zoom has a similar size to the Nikon D90.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the a77 with vertical grip and heavy zoom has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the a77 with vertical grip and heavy zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_267", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can this backpack hold a Canon t5i with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to hold that. I use it for a Canon 10-22mm lens, and they are very similar in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_203", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm not too fond of AmazonBasics or anything in that mica color. Show me your most affordable camera case that isn't either of those.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'AmazonBasics' AND color != 'mica' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_204", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I've heard good things about Altura Photo. Can you give me the product ID of one of their camera cases?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_205", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I've got this Sony camera but I couldn't care less about water resistance. Give me the product ID of one of those, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Sony\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Sony\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Sony' AND water_resistance = 'no' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_268", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "May I utilize this camera case for intense outdoor pursuits such as rock climbing?", "long_answer": "A camera case featuring a belt loop is not advisable for high-impact pursuits such as rock climbing. A more durable case that offers enhanced protection is necessary for such activities.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop cannot be used for securely storing the camera while engaging in activities with a high likelihood of impact, such as rock climbing or mountain biking, where a tougher case may be necessary.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_311", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can the Canon 200DG camera bag accommodate chargers and cables in addition to the camera?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag is designed with padded side pockets and zippered compartments that customers find spacious enough to hold additional accessories such as chargers and cables, along with the camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_269", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Throughout my travel photography, I often transition between sites; will my case remain sleek and manageable?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case remains compact and easy to manage while on the go. The nylon construction ensures it is both lightweight and form-fitting, providing a perfect solution for travel photographers who need to move frequently.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_206", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I hate fumbling around pockets. I need a water-resistant camera case without any extras. Find me the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_312", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does this case have designated compartments for storing batteries and memory cards?", "long_answer": "This case features zippered compartments located on both the front and the rear specifically designed to store small accessories such as memory cards and batteries, providing organization and easy access.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_313", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can you purchase additional dividers specifically designed for this backpack?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with a flexible divider system tailored for it; however, there are no additional dividers made specifically for this backpack available for purchase through Amazon. Nevertheless, dividers from other manufacturers or aftermarket solutions can be utilized as an alternative.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_270", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this Lowepro bag fit my Canon EOS Rebel T1i? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits perfectly. Your Canon EOS Rebel T1i is similar in size to what I have, so it should fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T1i has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T1i fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_271", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Should I frequently traverse varied terrains for photography, would this case prove beneficial?", "long_answer": "Certainly. When navigating different landscapes for assorted photographic pursuits, it's essential to keep your hands unoccupied and your equipment safe. This camera bag features external straps allowing for the attachment of your tripod, providing convenient and steady access to your tripod when it's time to take those impeccable photographs in demanding settings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with external straps for tripod attachment typically mean that photographers who engage in photography disciplines like landscape, wildlife, sports, and astrophotography have the added functionality to carry their tripods conveniently, enabling stable, long-exposure shots in various environments.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "external straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_272", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the case durable enough to withstand frequent outdoor use?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is crafted from nylon fabric, renowned for its excellent tensile strength. As a result, it offers resistance to tearing and stretching, guaranteeing lasting durability even with heavy outdoor use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_314", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the upper compartment of the Fastpack 200 backpack have enough space for additional items such as snacks or an e-reader aside from camera gear?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack includes an upper compartment designed to provide extra space for personal items, which is spacious enough to hold snacks, an e-reader, or other small items along with the camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_315", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the backpack come with a dedicated holder for securing a tripod or monopod?", "long_answer": "The backpack includes an exterior holder specifically designed for holding a tripod or monopod securely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_207", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I hate fumbling around with buttons and zippers. Find me a camera case with either a drawstring or velcro closure. And keep in mind, less is more, a case with fewer pockets please.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('drawstring', 'velcro') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_316", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Does the Canon PSC-85 case have a bulky design?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 case is designed to be compact, ensuring that it is not bulky and hence convenient for carrying on a belt or inside a bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_273", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will the case's tripod attachment mechanism endure even with regular use?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the hook-and-loop fastening mechanism employed for securing the tripod is both robust and dependable, ensuring it can endure repeated usage while also offering the quick assembly and disassembly crucial for active photographers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with tripod attachment using hook and loop fastener feature a pragmatic design which can cater to rapid setup and breakdown, which is particularly advantageous for photographers who need to capture shots on the spur of the moment.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "hook and loop fastener", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_274", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can the bag accommodate two Nikon D3200 with normal lenses?", "long_answer": "Yes, the bag should be able to fit. I am using it with a Canon L-series 100-400 and it fits perfectly and as your devices are of similar size, so it will fit your camera setup as well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the two nikon d3200 with normal lenses has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the two nikon d3200 with normal lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_317", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Does the Pelican 1200 case feature a pressure equalization valve?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 case is equipped with an Automatic Pressure Equalization Valve, which is designed to balance the internal air pressure while preserving the watertight integrity of the case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_275", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does this case perform well in environments with significant moisture, such as in proximity to waterfalls or along coastal beaches?", "long_answer": "The absence of waterproofing in this camera case renders it incapable of completely blocking moisture or water spray from entering. Environments with high humidity, like around waterfalls or at the beach, present a heightened risk of moisture infiltrating your camera, hence opting for a waterproof case would be more prudent for such settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_318", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the side opening of the bag's main compartment designed for easy lens changing while slung over the shoulder?", "long_answer": "The bag's main compartment features a side opening that is intended for quick access. However, certain users find it difficult to change lenses with the bag slung over the shoulder, suggesting that the design of the opening may not facilitate the process as seamlessly as intended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_319", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can a Nikon D7000 with an added battery grip be accommodated in this camera sling?", "long_answer": "The camera sling is not designed to comfortably accommodate larger DSLR bodies, such as the Nikon D7000 with an additional battery grip, based on customer feedback indicating that such bulky setups might be too big for the camera compartment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_320", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Does the manufacturer claim that this nylon case is water-resistant?", "long_answer": "The case is made of nylon, which inherently provides some level of moisture protection. However, the manufacturer has not advertised or claimed the case to be water-resistant. Users often place it inside water-proof bags to ensure additional protection against water.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_321", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this bag suitable for storing and transporting camera equipment?", "long_answer": "This bag is equipped with substantial padding and various compartments, which makes it an ideal choice for users who wish to use it for safely storing and transporting their camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_208", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm no fan of Velcro, so can you find me a camera case that's either Sony or USA Gear without it?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR` with asin: B005J09OXU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"USA Gear\") AND NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"USA Gear\") AND NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'Sony' OR brand = 'USA Gear') AND closure_type != 'velcro';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_276", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this backpack hold a Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens and it fits. So, your Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens should fit as well since it is a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_209", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm looking for a red camera case but I'm really not a fan of those with zippers. Find me the cheapest one you can that meets my needs.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND closure_type != 'zipper' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_277", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Will this day holster fit my Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I am using this case for my Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and your Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens should have similar dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_278", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag accommodate my Nikon v2 with a 70-300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it for my Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens, and I believe your Nikon v2 with a 70-300mm lens is of a compatible size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Nikon v2 with 70-300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Nikon v2 with 70-300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_210", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm quite keen on a splashproof camera case, but only in purple or orange. Can you pinpoint the most affordable one for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color IN (\"purple\", \"orange\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color IN (\"purple\", \"orange\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color IN (\"purple\", \"orange\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance='yes' AND (color='purple' OR color='orange') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_322", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the Lowepro Flipside 300 have a dedicated compartment for carrying a water bottle?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack has a mesh side pocket designed to accommodate a water bottle as well as other small items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_323", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can the backpack be opened and accessed without being removed?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed such that it cannot be opened from the front while being worn. It requires removal to access the contents. However, the backpack features a body-side opening which allows you to reach your gear without placing the bag down once it is off your back.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_324", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the bag come with straps for carrying a tripod?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with dedicated tripod straps, enabling the attachment and transportation of a tripod without hassle.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_279", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can I swiftly switch my camera from being carried to mounted on a tripod for landscape photography with this case during my hikes?", "long_answer": "Lacking a tripod attachment feature on this camera case, swiftly switching to a tripod-mounted configuration would be unfeasible. Consider seeking a case that includes a built-in tripod mount if rapid transitions are crucial for you in your outdoor photography endeavors.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_280", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can I fit my Nikon D7100 with 55-300mm VR lens into this bag?", "long_answer": "Yes, I fit my Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens perfectly and your device has similar dimensions, so it should be compatible.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Nikon D7100 + 55-300mm VR lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Nikon D7100 + 55-300mm VR lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_211", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case from either OP/TECH USA or Case Logic, but it better not have a zipper. Fetch me the first product id that matches my requirements.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Case Logic\") AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Case Logic\") AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'OP/TECH USA' OR brand = 'Case Logic') AND closure_type != 'zipper' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_281", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this case suit my Canon EOS 7D?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case will fit. I have a Nikon D3500 and it fits perfectly. The Canon EOS 7D is roughly the same size as the D3500, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS 7D has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS 7D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_325", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the bag weather-resistant?", "long_answer": "The bag is made with durable materials; however, it has not been advertised or marketed as being waterproof or weather-resistant. Therefore, if protection against inclement weather is essential, considering an additional rain cover would be advisable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_326", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Do the clips on the Canon 200DG camera bag produce noise that may disrupt wildlife photography?", "long_answer": "The metal clips on the Canon 200DG camera bag have been noted by some users to produce noise, which can be a point of concern for wildlife photographers who require stealth to avoid disturbing animals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_327", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is there a dedicated compartment for storing water bottles in the Fastpack 200 backpack?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack includes specific storage compartments designed to hold water bottles, offering convenient access to hydration while traveling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_328", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the Case Logic SLRC-205 camera bag designed for comfortable use during outdoor activities such as hiking and cycling?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLRC-205 camera bag is deemed suitable for outdoor activities such as hiking and cycling, thanks to its durability and comfort-enhancing features. Users report that the adjustable shoulder and waist straps provide a comfortable fit, while the strap system on the front of the bag offers the convenience of securing additional equipment, such as tripods or hiking poles.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_329", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the Lowepro Flipside 300 bag include an All-Weather (AW) cover, or is it merely resistant to moderate rain?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 bag is resistant to moderate rain according to customer feedback, but it is not supplied with an All-Weather (AW) cover. Users are advised to use separate protective measures in heavy rain conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_212", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm a little tight on cash right now, but I need a camera case. I only got 10 dollars to spare and don't want any Altura Photo stuff. Find me something cheap with the least pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand != 'Altura Photo' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_213", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm not a fan of too many pockets and I like the Ape Case brand. Find me the cheapest camera case they make with no more than 2 pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND brand = \"Ape Case\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND brand = \"Ape Case\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND brand = \"Ape Case\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Ape Case' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_214", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I can't stand the sight of teal, seriously. Give me the cheapest non-teal camera case you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"teal\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"teal\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"teal\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'teal' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_330", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does this backpack have a dedicated compartment for carrying a tripod?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with a tripod storage system that features both a side strap and a hidden foldout holder, which are specifically designed to hold and secure either a compact tripod or a monopod during transport.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_331", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is it possible to reach the camera in the backpack without taking the backpack off?", "long_answer": "No, access to the camera compartment in the backpack is not possible without removing it since the design incorporates a back panel opening to enhance security.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_282", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case accommodate a T2i with a grip and an 18-130 lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to. The case fits my Nikon D3500 just fine and the size of the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens is similar to the D3500.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_332", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is there a designated laptop compartment in the Flipside 300 backpack?", "long_answer": "The Flipside 300 backpack lacks a designated compartment specifically for a laptop. It is primarily designed to accommodate camera equipment. However, the camera compartment can fit a slim netbook, but it is not intended for that purpose, and there's no guarantee it will suit all laptops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_333", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the Sony LCS-CST case compatible with the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX50 camera?", "long_answer": "The Sony LCS-CST case is specifically designed to work with the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX50 among other cameras that share a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_215", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I don't need all those extra pockets, just one will do, and it's got to be water-resistant. Find me the cheapest one that meets these specs.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 1 AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_283", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this case suitable for outdoor photography sessions in all weather conditions?", "long_answer": "For everyday outdoor activities, opting for a nylon camera case is a practical decision, given its robustness and light construction. Nevertheless, should you expect to encounter severe temperature fluctuations, it's important to note that nylon does not provide optimal thermal protection. In such cases of extreme weather, a camera case designed with superior thermal insulation would be advisable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_334", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can the rain cover that comes with the bag be removed?", "long_answer": "The bag includes a rain cover that is designed to be easily detachable, allowing users to remove it when they need to shield their belongings from rain or other elements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_284", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this bag fit my Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "No, I don't think it would fit. I have a Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens and it fits just right. Your camera with the longer 55-250 mm lens would likely be too big for this bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_285", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can a small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E fit in this case?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have the Nikon D3500 and it fits perfectly. Your camera lens also has similar dimensions so it should work too.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_335", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the backpack heavy when empty?", "long_answer": "The backpack is engineered to be lightweight while still maintaining durability, which means it does not contribute significant weight before any items are placed inside it.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_336", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does this bag resemble a typical camera bag in appearance?", "long_answer": "Customers generally perceive this bag as not resembling a typical camera bag, thereby providing a more inconspicuous means of transporting camera equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_337", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the online-listed size and description of the Ape Case Cubeze considered accurate by most consumers?", "long_answer": "Most consumers agree that the dimensions and descriptions provided online for the Ape Case Cubeze accurately represent the actual product.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_286", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Canon EOS Rebel SL1? ", "long_answer": "Yes, this case is compatible with the Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens. Since your Canon EOS Rebel SL1 has a similar size to that, it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_338", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "What is the durability level of the case's material?", "long_answer": "The case is constructed from a material comparable to what is utilized in the production of luggage, and it is characterized as well-constructed and durable, indicating a high level of durability.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_287", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Canon Powershot SX50 HS? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it does. I used it for my Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and they are pretty much the same size, so I think it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon Powershot SX50 HS has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon Powershot SX50 HS fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_288", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is it possible for me to modify the case effortlessly to accommodate the various camera models I possess?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is crafted from a material that provides outstanding flexibility, which allows it to adapt to accommodate different camera sizes, guaranteeing a snug and secure fit for your cameras.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_216", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I've only got eyes for Case Logic and AmazonBasics, and I'm a bit of a klutz so it's got to be water resistant. What's my cheapest option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'AmazonBasics') \nAND water_resistance = 'yes' \nORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_217", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm a Canon and Altura Photo fan. Dig up the cheapest camera case from either of those brands for me, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Altura Photo\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Altura Photo\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Altura Photo\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Canon', 'Altura Photo') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_218", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm tired of the usual black, got only 10 bucks to spare. Show me the least expensive non-black camera case you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'black' AND price <= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_339", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is this bag suitable for extensive professional photography shoots requiring a lot of gear?", "long_answer": "This bag is designed for photographers who need quick access to their camera while moving between locations, suggesting it works well for smaller-scale, mobile shoots. However, for large-scale professional shoots that necessitate carrying a substantial amount of equipment, a larger, more specialized bag would be a better fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_340", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can the main compartments of the camera bag accommodate both a DSLR with an attached lens and additional camera equipment such as external flashes or extra lenses?", "long_answer": "The bag's main compartments are designed to hold a DSLR with an attached lens along with potential room for an external flash or an extra lens. For those who carry several accessories or larger equipment, it may be necessary to consider extra cases or a larger camera bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_289", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will a Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens fit in this case?", "long_answer": "No, it won't. I own a Nikon D90, which fits perfectly into this case. However, the Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens is larger than the Nikon D90, so it will not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Nikon D90, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "search_qa_219", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I have a particular taste: I want a green camera case and do not want too many pockets, definitely not more than 2. What's your best match?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND pockets <= 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND pockets <= 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_220", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Sony is not my kind of brand and teal isn't my favorite shade. Show me the cheapest camera case without these attributes, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Sony\" AND NOT color = \"teal\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Sony\" AND NOT color = \"teal\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Sony\" AND NOT color = \"teal\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Sony' AND color != 'teal' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_221", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I prefer using AmazonBasics or Ape Case but I need it to be water-resistant too. Can you find the cheapest option available that meets these requirements?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Ape Case\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Ape Case\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Ape Case\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('AmazonBasics', 'Ape Case') AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_341", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the bag come equipped with both a carry handle and a shoulder strap for carrying?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with a padded carry handle on top and features an adjustable, removable shoulder strap for versatile carrying options.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_222", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I don't want any green stuff. What's the cheapest camera case from Altura Photo that's not green?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND NOT color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND NOT color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND NOT color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND color != 'green' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_223", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I don't need anything fancy like water resistance or multiple pockets. Just give me the simplest camera case you have, preferably with one pocket or less.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_342", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is it possible to use this backpack as a sling bag, despite its primary design?", "long_answer": "Though the backpack's primary design is that of a conventional two-strap backpack, there are instances where users have improvised its use as a sling bag for brief durations, indicating that it can indeed be adapted for such a purpose, albeit not officially designed for it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_290", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "May I bring this case on my desert photography excursion to safeguard my camera against the heat?", "long_answer": "Considering the case is constructed of nylon, it is unsuitable for extremely high-temperature environments. Nylon does not possess sufficient insulation properties to protect against intense heat, which should be taken into account for settings such as deserts. A case designed with thermal protective qualities would likely better serve your requirements.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_224", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm not a big fan of zippers, they always jam on me. What's the cheapest camera case you got that doesn't use a zipper?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'zipper' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_291", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate my 50-500 Sigma lenses?", "long_answer": "Absolutely. The backpack fits my Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8 perfectly, and since your lens is about the same size, it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8"}}
{"id": "search_qa_225", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm all about that green life, but I hate bulk. Find me your least pocketed, green camera case.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_292", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "No, it can't. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits, but I'm afraid yours might be too large for this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_343", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "How durable is the interior padding of the Ape Case Cubeze for camera protection?", "long_answer": "The interior of the Ape Case Cubeze includes padding that enhances its durability and offers a dependable level of protection for general everyday use, although it is not the most heavily cushioned option available.", "short_answer": "very durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_293", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this case fit my Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Nikon D90 fits well in this case, and the size of your Nikon D750 with lens is similar, so it would also fit well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_344", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can Pelican cases be used in marine environments without water ingress?", "long_answer": "Pelican cases are engineered to be watertight, using a tongue and groove fit and a polymer o-ring seal to prevent water from entering, making them highly suitable for marine environments where they need to keep moisture out.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_345", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the sling bag suitable for carrying a mirrorless camera system?", "long_answer": "Some users have reported that the sling bag is well-suited for mirrorless camera systems, which tend to be smaller in size compared to their larger DSLR counterparts, making the bag an appropriate choice for such equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_294", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for use during a professional photography assignment?", "long_answer": "The suitability of a camera case with backpack straps hinges on the specifics of the task at hand. It is generally not advised if you require a professional appearance or need to swiftly swap out equipment because it can come across as casual and may hinder your speed.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are not recommended for situations that demand rapid gear changes or a professional appearance that aligns with formal event dress codes, as a backpack might be viewed as too casual or cumbersome in such environments.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_346", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the shoulder strap on the bag adjustable and detachable?", "long_answer": "The bag comes with a shoulder strap that offers the flexibility to adjust its length according to one's comfort and preference, as well as the convenience of being able to remove it entirely if required.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_295", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Does this case provide adequate protection for my camera against sand and dust while I'm at the beach?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the case's waterproof design ensures a tight seal against fine particles such as sand and dust. However, it's important to note that to prevent scratches or damage from accidental falls onto a hard surface, such as rock, the case must have internal padding.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof characteristics lack the capability to protect against substantial impacts or drops unless they also incorporate specific padding or shock-resistant materials.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_296", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is this camera case capable of providing adequate protection for my camera when shooting in snowy environments?", "long_answer": "In snowy environments, where the case may be exposed to wet snow or thawing ice, its lack of waterproofing could pose a problem. It provides only minimal protection, and moisture from the snow might seep into the case, jeopardizing your camera. For optimal safety of your camera in snowy conditions, it is advisable to opt for a case that is specifically designated as waterproof.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_226", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I need a camera case that can handle a splash and has a zipper, but I don't want to spend a fortune. What's the cheapest option you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type = \"zipper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND closure_type = 'zipper' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_297", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Does this case accommodate wildlife photography on the go, where precision is paramount?", "long_answer": "Wildlife photography frequently necessitates agility and accuracy, particularly when taking clear pictures of moving animals. Although this case suits active pursuits well, the absence of a tripod mount might be a drawback for scenarios demanding a steady base to achieve crisp, blurless photographs.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_227", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I don't need a fancy camera case. Just dig out the cheapest one that has no more than 2 pockets and doesn't cost more than 30 dollars.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND price <= 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND price <= 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_298", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I intend to photograph near a waterfall; will this case protect my camera from moisture?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is crafted from waterproof substances like PVC or silicone, offering superb water resistance that safeguards your camera from moisture when in proximity to waterfalls.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof capabilities typically mean they are constructed from materials such as PVC or silicone that inherently resist water penetration, thereby safeguarding the camera equipment in wet conditions.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_228", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I don't need a case filled with pockets, just one will do. What's the cheapest camera case you have with less than two pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_347", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is it safe to store valuables like wallets or phones in the external pockets of this bag?", "long_answer": "The external pockets of the bag are designed for easy access and therefore do not feature secure closures. Customers generally advise against storing valuable items in these pockets because they can be prone to falling out or might be targeted by pickpockets due to the lack of secured fastening.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_229", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm only interested in black camera cases, got any? Just show me one for now.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'black' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_348", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this backpack considered a good value for the price?", "long_answer": "The backpack is viewed as providing good value by customers due to its combination of sound construction and an accessible price, which makes it a compelling choice for those seeking quality without excessive expense.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_349", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can the pocket accommodate both extra batteries and an SD card at the same time?", "long_answer": "The pocket's design is meant for carrying small items and may provide a sufficient fit for an SD card alongside extra batteries only if the battery size and quantity are small enough to allow both items to be carried simultaneously.", "short_answer": "maybe", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_350", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the Hi-Vis yellow interior improve the visibility of small accessories under low-light conditions?", "long_answer": "The Hi-Vis yellow interior of the product is considered effective in enhancing the visibility of small accessories, facilitating their location in situations where lighting is poor.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_299", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does this camera case serve as a fashionable accessory that complements one's attire?", "long_answer": "The camera case is engineered to prioritize function, emphasizing carry comfort, yet it might not meet the expectations of those in search of a high-fashion look. The shoulder strap addition leans towards practicality rather than luxurious design.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap fail to meet the requirements for users seeking a fashionable accessory, as the strap's primary focus is on functionality and comfort over luxury aesthetics.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_230", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I don't trust those fancy closure types. What's the camera case with the least amount of pockets that either uses velcro or a drawstring?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('velcro', 'drawstring') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_300", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Will this bag accommodate my Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, I doubt it. I have a Canon 70D with a 70-250 lens and it fits, but just barely. Your camera and lens are larger than mine.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_301", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm fairly small in stature; would this camera case be cumbersome to tote on my back?", "long_answer": "No, it won't be excessively bulky. The camera case features a unique design with adjustable backpack straps that can be customized to fit your frame perfectly, ensuring maximum comfort and ease of transport, regardless of your size.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps feature adjustable elements that accommodate varying body types, which is a testament to their design versatility for personalized comfort and support.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_231", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm dead set on a lockable camera case, but fewer pockets the better. Fetch me the one with the least pockets, would ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'locks' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_302", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is it reasonable to expect this camera case to be less bulky than others?", "long_answer": "Indeed, as this camera case lacks waterproofing, it usually omits the additional heft associated with protective seals. Consequently, its design is more compact and less bulky, offering a convenient option for daily use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_232", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "No way am I getting anything from OP/TECH USA and I don't need the water resistance either. Find me the cheapest camera case without these features.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'OP/TECH USA' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_303", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this bag fit a Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it would fit. I have a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens and it fits perfectly. Your lens is even smaller, therefore it should fit without any issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_304", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will this sling be large enough to accommodate a Nikon D80 with an MB80 Grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens and it fits well. From my understanding, your Nikon D80 with an MB80 Grip has approximately the same size as my Canon, so it should accommodate your camera as well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_351", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the backpack provide dedicated pockets for small items such as SD cards and batteries?", "long_answer": "The backpack includes zippered mesh pockets and a top compartment space that can accommodate smaller items. However, it's noted by some customers that there is a lack of smaller, dedicated pockets specifically designed for very small accessories like memory cards and cords.", "short_answer": "No", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_305", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can I use it with my Canon T5i with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Canon 60D with the Sigma 17-55mm f2.8 fits this case perfectly and your Canon T5i with a 300mm lens is quite similar in size, so it should fit fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_352", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the bag suitable for carrying a micro four-thirds camera system along with several lenses and accessories?", "long_answer": "This bag is capable of accommodating a micro four-thirds camera system, including the camera body, multiple lenses, a flash unit, and other related photography accessories, as reported by customers with similar equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_233", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I need a red camera case from either OP/TECH USA or Lowepro, and make sure it's the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Lowepro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Lowepro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Lowepro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' \nAND brand IN ('OP/TECH USA', 'Lowepro') \nORDER BY price \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_306", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for someone seeking a fashionable accessory to complement their attire?", "long_answer": "Although the camera case is crafted for functional superiority with an emphasis on comfortable transport, it might not meet the criterion of those looking for a high-fashion look. The shoulder strap is included to enhance practicality rather than to serve a luxury style.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap fail to meet the requirements for users seeking a fashionable accessory, as the strap's primary focus is on functionality and comfort over luxury aesthetics.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_234", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm not interested in any of the AmazonBasics stuff and I prefer either black or purple. Find me the most affordable option, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"purple\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"purple\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"purple\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'AmazonBasics' AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'purple') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_307", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "As a professional photographer, ought I to consider this camera case for my fieldwork?", "long_answer": "As a professional accustomed to working in diverse shooting environments and requiring exact camera placement, this particular camera case may not suit your needs due to the absence of a tripod attachment. This feature is often suggested for professionals to secure the best outcomes in specialized photographic situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_308", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this camera case possess a luxurious, high-end appearance that distinguishes it?", "long_answer": "Although the case is sturdy and offers outstanding protection with its EVA construction, it lacks the lavish look that materials such as leather are celebrated for, which are synonymous with luxury and visual appeal.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with material described as EVA lack the capability to be as customizable and luxurious in appearance as some high-end materials like leather, which may be preferred for their aesthetic over practicality.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "eva", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_353", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the bag resistant to harsh weather conditions like snow?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to withstand various weather conditions, including snow, as it includes a water-resistant cover that provides protection against moisture.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_235", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm not too worried about water resistance, but I don't want a ton of pockets either. Can you find me the most affordable camera case that fits these needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND pockets <= 3 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_309", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Does this camera case enable swift camera retrieval in case of an unforeseen photo opportunity?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera cases equipped with a hand grip have been crafted to provide quick and easy access to your camera. This design is especially advantageous for seizing those fleeting, unanticipated moments commonly encountered in street photography or while transitioning between shots at events.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip are known for providing quick and easy access to the camera, which is advantageous in scenarios where time is critical, such as capturing spontaneous moments in street photography or transitioning between shots at an event.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_354", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the ACPRO2000 backpack remain comfortable to carry even when it is fully loaded?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 backpack is designed with an adjustable harness system and a sternum strap to enhance comfort and balance the load when fully loaded, though some users may perceive it as heavy and opt for a wheeled version for greater convenience.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_355", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the backpack be comfortably carried on one shoulder for easy access?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with a feature that enables it to be quickly rotated to the front of the body, allowing for comfortable one-shoulder carry and convenient access.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_236", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Listen, I need a camera case but I don't want any extra pockets. Plus, the color has to be either purple or yellow. So, which product should I go for?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"yellow\") AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"yellow\") AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND (color = 'purple' OR color = 'yellow');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_356", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Hideaway Tripod Mount compatible with larger tripods?", "long_answer": "The Hideaway Tripod Mount is primarily designed for smaller, compact tripods and monopods. It may not comfortably accommodate larger tripods, and some users choose to customize the carrying method or use a separate tripod bag for larger tripods.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_237", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I have a thing for teal and yellow. So, find me the cheapest camera case you have in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"yellow\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"yellow\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"yellow\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('teal', 'yellow') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_310", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Would you suggest this camera case to someone who needs to transport their equipment over extensive distances without additional stress?", "long_answer": "This camera case features D-ring and clip attachments for enhanced functionality. However, these additions might increase the weight and bulk, potentially leading to added strain over extended periods of carrying. Should minimizing strain be a key concern, opting for a case without these extras could be more appropriate for lengthy journeys.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with d-ring or clip attachments are not suitable for photographers who prioritize ultra-lightweight gear or minimalism over functionality, as the added hardware and potential bulk may be undesirable.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "d-ring or clip attachments", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_357", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is there a widespread problem with the zippers on this product?", "long_answer": "There have been occasional reports of zipper issues; however, such incidents appear isolated and are not indicative of a pervasive defect across the product line.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_238", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm not looking to break the bank here. Can you show me the cheapest camera case you've got in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_311", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I intend to embark on a desert photography venture. Would this case suffice to safeguard my camera against sand and dust?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is appropriate for a desert photo trip. It emphasizes portability and practicality in arid settings, ensuring your gear is shielded from sand and dust. However, bear in mind that it's intended for dry conditions and isn't designed for scenarios where your gear could be submerged or subject to significant moisture.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_239", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I don't need it to be water-resistant or purple, just budget-friendly. What's the cheapest camera case you have that meets my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT color = \"purple\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT color = \"purple\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT color = \"purple\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND color != 'purple' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_240", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm not here to mess around. I want a product either from USA Gear or Canon. Give me the first camera case you find from them.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Canon\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Canon\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'Canon') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_312", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I frequently need to rapidly retrieve my camera for unforeseen photographs. Does this case facilitate such quick access?", "long_answer": "If you need quick access to your camera, you might think about opting for a non-waterproof case. Although waterproof cases provide superior protection against the elements, the seals can be less practical for regular opening and may hinder your ability to swiftly retrieve your camera.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof property are not suitable for situations where quick access and multiple openings of the case are necessary, as their protective seals can make them less convenient to open frequently.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_241", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm into Altura Photo and need a camera case. The more pockets the better, but it has to be water resistant. Get me the one with the least pockets that still meets my criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_242", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I keep losing stuff with button closure types. Get me one with either a zipper or velcro, just the one product id will do.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"zipper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"zipper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'velcro') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_358", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is this camera case compatible with bulkier point-and-shoot camera models?", "long_answer": "Designed primarily for slim digital cameras, the case may not accommodate larger point-and-shoot camera models. It is important to compare the dimensions of your camera, ensuring it does not exceed the case size of 4.38 inches in length, 3 inches in width, and 3 inches in height for a proper fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_243", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I don't need any of that water resistance stuff, but I like Sony and Ape Case brands. Find me the cheapest case from them, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Ape Case\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Ape Case\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Ape Case\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no'\nAND (brand = 'Sony' OR brand = 'Ape Case')\nORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_359", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the camera holster feature dedicated compartments for additional accessories such as spare batteries or SD cards?", "long_answer": "The camera holster is designed with an internal slip pocket specifically for a lens cap, but it lacks dedicated compartments for other accessories such as spare batteries or SD cards. Its design prioritizes a slimmer profile, catering essentially to the camera and an attached lens.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_313", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this backpack fit a Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to fit that. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens which is similar in size and it fits perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_314", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "If I frequently capture photos in extremely hot and extremely cold environments, would this case suffice?", "long_answer": "The camera case is crafted from durable and adaptable nylon, making it suitable for mild climates. Yet, it falls short in providing adequate insulation in extreme heat or cold due to nylon's limited thermal protection abilities. For your needs, a case made with specialized insulating materials would offer superior protection for your camera gear under severe weather conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_360", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the case capable of holding both a spare battery and a memory card at the same time?", "long_answer": "The case includes a small zipper pouch, designed to store either a spare battery or a memory card, however, it is not large enough to accommodate both items simultaneously.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_361", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is this case designed to accommodate electronic devices and their accessories like smartphones and chargers?", "long_answer": "The case is designed to be spacious and features customizable compartments, making it capable of securely storing various electronic devices, including smartphones and chargers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_362", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the bag provide easy and quick access to the camera for right-handed users?", "long_answer": "The bag is constructed with a zippered main compartment; however, its accessibility may be somewhat inconvenient for individuals who prefer to wear the bag on their left hip because the zipper is designed to be more accessible when worn on the right side. This suggests that right-handed users might find it easier to reach their camera quickly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_315", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this case offer sufficient protection for my camera on adventurous excursions such as mountain climbing?", "long_answer": "Should you intend to participate in activities such as mountain climbing, which involve extreme conditions, a camera case with a shoulder strap might not suffice. While these cases afford convenience, they can fall short in providing essential protection due to their flexible nature. For utmost stability and optimal safeguarding of your gear, it is advisable to opt for a hard case in these circumstances.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap cannot be used for circumstances where a rigid case is necessary due to extreme conditions or when full immobility of the equipment is required, as the mobility afforded by straps may not provide sufficient protection in these scenarios.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_316", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I favor taking photographs swiftly without much setup time involved; would this camera case suit my needs?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is perfect for photographers such as yourself who prioritize quick access and simplicity. With the omission of a tripod attachment, it's crafted to be light and handy for those swift, impromptu shots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_317", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does this backpack fit a Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it does. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens, and it fits perfectly. The Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens and the Canon 10-22mm lens are of similar sizes, so your device should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_318", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can this case provide adequate protection for my camera when I travel with it in checked baggage?", "long_answer": "No, a neoprene camera case wouldn't be ideal for transporting camera gear in checked luggage, where it's possible for heavy items to shift and exert crushing pressure. The material doesn't have the necessary stiffness to provide ample protection under these conditions. A hard-shell case would be more appropriate for this scenario.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with neoprene material do not have a function of rigid support, given neoprene’s flexible nature; therefore, they may be less protective against heavy crushing forces compared to hard-shell cases.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "neoprene", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_363", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the bag capable of accommodating two large DSLR cameras and several lenses?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with customizable interior dividers which enable it to comfortably hold two large DSLR cameras and several lenses, as reported by our customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_319", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I frequently shoot in windy conditions; would this case still be functional for me?", "long_answer": "In blustery conditions, ensuring camera stability is crucial, particularly for disciplines such as landscape photography, where the slightest motion can result in blurred photographs. Regrettably, this particular case lacks a tripod attachment, potentially rendering it less efficient at maintaining camera steadiness in such settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_320", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this fit my Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, it may not fit. I use it for my Canon L-series 100-400, and it fits perfectly. Given that your Rebel T3i with a long lens is larger, it likely won't fit in this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_364", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the AmazonBasics Sling Backpack capable of holding a DSLR camera along with 1-2 lenses and small accessories?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Sling Backpack is specifically designed to secure a smaller SLR camera body, 1-2 lenses, and several small accessories, thanks to adjustable padded dividers in its main compartment that allow you to customize the fit for your camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_365", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the bag capable of standing upright independently?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with a semi-rigid, molded EVA base, which enables it to stand upright without support, allowing for convenient accessibility to the contents inside.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_244", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm only interested in Sony or OP/TECH USA brands. Can you find me the cheapest camera case from either of these two?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"OP/TECH USA\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"OP/TECH USA\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'OP/TECH USA') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_366", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is it possible to access the contents of the backpack without fully removing it?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with a side entry compartment, allowing the wearer to swing the backpack around to the front to access items such as a camera without having to take the backpack off entirely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_367", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the ACPRO2000 backpack feature a specific attachment mechanism for a tripod?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 backpack is equipped with loops at its bottom, which are designed to attach a tripod or a monopod, allowing for secure transportation of these items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_368", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is the camera quickly accessible when using this pouch?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch is designed to protect your camera and does offer convenience, but due to its snug fit and secure snaps, it may take a few seconds to retrieve your camera, suggesting it is not the best option for those seeking immediate access.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_369", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can the Lowepro Passport Sling be used as a carry-on item during air travel without exceeding standard size restrictions?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Passport Sling has a compact design that generally adheres to carry-on size restrictions for air travel, making it a comfortable choice for passengers to bring on board. However, it is advisable for travelers to verify the size guidelines with their specific airline before travel to ensure compliance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_370", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the dividers in the Fastpack 200 camera compartment be easily adjusted to fit specific camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The dividers in the Fastpack 200 camera compartment are designed to be adjustable, enabling customization for various sizes of camera gear. The ease of reconfiguration is subject to the dimensions of the equipment, as larger items may reduce the range of possible arrangements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_371", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the Ape Case Cubeze waterproof?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze itself is not marketed as waterproof. However, users recommend putting it within a waterproof or dry bag to provide additional water protection if necessary.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_372", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the backpack offer a feature to secure its contents with a luggage lock?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with zippers that are designed to be compatible with a luggage lock, enabling you to enhance the security of the backpack's contents.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_321", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it for my Canon 60D with a Sigma 17-55mm f2.8 lens, and your camera with the 135mm zoom is roughly the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_322", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this pouch fit my Canon EOS Rebel T5?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits like a glove. The Canon EOS Rebel T5 is similar in size to the 70D so it should fit well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T5 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T5 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_323", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for hiking excursions where I'll be frequently mobile?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is equipped with backpack straps, which makes it perfectly suited for situations that necessitate traversing different terrains. It is especially beneficial for adventure photographers who need to transport their gear comfortably while hiking or engaging in comparable journeys.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are ideally used for applications that involve movement across varying terrain or travel, lending themselves to be particularly useful for adventure and travel photographers.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_324", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate my Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense?", "long_answer": "Sorry, this backpack would not be a good fit. It's designed to hold devices up to the size of a Nikon D3500. Your Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense is larger than the Nikon D3500.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_245", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I've heard good stuff about Altura Photo and Canon. Tell me which one of their camera cases is the cheapest.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Canon\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Canon\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Canon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Altura Photo', 'Canon') \nORDER BY price \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_246", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case from either Case Logic or Altura Photo, but nothing too fancy - just one with the fewest pockets. Can you help me out?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Altura Photo\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Altura Photo\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Altura Photo\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'Altura Photo') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_373", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is there a designated way to attach a tripod to this camera bag?", "long_answer": "Yes, the camera bag is equipped with tripod straps on the exterior, allowing for the convenient attachment and transportation of a tripod with your camera gear.", "short_answer": "Yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_247", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I need a compact case without all that excessive storage. What's the product ID for the smallest camera case from Case Logic or Sony?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Sony\") AND pockets < 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Sony\") AND pockets < 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'Sony') AND pockets=0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_374", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG camera bag comfortable for prolonged carrying?", "long_answer": "The comfort level of carrying the Canon 200DG camera bag for extended periods is subjective, with some users considering it comfortable and others recommending a more padded strap or a backpack for better comfort during long carrying durations.", "short_answer": "User experiences vary", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_248", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Mica's just not my color. Tell me, what's the first camera case you have that's not in this color?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'mica' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_375", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does this backpack comfortably fit larger camera bodies like the Nikon D7000?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed to be accommodating, but users with larger camera bodies, such as the Nikon D7000, have experienced a snug fit which might make carrying such equipment less comfortable. To ensure compatibility, it is recommended to compare the backpack’s dimensions with the dimensions of the camera body.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_376", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can the Case Logic SLR Camera Sling fit a Canon SL1 camera, an additional lens, and various camera accessories?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLR Camera Sling is specifically designed to carry an SLR camera body, such as the Canon SL1, with a standard lens attached. Furthermore, it offers a separate zippered compartment for storing an extra lens or flash, as well as additional pockets tailored for carrying camera accessories like batteries, chargers, and memory cards.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_249", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I don't want any other brands. Give me the first camera case you find from Altura Photo or Pelican.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Pelican\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Pelican\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Altura Photo', 'Pelican') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_377", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the bag resistant to water and able to protect its contents in rainy or wet conditions?", "long_answer": "The bag is crafted from durable, water-repellent nylon and incorporates a weather-flap lid, features that contribute to its capacity to withstand wet conditions effectively, as reported by consumers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_378", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the ACPRO2000 bag feature pockets suitable for organizing accessories such as cords, chargers, and batteries?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 is equipped with several pockets and sleeves specifically designed for efficient organization, allowing users to neatly arrange accessories like cords, chargers, batteries, and other small items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_325", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can I fit my Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom into this bag?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The product is compatible with a Canon 10-22mm lens, and your Canon 70D with a 135mm is similar in size, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_379", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can the Pelican 1120 case fit comfortably inside a backpack for easy transportation?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1120 case is considered by many users to be compact and convenient for transportation, which makes it suitable for carrying within a larger bag or backpack without taking up excessive space.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_250", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I need a camera case that doesn't have that Lowepro branding, preferably something with zippers or locks. Show me the one with the fewest pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") AND NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") AND NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") AND NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Lowepro' AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'locks') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_251", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I got a thing for teal and I don't need a bunch of pockets. Just find me the cheapest teal camera case with less than two pockets.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND pockets < 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND pockets < 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'teal' AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_252", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm looking for a quirky camera case in teal or orange, but I'm not a fan of too many pockets. So, find me a case that has the least pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"orange\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"orange\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"orange\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('teal', 'orange') \nORDER BY pockets ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_253", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I have a thing for Lowepro but my wallet does not. Can you get me the cheapest Lowepro camera case you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Lowepro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_380", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is this case capable of protecting its contents from significant impacts?", "long_answer": "The design of this case prioritizes durability, aiming to protect its contents from damage due to impacts. The level of protection is influenced by the severity of the impact, so while the case is built to be tough, the contents might still be at risk if subjected to extremely forceful impacts, and careful handling is recommended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_381", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the Ape Case Cubeze 37 an appropriate choice for carrying camera equipment during ice climbing or hiking trips?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze 37 is designed to be suitable for outdoor activities such as ice climbing or hiking. It is compact enough to fit inside most backpacks, which makes it convenient for storing and protecting camera equipment during such activities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_254", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I want a camera case that stands out. Find me a yellow one that either has a drawstring or velcro closure.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND color = \"yellow\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND color = \"yellow\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'yellow' AND (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'velcro');"}}
{"id": "search_qa_255", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I hate fumbling around for my stuff. Give me a camera case with either a zipper or velcro but no extra pockets. And make it the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'velcro') AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_382", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the Ape Case ACPRO2000 provide sufficient storage and organization for professional photographers with extensive equipment?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 is tailored to meet the needs of professional photographers and serious enthusiasts by offering substantial space and customizable padded dividers. These features allow for efficient storage and organization of an array of photography equipment, such as multiple cameras, lenses, lighting setups, and audio devices.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_326", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is this case suitable for ensuring that there is no movement of the camera and its components within the bag?", "long_answer": "Should it be critical to restrict interior movement, consider choosing a case offering less elasticity than that of nylon. Nylon's pliability may permit slight displacement of the camera and its parts, contrary to the need for absolute immobilization of the camera inside the case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_327", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "During my photography travels, I often transition between spots; will my case remain sleek and manageable?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case will remain compact and easy to manage while on the go. Its nylon fabrication ensures it's both lightweight and form-fitting for your photographic gear, rendering it perfect for travel photography where constant movement is required.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_256", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm only looking for Case Logic camera cases that can withstand some water. Give me the first one you find, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)` with asin: B00WUIIH8W", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Case Logic' AND water_resistance = 'yes' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_383", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "How durable are the zippers and straps on this bag according to customer reports?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback indicates that the zippers and straps on the bag are considered robust and offer satisfactory durability under a variety of conditions, suggesting that they are reliable components of the bag.", "short_answer": "very durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_384", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Flipside 300 pack designed to be easily maneuverable on public transportation?", "long_answer": "The Flipside 300 pack features a compact and non-bulky design, which enhances its manageability in crowded spaces and makes it well-suited for use on public transportation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_385", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG camera bag designed with a secure closure system to prevent equipment from falling out?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag is equipped with a top flap that features two Velcro strips on the sides and utilizes front clips for additional security. To prevent equipment from falling out, it is essential to fasten the front clips securely since the bag's main compartment does not have a zipper closure.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_386", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Does the bag have dedicated space for personal items in addition to camera gear?", "long_answer": "The bag has been designed with specific compartments that allow for the storage of both camera gear and personal essentials such as a wallet, phone, keys, and other items, ensuring that users can carry everything comfortably in one bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_387", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can the gear within the bag be fully accessed without placing the bag on the ground?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to allow on-the-go access to all gear, although some customers report difficulty reaching items in the lower compartments due to the zipper not fully extending to the base of the bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_328", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Would this case suffice if I frequently take photos in extremely hot and extremely cold climates?", "long_answer": "This camera case boasts the durability and adaptability of nylon, suitable for temperate climates. Nevertheless, it falls short in providing adequate insulation against the severe heat or cold. In your case, opting for a case designed with specialized thermal insulation materials would offer superior protection for your camera gear under those extreme weather conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_329", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can this case shield my camera from water damage while shooting outdoors?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case's waterproof functionality, featuring sealed zippers or roll-top closures, is designed to protect your camera under harsh weather conditions, effectively shielding it from water damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a waterproof design are known for incorporating sealed zippers or roll-top closures that prevent water intrusion, ensuring that the camera remains dry in challenging weather or aquatic environments.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_330", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this case appropriate for outdoor photography where I frequently need to alter storage configurations?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the material is perfect for outdoor photography because it offers the essential flexibility, letting you easily adjust the storage options to meet your needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_331", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can this bag accommodate my Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. This backpack can accommodate a Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip is similar in size to that, so your camera should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_332", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon 5DII? ", "long_answer": "Yes, this bag should fit your Canon 5DII perfectly. It holds my Nikon D3500 well and the dimensions are very similar.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5DII has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5DII fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_257", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm a fan of Pelican and love cases with drawstring closures. Show me the one you have with the smallest number of pockets.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND brand = \"Pelican\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND brand = \"Pelican\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND brand = \"Pelican\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Pelican' AND closure_type = 'drawstring' ORDER BY pockets LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_333", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Will this case adequately protect my camera should I inadvertently knock against objects while exploring a new city?", "long_answer": "Although the camera case featuring a belt loop offers essential protection, it isn't engineered to absorb substantial impacts. Should you have a tendency to knock into objects or expect a greater likelihood of impacts, a sturdier case would be advisable to safeguard your camera effectively.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop cannot be used for securely storing the camera while engaging in activities with a high likelihood of impact, such as rock climbing or mountain biking, where a tougher case may be necessary.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_388", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does this case provide sufficient protection for a DSLR camera to be carried without a larger bag?", "long_answer": "The case is designed to offer enough protection for a DSLR camera, allowing it to be carried without requiring the additional use of a larger bag, which has been found suitable by many customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_389", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the item have multiple pockets to accommodate small accessories such as cables, batteries, and memory cards?", "long_answer": "The item comes with several pockets specifically designed to hold and organize small accessories, including cables, batteries, and memory cards, to ensure they are easily accessible.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_258", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I got a thing for teal and I’m a die-hard Canon fan. Point me to your first Canon camera case in teal, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras` with asin: B001I3X3HU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND brand = \"Canon\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND brand = \"Canon\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'teal' AND brand = 'Canon' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_334", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can I use this pouch for my 6D with a 24-105mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I've been using it with a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens, which is about the same size as your camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the 6D w/24-105mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the 6D w/24-105mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_259", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm looking for a fresh look. Give me the first camera case you find that's either purple or teal.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"teal\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"teal\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('purple', 'teal') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_335", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is it reasonable to anticipate that this camera case will retain its shape through years of usage?", "long_answer": "Certainly. The camera case is constructed of nylon, a material renowned for its stretch resistance. As a result, the case is more likely to maintain its form over prolonged periods, despite frequent usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_260", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I don't need anything too fancy or expensive but still need some storage. What's the cheapest camera case under a hundred bucks and with no more than two pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND pockets <= 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND pockets <= 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_336", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is there a solution within this case for securely carrying my bulky tripod together with my camera?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the case features a specialized compartment perfectly suited for holding your large tripod. This thoughtful design not only ensures the protection of your camera gear but also facilitates more convenient and secure transport of the entire kit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket feature designs that aim to protect camera equipment from scratches or damage potentially caused by tripod legs or knobs, contributing to the overall safety of the stored gear.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_337", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I frequently photograph events where swift lens changes are necessary; is this case suitable for that purpose?", "long_answer": "No, this case may not be the ideal choice for situations demanding rapid, single-handed access, such as event photography. Its backpack strap design necessitates more time to take off and reach equipment than a shoulder bag, which can be easily swung around for quick retrieval.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps cannot be used for scenarios where a quick, one-handed operation or access is necessary such as in certain types of event photography, since taking off the backpack can be more time-consuming than simply swinging a shoulder bag around.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_390", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the padding in this camera case sufficient to protect my camera from shock damage?", "long_answer": "The case's padding offers some level of shock protection, but for enhanced protection against more substantial impacts, users have the option to insert additional padding based on their specific needs and concerns.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_391", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the bag designed solely for carrying camera equipment, or can it be used for other items as well?", "long_answer": "The bag is not exclusively for camera equipment; the top compartment and additional pockets are versatile enough to hold personal items, enabling the bag to serve multiple purposes.", "short_answer": "versatile use", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_261", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Look, I don't care about water resistance and I hate too many pockets. Just find me the simplest camera case you got with no more than 1 pocket.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_392", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Do the bag's external pockets feature zippers for secure storage of accessories?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with zippered external pockets which offer secure storage options for items such as batteries, chargers, and card readers, ensuring they are safely contained.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_262", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Look, I don't want any camera cases that lock and they better be water resistant. Now find me the cheapest one that meets those criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'locks' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_263", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm not exactly after fancy stuff, just need a basic camera case without too many pockets and definitely not pricey. Point me to the least expensive one with pockets not more than the average.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_264", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Look, I only trust Altura Photo or Lowepro for my gear. What's the cheapest camera case you have from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Lowepro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Lowepro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Lowepro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Altura Photo', 'Lowepro') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_265", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I lost my keys way too often for a case with locks. What's the cheapest camera case that doesn't have a lock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'locks' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_338", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is it safe to take this camera case to the beach without concern for water damage?", "long_answer": "The camera case material provides a degree of protection against moisture, yet it is not entirely waterproof without supplemental treatments. It is prudent to implement extra protective measures when exposing it to challenging elements like sand and saltwater.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_393", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is there an allocated space for small accessories such as batteries and memory cards in the Ape Case Cubeze 37?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze 37 lacks designated pockets for small accessories, meaning items like batteries and memory cards must be kept in the main compartment or in a different section of the external bag used to carry the case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_394", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "What are the specific exterior dimensions of the Ape Case Cubeze 37?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze 37 has exterior dimensions measured to be 8.5 inches in length, 6.5 inches in width, and 3.5 inches in height. It is advised for potential customers to verify these dimensions to ensure it will fit properly inside any other bag they plan to use it with.", "short_answer": "8.5x6.5x3.5 inches", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_395", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the backpack provide protection for equipment against bumps and possible damage during transport?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with significant internal padding specifically designed to cushion equipment from standard impacts and jolts that may occur while carrying the items during transit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_266", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I lose it with velcro and I'm not too keen on water resistant stuff either. Run me through the first camera case you have that stays clear of both.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type <> 'velcro' AND water_resistance <> 'yes' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_267", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I can't stand fussing over too many pockets and zippers. Just get me a simple drawstring camera case with one pocket or less. So, which model is it?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring' AND pockets <= 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_396", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Does the Velcro closure maintain its effectiveness after prolonged use?", "long_answer": "The durability of the Velcro closure has not been frequently reported by customers; however, it is common for Velcro to lose its effectiveness after being used repeatedly over an extended period.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_397", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "How sturdy are the metal clips on the shoulder strap of this bag?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with heavy-duty metal clips on the shoulder strap that are designed to offer a robust and dependable attachment, ensuring the durability of the connection points.", "short_answer": "very sturdy", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_339", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm organizing a desert photo shoot. Would this case adequately safeguard my camera against sand and dust?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is well-suited for a desert photography expedition. Its design emphasizes both compactness and practicality in arid conditions, providing protection against sand and dust. However, be aware that although it's intended for dry climates, it's not designed for scenarios in which your gear could be submerged or subjected to substantial moisture.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_398", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the backpack comfortable to wear when it is fully loaded?", "long_answer": "Customer reviews indicate that the backpack comfortably distributes its weight when fully loaded due to its padded straps and an adjustable sternum strap, contributing to a comfortable wearing experience even with a heavy load.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_340", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Will this sling backpack fit my Nikon D3200 with a Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should do. I use it for my Canon 60D with a Sigma 17-55mm f2.8 lens and they fit perfectly. The size of your Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 would be comparable to that.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_399", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Can the camera bag remain fully horizontal when a tripod is attached?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with the tripod straps on the front, which prevents it from sitting completely flat when a tripod is attached. The design primarily facilitates transport rather than stationary support or storage in an upright position.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_268", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I've had enough with Lowepro products. Can you please find me another brand for camera cases? Just one will do.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lowepro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Lowepro' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_400", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Does the case's interior material effectively protect the camera screen from scratches?", "long_answer": "The case's interior is lined with a soft material specifically designed to shield your camera's screen from being scratched, providing protection and maintaining the screen's integrity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_269", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm not into that mica nonsense and I'm a fan of locks and zippers. Run me the cheapest camera case you have that meets those criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color <> 'mica' AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'zipper') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_401", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the camera case returnable if it does not properly fit my camera?", "long_answer": "The camera case can be returned if it does not accommodate your camera, provided that the return is made in alignment with the established terms and conditions of our return policy.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_270", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm trying to stay under 10 dollars for a case, but I'm also picky about color. I want either a teal or yellow one. What's the best option that has the fewest pockets?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"teal\", \"yellow\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"teal\", \"yellow\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"teal\", \"yellow\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND (color = 'teal' OR color = 'yellow') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_341", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this case withstand daily use in a professional photography environment?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is designed to endure the rigors of routine use, particularly in professional environments. Its nylon build provides outstanding abrasion resistance, ensuring it retains its structure and safeguards your camera even through regular use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_402", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack come with a tripod mount attachment feature?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with a hideaway Tripod Mount system that allows for the secure attachment of a tripod to the pack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_342", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I like capturing images in dynamic settings. Is this case designed for such activities?", "long_answer": "This camera case thrives in fast-paced settings. Its design, lacking a tripod attachment, minimizes encumbrances, facilitating rapid and effortless access to your camera so that you can snap those ephemeral moments with the slightest delay.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_271", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I can't stand Case Logic, but I do have a soft spot for orange. What's the cheapest orange camera case you've got that isn't from that brand?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" AND color = \"orange\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" AND color = \"orange\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" AND color = \"orange\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'orange' AND brand != 'Case Logic' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_343", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I frequently trek to my photoshoot sites. Does this camera case offer convenient portability for extended hikes?", "long_answer": "Should you favor a lightweight and minimalist setup for your hiking adventures, this particular camera case may not be ideal, given that the integrated tripod pocket could contribute extra weight and bulk. Opting for a case devoid of this specific feature may align more closely with your desires for portability.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket are not suitable for photographers who prioritize the most lightweight and minimalist gear setup, as this feature may add to the bulk and weight of the case.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_403", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can the Pelican 1200 Case be safely used to transport firearms by air?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case is specifically designed to offer secure and robust protection for valuables, such as firearms, intended for air travel. To ensure the firearm is securely stored, it is recommended to custom cut the foam for a snug fit and comply with TSA regulations concerning locks and the transportation of firearms.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_272", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I've had it up to here with all these drawstring camera cases, they're just not for me. Give me the first Altura Photo brand case you have without a drawstring, would ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND closure_type != 'drawstring' ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_344", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is there cause for concern regarding moisture penetration into the case when photographing in misty or humid environments?", "long_answer": "No need for concern; the waterproof construction, featuring sealed zippers or roll-top closures, provides strong protection against moisture, ensuring your camera remains secure in humid or wet conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a waterproof design are known for incorporating sealed zippers or roll-top closures that prevent water intrusion, ensuring that the camera remains dry in challenging weather or aquatic environments.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_404", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the bag require extensive maintenance to keep it clean?", "long_answer": "According to customer feedback, the bag does not require extensive maintenance and is considered relatively easy to maintain. However, for removal of external dirt or stains, occasional gentle cleaning with a damp cloth might be necessary.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_405", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the design of the camera bag allow for fast retrieval of the camera?", "long_answer": "The bag is explicitly designed to enable photographers to swiftly access their camera, which is especially advantageous when they need to capture moments on the go without delays.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_273", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm not a fan of purple and I really don't need many pockets. So, tell me, what's the first camera case you have that doesn't come in purple and has less than two pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND pockets < 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND pockets < 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'purple' AND pockets < 2 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_274", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I want a red camera case but definitely not from AmazonBasics. Find me one now.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND brand <> 'AmazonBasics';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_345", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for my requirement of swiftly changing locations during a shoot?", "long_answer": "Absolutely, this camera case is designed to facilitate quick movements and swift changes in location during shooting sessions. Its construction, lacking a tripod attachment, enhances mobility and convenience for dynamic on-the-go photography, aligning seamlessly with an active approach to shooting.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_346", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "As a professional photographer, is this camera case suitable for my fieldwork?", "long_answer": "As a professional accustomed to diverse shooting environments and requiring exact camera placement, this particular camera case may fall short as it lacks a tripod attachment—a feature often suggested for professionals to achieve optimal outcomes in specialized shooting situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_275", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm only buying if it's a Pelican brand and want either a drawstring or a zipper closure. So what's the product id for the case that checks those boxes?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") AND brand = \"Pelican\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") AND brand = \"Pelican\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Pelican' AND (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'zipper');"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_347", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Could this camera case assist in alleviating fatigue during prolonged outdoor photography sessions?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case featuring backpack straps is designed to distribute weight uniformly across your shoulders, significantly minimizing fatigue during extended outdoor photography sessions. Its ergonomic design provides support for adventure photographers traversing a variety of terrains.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are ideally used for applications that involve movement across varying terrain or travel, lending themselves to be particularly useful for adventure and travel photographers.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_406", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this camera bag accommodate an SLR camera body with a 70-300mm lens attached?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is built to fit most SLR camera bodies with standard kit lenses, and while the interior dimensions imply a tight fit, it may not comfortably accommodate a camera with a 70-300mm lens attached.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_348", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is this case suitable for outdoor photography sessions in all weather conditions?", "long_answer": "For most outdoor activities, a nylon camera case is a practical option because it's both durable and light. Nevertheless, in situations where you expect to encounter extreme temperatures, it's important to know that nylon does not provide optimal insulation from such extremes. For those harsh weather conditions, a camera case with better thermal protection may be required.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_276", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm looking for a new camera case, but I'm not a fan of the color green. Do you have any options from Altura Photo or OP/TECH USA? Just show me the first one that comes up.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND NOT color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND NOT color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Altura Photo', 'OP/TECH USA') AND color != 'green' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_277", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm not big on green. Give me a camera case of any other color, but make sure it's the one with the least number of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'green' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_407", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the belt loop attachment considered reliable for securely carrying a camera?", "long_answer": "The belt loop attachment has generally received feedback that it functions well for carrying a camera; however, it is not infallible, and caution is recommended during use to ensure the safety of the camera.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_408", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag designed for use with items other than camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag's design includes multifunctionality, featuring an expandable compartment that allows the bag to carry personal items beyond just camera equipment, which can be particularly convenient for activities like sightseeing or casual strolls around town.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_278", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I am a fan of USA Gear and Ape Case brands. Could you find me the cheapest camera case from these two brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Ape Case\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Ape Case\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Ape Case\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'Ape Case') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_409", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the side-entry compartment of the bag designed for rapid retrieval of the camera?", "long_answer": "The bag is outfitted with a side-entry compartment, which is specifically designed to enable fast and convenient access to the camera and its accessories, thereby eliminating the need to take off the backpack to reach the contents.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_279", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I need a camera case that can handle a drizzle and is green in color. What do you have like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND color = 'green';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_280", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I ain't gonna be near any water, and I fancy the zipper type. What's the cheapest camera case you got that matches my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras` with asin: B005VTIMEQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND closure_type = \"zipper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'zipper' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_349", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will the camera case provide complete protection for my equipment during heavy rainfall?", "long_answer": "Despite the camera case being constructed from robust material, it should be noted that cases fashioned from this material typically offer only elementary water resistance. To achieve full waterproof-proofing, further measures would be required to guarantee that your gear remains dry during intense rainfall.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_410", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the backpack have a dedicated holder for carrying a tripod or monopod?", "long_answer": "The backpack features an exterior holder specifically designed for the purpose of accommodating a tripod or monopod, allowing for easy transport of such equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_411", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the case considered bulky by customers?", "long_answer": "Based on customer feedback, the case is perceived as relatively compact and is not considered to be bulky, which enhances its practicality for daily use and for carrying around during travel.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_350", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can I use this case for my Nikon D5000?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will fit. I use this case for my Nikon D3500 which is similar in size to the Nikon D5000.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Nikon D5000 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Nikon D5000 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_351", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is it possible to adjust the camera case for a comfortable fit on someone with a larger build?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case features adjustable components that accommodate different body shapes, ensuring that it offers a customizable fit for both large and small frames. The backpack straps, in particular, offer flexibility in adjustment and support.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps feature adjustable elements that accommodate varying body types, which is a testament to their design versatility for personalized comfort and support.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_352", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will this case fit my Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Nikon D5000 with a battery grip, which is about the same size as your lens, and it fits perfectly in this case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_412", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 model designed to accommodate a 17\" Macbook Pro?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 model is not equipped with a dedicated laptop compartment suitable for a 17\" Macbook Pro. If you need to carry a laptop of that size, the Lowepro Fastpack 350 is recommended as an alternative since it features a dedicated compartment for larger laptops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_413", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can the camera be quickly accessed from this sling while walking?", "long_answer": "The sling is designed to offer quick camera access, enabling the user to swiftly swing the case to the front and reach their camera and accessories without delay.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_353", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case that isn't overly bulky for my everyday city photography pursuits. Would this item suit my needs?", "long_answer": "Considering that camera bags featuring a specialized tripod compartment are often bulkier, they may not be the best option if you prefer a lightweight, easily portable bag for urban excursions. Opting for a slimmer case without a tripod pocket might be preferable for a streamlined gear arrangement.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket are not suitable for photographers who prioritize the most lightweight and minimalist gear setup, as this feature may add to the bulk and weight of the case.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_281", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I've got a thing for teal and don't like too many pockets. Can you find me the cheapest teal camera case with one or less pockets?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND pockets <= 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND pockets <= 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'teal' AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_414", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "How accessible are the small accessories included with this product?", "long_answer": "The small accessories that come with this product are easily accessible, as indicated by the product's design and packaging which ensures users can reach and use these components without difficulty.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_415", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does this backpack come with an external holder for a tripod or monopod?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with an exterior holder specifically designed to secure a small tripod or monopod.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_354", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can I fit a 70-200/2.8 lens in this bag?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be fine. I am using it with a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens which is approximately the same size as your lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the 70-200/2.8 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the 70-200/2.8 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_416", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Do users commonly experience problems with the zippers on the bag?", "long_answer": "Some users have reported that they find the zippers on the bag a bit challenging to access. However, this seems to be a subjective issue, as it is not widely reported as a widespread problem.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_282", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm tired of the same old black camera cases. Show me the non-black case with the least amount of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'black' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_283", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I can't stand the flimsy stuff from OP/TECH USA. Give me a case that either locks or uses velcro straps. And by the way, I don't need a lot of pockets, so what's the one with the least?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'OP/TECH USA' AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'velcro') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_417", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is this camera bag considered ideal for both travel and hiking by customers?", "long_answer": "This camera bag has been reported by many customers to be ideal for travel and hiking, thanks to its optimal size, protective features, and sufficient capacity to hold essential gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_355", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is it possible for me to swiftly retrieve my camera from this case when a photographic opportunity arises as I stroll?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case may not be the most practical option if you require quick, one-handed access to your camera while on the go. The backpack design requires you to remove it to get to your gear, making it less speedy than other cases with designs that allow for easier access.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps cannot be used for scenarios where a quick, one-handed operation or access is necessary such as in certain types of event photography, since taking off the backpack can be more time-consuming than simply swinging a shoulder bag around.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_418", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Have users reported any problems with the zippers on the side pockets when they are fully packed?", "long_answer": "Users have occasionally noted that the zippers may feel constrained when the side pockets are fully packed, although there are no widespread complaints concerning the zipper functionality overall.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_284", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm pretty clumsy and can't risk getting my camera wet. Also, I hate fiddling with those latch closures. What's the first case that's water-resistant and has either a zipper or drawstring?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_356", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can this bag fit my Canon EOS Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case will comfortably fit your Canon EOS Rebel T3. I use it for my Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, which is a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_285", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I've got my eyes on an Altura Photo case, but I really can't stand teal. Tell me the one with the least pockets that isn't that obnoxious color.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND NOT color = \"teal\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND NOT color = \"teal\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND NOT color = \"teal\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND color != 'teal' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_419", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the backpack come with straps that allow for the attachment of a tripod?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with exterior straps specifically designed to securely attach a tripod or other large items to the outside of the bag, facilitating easy transport.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_286", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm not one for swimming or beach trips, so I don't need any of that water-resistant stuff. Give me a camera case from either Lowepro or USA Gear without water resistance.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"USA Gear\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"USA Gear\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'Lowepro' OR brand = 'USA Gear') AND water_resistance = 'no';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_287", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm only interested in camera cases that are either black or green. Point me to the first one you got in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('black', 'green') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_357", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the case sufficiently sturdy to endure regular use outdoors?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is made from nylon, a material renowned for its exceptional tensile strength. As a result, it boasts resistance to tearing and stretching, ensuring lasting durability even with heavy outdoor usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_358", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this case appropriate for photographing scenarios where holding the camera isn't feasible, such as when utilizing a remote shutter?", "long_answer": "In scenarios that require hands-free camera operation, such as using a remote shutter, the absence of a tripod attachment on this camera case will not offer sufficient stability independently. For such circumstances, a case compatible with a tripod is recommended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_359", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm uncertain whether my robust tripod exceeds the size of a typical camera case. Is your product capable of accommodating larger gear?", "long_answer": "The adjustable external straps on our camera case offer versatility, allowing for the secure attachment of even larger tripods, ensuring your heavy-duty gear can be accommodated.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with external straps for tripod attachment feature adjustable designs that cater to various sizes and models of tripods, making the camera case versatile and adaptable to individual photographer's needs.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "external straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_360", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for professional photographers with extensive equipment?", "long_answer": "Professional photographers often transport a significant collection of equipment, encompassing hefty lenses and various accessories. A camera case equipped with a belt loop might not be the ideal suggestion, considering its restricted carrying capacity, which isn't meant to accommodate such a comprehensive array of gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop are not suitable for individuals who prefer to carry multiple heavy lenses and accessories due to the limited load capacity that a single belt loop may offer.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_420", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is neoprene sufficient for protecting my camera from minor impacts, moisture, and dust?", "long_answer": "Neoprene, the material used in the Soft Pouch, offers your camera some level of protection against minor impacts, moisture, and dust, which can be suitable for everyday use situations. However, it may not be adequate for safeguarding against more severe drops or impacts that could be encountered in harsher conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_361", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the camera case crafted for photographers requiring swift location changes?", "long_answer": "Certainly, our camera cases are designed for photographers who need to transition swiftly from one location to another. Lacking a tripod attachment feature ensures a streamlined experience, facilitating rapid packing and unpacking of your camera equipment without additional procedures.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_288", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Look, I'm tired of zippers and claps. Get me the ID of a camera case with a drawstring closure, would you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_289", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I can't be bothered with zippers or latches. Just show me the cheapest camera case with either a lock or drawstring closure.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('lock', 'drawstring') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_362", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this case appropriate for outdoor photography when frequent adjustments to storage configurations are required?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the material is perfect for outdoor photography, offering the required adaptability and enabling effortless customization of storage setups to meet your needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_290", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I've had enough of those lock-type cases and nothing from USA Gear for me, got it? Find me the cheapest camera case you got that meets these conditions.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'USA Gear' AND closure_type != 'locks' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_421", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can the internal compartments of the camera bag be reconfigured to accommodate various types of camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is designed with adjustable dividers, allowing users to customize the interior layout to suit their individual camera gear requirements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_291", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm looking for a mica colored camera case specifically from either OP/TECH USA or Altura Photo. Can you help me find that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Altura Photo\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Altura Photo\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'mica' AND (brand = 'OP/TECH USA' OR brand = 'Altura Photo');"}}
{"id": "search_qa_292", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I've got a thing for yellow, but keep Canon off the table. Can you find me the most affordable yellow camera case from a different brand?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND NOT brand = \"Canon\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND NOT brand = \"Canon\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND NOT brand = \"Canon\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'yellow' AND brand != 'Canon' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_422", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack spacious enough to accommodate multiple camera lenses and a battery grip along with a DSLR camera?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack is specifically designed to carry a DSLR camera with a standard zoom lens and offers additional compartments for accessories like extra lenses or flash units. However, customers with a considerable amount of gear have found the backpack to be insufficient in size, especially when needing to include multiple lenses and a battery grip.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_363", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "As a petite individual, I'm concerned that this camera case might be too cumbersome for me to comfortably tote on my back.", "long_answer": "No, it won't be overly bulky. The camera case features an innovative design with adjustable backpack straps that can be customized to fit your physique, ensuring maximum comfort and ease of carrying, no matter your body size.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps feature adjustable elements that accommodate varying body types, which is a testament to their design versatility for personalized comfort and support.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_293", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I'm a fan of Case Logic, but don't need it to be water resistant. What's the cheapest Case Logic camera case you have without water resistance?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Case Logic' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_423", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the Soft Pouch attachment screw remain reliably fastened during use?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch utilizes a plastic attachment screw, and though most users haven't faced problems, some have experienced it becoming loose over time. It is recommended to check and tighten the attachment screw regularly to ensure the security of the pouch.", "short_answer": "Occasionally loose", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_424", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the case designed to accommodate a charger along with extra batteries?", "long_answer": "The case is primarily designed to carry small accessories, including extra batteries and memory cards. However, fitting a charger inside the case is possible, albeit the fit may be snug and will vary based on the charger's dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_294", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm only interested in Sony or Canon camera cases, and it must be orange. Give me a product ID for one that fits.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Canon\") AND color = \"orange\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Canon\") AND color = \"orange\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'Canon') AND color = 'orange' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_425", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is the Pelican case suitable for motorcycle mounting during travel?", "long_answer": "Pelican cases are frequently mounted on motorcycles by customers, leveraging the case's robustness and durability, which makes it well-suited for such applications.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_364", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for extended photo shoots where I will be standing for the majority of the day?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is well-suited for all-day photography sessions, thanks to its lightweight nylon construction that eases the load on your shoulders and back during prolonged use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_295", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I don't do purple, so find me the cheapest non-purple camera case you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'purple' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_426", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the bag equipped with an integrated waterproof cover?", "long_answer": "The listed features of the bag do not claim the presence of a built-in waterproof cover. While the materials used in the bag's construction are durable and provide some protection against light rainfall, as shared by customer experiences, it is advisable to utilize an additional rain cover for substantial protection in heavy rain conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_365", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can I use this case with my Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes. This case is a great fit for the Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and your device has similar dimensions, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_366", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a Canon 70-200 F4 lens? ", "long_answer": "No, I don't think so. I have had a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens in this backpack, which just fit perfectly. Since Canon 70-200 F4 lens is larger than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, it seems unlikely that the lens will fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_296", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I don't want anything from AmazonBasics. Find me a camera case from a different brand with the least pockets you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'AmazonBasics' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_367", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm highly interested in macro photography; does this case provide any assistance for that type of precise work?", "long_answer": "Macro photography typically necessitates a highly stable camera to capture intricate details without any blurriness. Unfortunately, this camera case lacks a tripod attachment feature, which is crucial for achieving such stability.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_368", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this camera case a suitable option for an individual who prioritizes convenience over comprehensive protection against the elements?", "long_answer": "Indeed, should convenience and effortless accessibility rank higher for you than safeguarding against water and harsh environmental conditions, then this camera case is aptly suited for your needs. It foregoes waterproof capabilities to allow for more straightforward, accessible handling of your camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_427", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is the case designed to protect and store smaller photography equipment safe during transit?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the case comes with protective features and customizable foam that make it ideal for the safe and secure storage and transportation of smaller photography equipment, such as cameras and accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_428", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the camera case provide protection for the LCD screen of the camera?", "long_answer": "The interior lid of the camera case is lined with memory foam, which serves to safeguard the camera's LCD screen against potential damage by providing cushioning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_429", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the DSLR Day Holster designed to be waterproof and protect a camera during heavy rain?", "long_answer": "The DSLR Day Holster is designed to provide protection against minor bumps and scratches while offering resistance to light moisture. However, it is not designed to be fully waterproof or provide heavy-duty protection, and should not be depended on in heavy rain conditions for safeguarding your camera.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_430", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does this backpack provide separate storage for personal items in addition to camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The backpack offers a dedicated main compartment specifically for camera gear, while also providing extra space in the top and outer pockets for carrying personal items such as snacks, a small purse, or various accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_297", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I don't want a bunch of pockets in my case, two is plenty. But I'm a Sony guy, so find me a Sony brand camera case that suits my needs.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND brand = \"Sony\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND brand = \"Sony\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Sony' AND pockets <= 2;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_369", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm concerned about the amount of time I spend packing up my equipment; can this case expedite that process?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case prioritizes efficiency. Its design facilitates quick storage of your camera as it eliminates the hassle of detaching external accessories such as tripods. This allows you to stow your equipment rapidly without skipping a beat.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_431", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the bag large enough to accommodate a DSLR camera with an attached battery grip?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to be spacious enough to carry DSLR cameras, and customer feedback confirms that it can indeed hold a DSLR camera with a battery grip attached without issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_298", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I seriously hate dealing with pockets, but I need a secure case. Get me the camera case without any pockets that uses either a zipper or lock.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'locks');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_432", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the shoulder strap of the bag designed to remain comfortable when worn for extended periods?", "long_answer": "The shoulder strap that comes with the bag is crafted with the intention of facilitating comfortable and easy transport, particularly for extended use, which is supported by user feedback indicating general comfort.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_433", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "How would you rate the build and durability of the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack based on user satisfaction?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack is generally perceived as a robust and durable product, with a majority of users expressing contentment regarding its build quality.", "short_answer": "well-made and durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_370", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the camera case space-efficient for use as carry-on luggage on airplanes?", "long_answer": "Considering that airline carry-on luggage typically comes with size limitations, this camera case may not be the most space-saving choice owing to its specialized tripod pocket, which could occupy extra room, possibly complicating the fit into compact overhead bins or under-seat areas.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket fail to meet the requirements for a compact storage solution when space is a premium, such as for photographers needing to adhere to strict travel luggage constraints.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_434", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the bag suitable for discreet travel in urban settings without drawing attention?", "long_answer": "The size of the bag makes it more noticeable and potentially less suitable for individuals who prefer to travel inconspicuously in urban areas where blending in is preferable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_371", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "For street photography, accessing my camera quickly is crucial. Does this camera case facilitate that requirement?", "long_answer": "A camera case featuring backpack-style straps offers comfort and is excellent for toting your equipment over long durations, but it might not be the best option for street photography, where quick and easy camera retrieval is essential. Sling bags or other designs that allow for faster and more convenient access are more appropriate for the spontaneity required in street photography.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps do not have a function of instant accessibility compared to certain sling bags which can provide faster access to equipment for those who need to switch gear quickly and frequently.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_299", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I don't like carrying too much stuff. Give me the simplest USA Gear camera case with less than two pockets.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND pockets < 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND pockets < 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_300", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm not a fan of too many pockets and I love Altura Photo. Can you recommend a camera case from them with one pocket or less?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND pockets <= 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_372", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I currently use it for my Nikon D5000 with a battery grip, which is roughly the same size as your Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_435", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Does the camera case remain upright when the camera is not inside?", "long_answer": "Yes, user remarks indicate that the rigidity of the camera case allows it to maintain its shape and remain upright even when the camera is removed.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_436", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the Canon camera bag made from materials that provide water resistance?", "long_answer": "The Canon camera bag is made from durable nylon with water-repellent properties, offering protection for your camera gear against moisture.", "short_answer": "water-repellent", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_301", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I can't drop more than 50 on a case right now, and I ain't planning no underwater photo shoot.  Arrange for me the least expensive case without water resistance, would ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_373", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this case fit my Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. This case is designed to fit a Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the dimensions of your Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR lens are similar, so it should work.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_437", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG emit any unpleasant odors?", "long_answer": "There are no reports or customer reviews indicating that the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG emits any unpleasant odors; it is considered well-crafted and free from such issues.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_374", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can I use this bag for my Canon 1100D?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits perfectly in this bag. Your Canon 1100D has similar dimensions so it should fit as well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon 1100D has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon 1100D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_375", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Does the camera case shield against discoloration that may result from various environmental elements?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is crafted from material that is not only durable but also impervious to color fading caused by environmental elements like ultraviolet light and various chemicals, preserving the case's visual charm for the long haul.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with material described as EVA feature a degree of chemical resistance, which safeguards the case from deteriorating when it comes into contact with common chemicals, oils, and UV exposure.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "eva", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_376", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is the camera case crafted for photographers who require swift location changes?", "long_answer": "Certainly, our camera cases are designed for photographers who are on the move and require the ability to swiftly transition between venues. The lack of a tripod attachment feature ensures a seamless experience, facilitating rapid packing and unpacking of your camera equipment without additional procedures.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_302", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm a fan of AmazonBasics, but I don't want a case with stacks of pockets. Give me their product with no more than the average number of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'AmazonBasics' AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases WHERE brand = 'AmazonBasics');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_438", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG large enough to accommodate a Canon Rebel T3i with both a kit lens and an extra lens?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG is specifically designed to contain one or two camera bodies as well as one or two lenses, ensuring that a Canon Rebel T3i equipped with a kit lens and an additional lens would indeed fit snugly and securely within the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_439", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the holster compatible with a camera that has a tripod mount attached?", "long_answer": "The holster is most compatible with cameras without any additional accessories, such as a tripod mount. Customers have reported issues with the case closing properly when a tripod mount is attached.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_303", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm always losing stuff in those big pouch pockets. I need a case that closes with a zipper or a drawstring and I don't care if it's not water resistant. Now find me the one with the least amount of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'drawstring') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_440", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the camera case offer water resistance?", "long_answer": "The camera case is crafted from durable nylon but does not tout water resistance capabilities, suggesting it may not offer adequate protection in wet conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_441", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the bag designed to allow for rapid retrieval of contents?", "long_answer": "The bag features a buckle closure system that facilitates easy and quick access to equipment, making it convenient for situations where speed is of the essence. Additionally, it offers an optional zip-up feature to secure the contents while traveling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_304", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm not looking to splurge and don't need any of that high-tech waterproof stuff. Just give me the product id for your cheapest, non-water resistant camera case that's below average price.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' \nORDER BY price \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_305", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm interested in Ape Case. What's the cheapest product from this brand for camera cases?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Ape Case' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_306", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm not about to risk water damage on my camera. Do you stock any waterproof cases? Show me the first one you've got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_442", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the backpack carry personal items in addition to camera gear, and is it spacious enough for a jacket?", "long_answer": "The backpack is specifically designed to hold camera gear; however, it does have a top compartment and mesh pockets that can be used to store small personal items. Despite this, the bag may not accommodate larger items like a jacket with comfort.", "short_answer": "small personal items", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_307", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I gotta carry a lot of stuff around and I need a water-resistant camera case with a drawstring closure. Can you find me one with the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND closure_type = 'drawstring' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_308", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I can't stand the color mica. Still, I need a camera case under 100 dollars. What's the first one you got without that damned color?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" AND price <= 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" AND price <= 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND color != 'mica' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_377", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Will this case fit a Canon T31 with a 55mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case should fit. I have a Canon L-series 100-400 and it fits perfectly. Your camera should be similar in size, so it should work fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon T31 with 55mm lens has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon T31 with 55mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "search_qa_309", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm only interested in OP/TECH USA and Case Logic brands, and I don't want any pesky pockets. Which is the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Case Logic\") AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Case Logic\") AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Case Logic\") AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('OP/TECH USA', 'Case Logic') AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_443", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 backpack heavier than other similar models when empty?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 backpack is considered to be slightly heavier when compared to other models, which is attributed to its larger size and the durable materials used for enhanced protection and storage capabilities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_378", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this camera case designed for quick retrieval of my compact travel tripod while hiking?", "long_answer": "Certainly, as long as your collapsible travel tripod conforms to a standard shape and size, it ought to slide into the dedicated tripod pocket of your camera case, ensuring swift accessibility for your outdoor expeditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket do not have a function of accommodating very large or unusually shaped tripods that require more space or alternative attachment mechanisms than the pocket provides.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_310", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I don't want black and I've had enough of this \"USA Gear\" brand. Find me a camera case that is a different color, different brand and has the least number of pockets, alright?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'black' AND brand != 'USA Gear' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_311", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Look, I've only got 30 dollars to spare, and I only buy from USA Gear or AmazonBasics. What's the cheapest camera case you have from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"AmazonBasics\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"AmazonBasics\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'AmazonBasics') AND price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_312", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I only got a tenner left for this. Get me the cheapest drawstring camera case you have in stock.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type = 'drawstring' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_379", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this pouch fit my Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Nikon D90 which is similar in size to your camera and it fits well in this pouch.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_444", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the bag remain stable during activities such as hiking or biking?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with a waist strap to enhance security and stability, which effectively limits excess movement. According to customer feedback, the bag typically maintains its position during dynamic activities like hiking and biking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_313", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I've had it with Ape Case, they just don't cut it. I need a camera case with locks, nothing fancy, just the one with the least number of pockets. Can you help me out?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand <> 'Ape Case' AND closure_type = 'locks' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_445", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the main compartment of the camera bag tall enough to accommodate a DSLR with an attached battery grip?", "long_answer": "The main compartment of this camera bag is not adequately tall to house a DSLR with an attached battery grip. It is primarily crafted to fit the camera body accompanied by a standard lens.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_446", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the bright orange color of the bag's interior facilitate the location of items inside it?", "long_answer": "The bright orange color of the bag's interior is beneficial as it helps customers find equipment and small accessories more easily, particularly in situations where there is insufficient lighting.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_447", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this backpack suitable for carrying items other than photography gear?", "long_answer": "This backpack offers versatility and is not exclusively for photography gear; the top compartment and pockets can be used to carry a variety of other items as noted by customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_448", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the bag designed for comfortable use during nature photography and hikes while providing quick access to gear?", "long_answer": "Customers commonly report that the bag is appropriate for nature photography due to its comfort while hiking as well as the feature that allows quick access to photographic gear without the need to place the bag on the ground.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_314", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I don't like fussing with locks or buttons, so I only want a green camera case with either a zipper or velcro closure. Oh, and I want the most affordable option, alright?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'velcro') AND color = 'green' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_380", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will this case accommodate my Nikon D80 with an MB80 Grip? ", "long_answer": "Yes. I have a Nikon D5000 with battery grip and it fits perfectly. Your camera is similar size with mine so it should fit in the case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_381", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Does this camera case allow for swift retrieval of my camera in a range of outdoor settings?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case's belt loop facilitates rapid access to your camera, ideal for outdoor settings where quickly taking a photo is necessary. Nonetheless, should your outdoor excursions entail more rigorous demands, consider a case with a greater variety of carrying choices for enhanced access and security in more challenging conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop fail to meet the requirements for those who need to carry their camera case in a rugged or challenging environment that would benefit from alternative carrying methods.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_449", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does the camera bag provide protection against bumps and minor drops for cameras and lenses?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is designed with full padding and reinforcement, which provides a level of protection suitable for normal handling, standard bumps, and minor drops, although it may not safeguard against serious impacts or accidents.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_382", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this case assist in preventing missed vital shots during high-speed events?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case comes equipped with a specialized tripod pocket, designed for photographers who must be swift to action, such as during event photography. Having quick access to and the capability to promptly deploy your tripod could mean the difference between seizing a crucial shot or failing to capture it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket typically mean that the product is designed with the needs of photographers in mind who require quick and easy access to their tripods for capturing stable and precise shots across various photography genres.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_383", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon T3i with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I've been able to store my Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens in it with no problems, and your T3i with a 300mm lens should be a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon T3i with 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon T3i with 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_384", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I frequently hike with my camera in tow; is this case durable enough to handle persistent rubbing against rugged surfaces, such as rocks or branches?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is crafted from nylon, a material selected for its durability against constant rubbing against coarse surfaces. Its abrasion resistance ensures that it can withstand the challenges of trekking and encounters with rough elements like rocks or branches.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_315", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I'm only interested in Sony or Lowepro cases, and I don't need more than two pockets. What's the cheapest one you got that meets my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Lowepro\") AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Lowepro\") AND pockets <= 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Lowepro\") AND pockets <= 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'Lowepro') AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_450", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the case designed to hold USB cables and small accessories in addition to a camera?", "long_answer": "Customers have reported that they can store USB cables and small accessories in the case's pocket, however, the available space depends on the size of the camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_451", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the Lowepro Passport Sling bag acceptable as a personal item on an airplane?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Passport Sling bag is suitable for use as a personal item when flying, as its compact design allows it to be stowed under the seat in front of you, and customers have reported using it successfully in this capacity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_385", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is this camera case capable of withstanding severe outdoor conditions while maintaining its aesthetic integrity?", "long_answer": "Although canvas is quite resilient to outdoor environments, it is not completely resistant to the weather. Extended exposure may cause the material to fade and show signs of wear. Therefore, if maintaining the appearance of the case is important to you, anticipate the necessity for more regular maintenance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with canvas material lack the capability to maintain a pristine appearance over long periods; they may fade in color and show wear more visibly, presenting a challenge in maintenance to retain both appearance and function.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "canvas", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_386", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can I swiftly retrieve my camera from this case to take impromptu photos?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the absence of a tripod mount on this case allows for rapid access to your camera, rendering it perfect for effortlessly snapping those unanticipated, candid moments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_387", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is it possible for me to readily modify the case to accommodate the various camera models I possess?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is crafted from a material that provides outstanding flexibility, accommodating a range of camera sizes to ensure a snug and secure fit for your photography equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_388", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for formal occasions or professional environments?", "long_answer": "Although this camera case is sturdily made with a durable nylon exterior, its aesthetic lends itself more to everyday or functional purposes rather than in formal or professional environments where the refined appearance of a leather case might be more suitable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_452", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the bag come with a compartment specifically designed for carrying a tripod?", "long_answer": "The bag comes equipped with a dedicated tripod storage system featuring a hidden foldout holder and a quick-release buckle with a strap, which users have found to be effective for securing and carrying compact tripods or monopods on the side of the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_453", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this bag suitable for carrying multiple professional photography equipment items like camera bodies, lenses, and accessories?", "long_answer": "Yes, the bag is specifically designed to hold professional photography equipment securely, providing enough space for multiple camera bodies, lenses, a flash unit, and additional photography accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_454", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can this pouch accommodate professional DSLR cameras?", "long_answer": "The pouch is designed to be suitable for a variety of cameras, which includes being able to fit professional DSLR cameras, given the camera and attached lens are within the size constraints of the pouch.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_455", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera compartment of the sling large enough to house bigger lenses, such as a 70-300mm Nikon lens?", "long_answer": "The sling's camera compartment is tailored to fit most standard SLR bodies and lenses. Reports from customers show that lenses up to a 70-300mm Nikon lens can be accommodated and are protected provided the lens isn't excessively long.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_456", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the Lowepro Passport Sling bag an ideal choice for carrying camera gear in crowded tourist attractions?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Passport Sling bag is tailored for comfortable carrying and quick access to camera equipment, which makes it a good fit for tourist spots. Yet, its suitability may vary as some users find the bag somewhat bulky for very crowded areas, so the amount of gear you plan to carry and your preference for the bag's size should be taken into account.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_389", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can a Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens fit in this backpack?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, it won't fit. I've tried it with a Canon 70D with a 70-250 lens and it was quite snug. The Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens is larger, so it won't fit in this backpack.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_316", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I don't want anything red and only like \"USA Gear\" and \"Case Logic\". Find me the cheapest camera case from these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"red\" AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Case Logic\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"red\" AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Case Logic\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"red\" AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Case Logic\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'Case Logic') \nAND color != 'red' \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_390", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for a photographer who carries a full-sized professional tripod while traveling?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, this camera case isn't suitable for photographers who travel with a full-sized professional tripod, as the tripod compartment isn't large enough to accommodate bigger models, which may result in the need to carry an additional bag for the tripod.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod compartment cannot be used for conveniently storing larger professional tripods that exceed the size limitations of the pocket, which could lead to inconvenience or the need for additional carrying solutions for such equipment.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_457", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the bag designed to be waterproof and dustproof?", "long_answer": "The bag is padded and robustly constructed; however, it lacks designated waterproof and dustproof features. The padding provides a basic level of protection, but for heightened resistance to moisture and dust, especially in more severe conditions, a specialized bag is advisable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_317", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Listen, I got only 30 dollars and don't want my camera case to surrender to the first raindrop. Find me the cheapest water-resistant case you have, would ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_458", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is this holster suitable for travelers who need to protect their camera without carrying a larger bag?", "long_answer": "This holster is considered ideal for travel by many customers, particularly for those looking to safeguard their camera while avoiding the bulkiness of a larger bag. Its compact size makes it conducive for travelers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_391", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this case suitable for my camera when I primarily engage in long-exposure photography that necessitates the use of a tripod?", "long_answer": "In long-exposure photography that often necessitates steady camera support, this case may not be the ideal choice due to the lack of a built-in tripod mounting system. Consequently, you'll need to remove your camera from the case and mount it onto the tripod independently.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_318", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm really not in the mood for hassling with complicated closures. Just find me the cheapest case that either has a zipper or velcro, would ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"zipper\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"zipper\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"zipper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'velcro') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_392", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "When shooting in snowy conditions, does this case offer sufficient protection for my equipment?", "long_answer": "Although the case is built to function in arid conditions, the presence of snow could lead to moisture seeping in, posing a risk to your equipment. As this camera case isn't tailored for water resistance, it's important to bear in mind the possibility of exposure to melting snow. Opting for a waterproof or weather-resistant case would be more prudent for ensuring full protection in snowy settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_393", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is it simple for me to adapt the case to accommodate the various camera models I possess?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is crafted from a material renowned for its outstanding flexibility, which allows it to accommodate different camera sizes, guaranteeing a snug and secure fit for your equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_459", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Do the case's latches have any operational difficulties due to their design?", "long_answer": "The case features latches that are intentionally created to ensure a secure closure. Consequently, they may necessitate additional force for their operation. A subset of customers have noted that the latches can be somewhat difficult to handle, but they also recognize and value the added security these latches bring to the case's design.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_394", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "If I bring along this case on a snorkeling excursion, will it keep my camera dry?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the case will protect your camera from water while snorkeling, provided that you do not exceed the advised depth boundaries. However, it should be noted that while the case provides waterproofing capabilities, it may not be appropriate for prolonged deep-sea dives without a suitable IP rating or a design that withstands high pressure.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof protection cannot be used for extended deep-sea diving if they don't have a high enough IP rating or are not designed to withstand high pressure at depth.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_395", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "At times, I utilize potent cleaning solutions; might these impact the camera case I'm considering purchasing?", "long_answer": "Certainly, when selecting a camera case constructed of neoprene, it is crucial to steer clear of prolonged contact with potent cleaning agents. Although neoprene possesses a degree of chemical resilience, harsh solvents can gradually deteriorate the fabric, compromising the case's protective function for your camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with neoprene material are not recommended for long-term exposure to oils, solvents, and certain harsh chemicals, despite their chemical resistance, as over time these substances can still degrade the quality and effectiveness of the material.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "neoprene", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_460", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the main compartment of the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack accommodate a DSLR camera with a standard zoom lens?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack features an adjustable main compartment with padded dividers, which is specifically designed to securely fit a DSLR camera along with a standard zoom lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_461", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Can this bag accommodate both an iPad and camera equipment simultaneously?", "long_answer": "Customers have indeed used this bag to store both an iPad and camera equipment. However, whether all items fit comfortably can vary based on the specific dimensions of the iPad and the amount and size of camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_396", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fit in this case?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use this case with my Nikon D5000 with a battery grip which is similar in size to your Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_397", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for me if my goal is to reduce movement and sound when photographing in tranquil settings?", "long_answer": "In silent settings where minimizing motion and sound is vital, a camera case designed for hand-carrying or secure attachment close to the body, without dangling straps, is preferable to those with a shoulder strap that may swing and generate noise.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not recommended for situations where stealth is necessary, as the motion of a dangling strap might draw unwanted attention or noise, unlike a case that is carried by a handle or secured closer to the body.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_398", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can this case hold a Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid it would not. The Nikon D3500 fits in this case, and your Canon 70-200 F4 lens is larger than this camera, so it would not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_319", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I ain't got time for a case that disintegrates at the first drop of rain or doesn't have enough pockets for my stuff. I also want either a black or purple one. Which one checks all the boxes and has the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"purple\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"purple\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"purple\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' \nAND (color = 'black' OR color = 'purple')\nORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_399", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Will this camera case protect my equipment during photography outings if I get caught in the rain?", "long_answer": "The camera case you're evaluating prioritizes being lightweight and compact, thereby making it an excellent choice for use in dry settings. It is functional when not subjected to moisture, but it might not offer complete protection in rainy conditions. If you often find yourself in wet situations, it would be prudent to seek a case that features waterproof capabilities.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_462", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is the foam inside the case customizable?", "long_answer": "The case includes a Pick N'Pluck foam system that enables users to customize and create shapes according to the items they want to secure, allowing for better protection and organization of contents.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_463", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack come with a designated compartment for carrying a water bottle?", "long_answer": "The backpack features a side pocket intended to serve as a dedicated compartment for a water bottle or similar objects, allowing easy and convenient access to hydration or storage for miscellaneous items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_400", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can I hike with this camera case without it becoming an obstruction?", "long_answer": "Undoubtedly, the backpack straps on the camera case are perfect for hikers, enabling you to securely transport your photography gear on your back, allowing for effortless navigation across diverse terrains without the case becoming a hindrance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are known for facilitating hands-free operation, thus enabling photographers to move more freely and focus on capturing images without the encumbrance of holding onto their case.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_464", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the main compartment of the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack accommodate both a DSLR camera and extra lenses?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack's main compartment is adjustable and padded, specifically designed to securely hold a DSLR camera with an attached standard zoom lens. It also provides sufficient space to store additional lenses or flash units, catering to the needs of photography enthusiasts and professionals who require extra gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_320", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I've got a thing for orange. Give me the product id of an orange camera case, quick.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'orange' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_465", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this camera case considered durable and protective for travel when placed inside luggage?", "long_answer": "The case is perceived by customers as durable, providing adequate protection for the camera when stored within luggage for travel purposes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_401", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Will this backpack accommodate my Canon t5i with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens, which has similar dimensions as your Canon t5i with a 300mm lens, and it fits fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_466", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this bag practical for photographers who frequently switch lenses?", "long_answer": "The bag is engineered with ease of access in mind, and while it generally facilitates changing lenses, one user highlighted the benefit of using an additional external case for the most commonly utilized lens to improve the convenience of lens exchange.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_321", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm trying to save cash here and also add some color to my gear. Got any camera cases under 10 dollars in either red or yellow?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"red\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"red\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND (color = 'red' OR color = 'yellow');"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_402", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Would this case fit a Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens? ", "long_answer": "No, it's not likely. I have a Nikon D90 and it fits just right. Considering that your Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens is bigger, it probably won't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Nikon D90, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "search_qa_322", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I don't like bulky stuff. Find me a lightweight camera case with one pocket maximum, and either a zipper or drawstring. Make it the cheapest one you have, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 \nAND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') \nORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_467", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is there a dedicated tripod compartment included with the bag?", "long_answer": "The backpack does indeed include a feature specifically designed for carrying a tripod, which permits the tripod to be attached externally.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_323", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I don't want any Altura Photo stuff. Find me the cheapest case from any other brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Altura Photo' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_468", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "What is the durability of the bag concerning wear and tear?", "long_answer": "The bag is constructed from high-quality, heavy-gauge (840D) nylon, which is chosen for its ability to endure rough handling and provide long-term durability. User feedback generally supports that the bag holds up well against wear and tear.", "short_answer": "durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_469", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG Camera Bag suitable for carrying laptops or tablets?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG Camera Bag is primarily designed for storing and transporting camera bodies, lenses, and small photography accessories, and it is not intended to hold laptops or tablets.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_470", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 backpack appropriate for individuals with minimal camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 backpack is tailored toward professionals and serious photography enthusiasts who require ample space and robust protection for a considerable amount of gear, which can be excessive for individuals with only a modest amount of camera equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_403", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can this case accommodate the 50-500 Sigma lenses?", "long_answer": "Sure, it should be fine. I've tried it with a Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the size is quite similar to the 50-500 Sigma lenses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_471", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the case designed to accommodate a travel tripod?", "long_answer": "This case is not intended for storing larger equipment such as a typical travel tripod; however, it is suitable for smaller items and related equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_404", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this bag fit my Pentax K-2 with a Sigma 18-125 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits perfectly. The size of your Pentax K-2 with a Sigma 18-125 lens is similar to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_405", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can I fit a Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens into this bag?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, no. This bag is designed to fit a Nikon D3500, and a Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens is larger in size. Therefore, it would not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_324", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Green just ain't my color and I gotta have something that's water resistant. Just give me your cheapest non-green, water resistant camera case.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'green' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_472", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is the Pelican 1200 Case large enough to accommodate a GoPro and multiple accessories?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case is suitable for a GoPro and a few accessories, providing adequate space without causing a tight fit. However, if you possess a vast collection of GoPro accessories, choosing a larger case is advisable to ensure comfortable storage and to prevent overcrowding.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_473", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is the Pelican case both waterproof and airtight?", "long_answer": "Pelican cases are engineered to be watertight and airtight, utilizing a tongue and groove fit along with a polymer o-ring to achieve this. Additionally, they come with an Automatic Pressure Equalization Valve that balances air pressure inside the case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_406", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is this case suitable for a wedding photographer to carry around?", "long_answer": "Given that weddings typically demand a professional demeanor, employing a camera case with backpack straps might clash with the formal attire expected, since it can appear overly informal for these occasions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are not recommended for situations that demand rapid gear changes or a professional appearance that aligns with formal event dress codes, as a backpack might be viewed as too casual or cumbersome in such environments.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_474", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is there a warranty or return policy for this backpack in case of issues?", "long_answer": "Lowepro provides customer service and return policies that you can avail of if you encounter any problems with the backpack. Depending on the circumstance, you can contact the retailer from whom you purchased the backpack or get in touch with Lowepro directly for support.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_325", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm not looking for anything fancy, just a simple camera case with no more than two pockets. Oh, and it has to be in mica or yellow. What's the cheapest you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND color IN (\"mica\", \"yellow\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND color IN (\"mica\", \"yellow\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND color IN (\"mica\", \"yellow\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND (color = 'mica' OR color = 'yellow') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_475", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the Fastpack 200 be worn comfortably on one shoulder?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 features contoured shoulder straps that are specifically designed to distribute weight evenly when worn with both straps. However, users do have the ability to wear the bag over one shoulder for brief periods if they desire convenience.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_407", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Would you recommend this case for safeguarding professional photography gear on high-risk field assignments?", "long_answer": "For high-risk field assignments where the security of professional photography equipment is paramount, I would advise against using a camera case with a shoulder strap. Such cases enable movement, potentially offering insufficient protection against the impacts or drops that might happen. A hard case designed for full immobilization would be better suited for these situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap cannot be used for circumstances where a rigid case is necessary due to extreme conditions or when full immobility of the equipment is required, as the mobility afforded by straps may not provide sufficient protection in these scenarios.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_476", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is a carrying strap included with this camera case?", "long_answer": "The camera case comes with a shoulder strap and also includes a belt loop, offering two convenient options for carrying.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_477", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can the internal compartments of the bag be reconfigured to fit various gear sizes?", "long_answer": "The bag comes equipped with padded, reinforced compartments that include Velcro dividers. These dividers enable the user to alter the sizes of the compartments, ensuring a custom fit for different pieces of gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_326", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I need a camera case with a lock or drawstring from Canon or OP/TECH USA. No high-end stuff though, just show me the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"OP/TECH USA\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"OP/TECH USA\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'Canon' OR brand = 'OP/TECH USA') AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_408", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Would you recommend this case for protecting professional photography gear during high-risk field operations?", "long_answer": "In high-risk field assignments where the safety of professional photography gear is paramount, I would advise against using a camera case with a shoulder strap. Such cases permit motion, potentially offering insufficient protection from impacts or drops that may happen. A sturdy case engineered for total immobilization would be preferable in these scenarios.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap cannot be used for circumstances where a rigid case is necessary due to extreme conditions or when full immobility of the equipment is required, as the mobility afforded by straps may not provide sufficient protection in these scenarios.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_478", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack suitable as a carry-on bag for air travel?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is considered by numerous customers to be well-suited for use as a carry-on during air travel. Its compact dimensions ensure it fits within the size restrictions for carry-on luggage, while offering ample space to accommodate essential camera equipment and personal belongings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_327", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm not a fan of USA Gear and I don't need a case with a ton of pockets. Find me the cheapest camera case you got that isn't from USA Gear and has two or fewer pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND pockets <= 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND pockets <= 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'USA Gear' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_409", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon Rebel SL1?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The case is designed for the Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon Rebel SL1 is similar in size, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon Rebel SL1 has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon Rebel SL1 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_410", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I like creating time-lapse videos; would this case benefit my workflow?", "long_answer": "In time-lapse photography, maintaining your camera's absolute stillness for prolonged durations is essential, often requiring the use of a tripod. As this camera case lacks a tripod mount, it might not be the best option for time-lapse endeavors where stability is paramount.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_479", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the sling strap of the bag equally comfortable for both left and right-handed users when rotated to the front?", "long_answer": "The sling strap is intended to be worn over either shoulder. However, some users who wear the strap over the left shoulder report discomfort when the bag is rotated to the front, indicating a potential preference in the design for right-handed users.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_411", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this camera case suitable to carry my camera and multiple heavy lenses when I need to transport them?", "long_answer": "Should you intend to transport several heavy lenses and accessories, it might be wise to opt for a camera case featuring sturdier carrying options. Cases equipped with a belt loop often have a restricted load capacity, potentially inadequate for your requirements.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop are not suitable for individuals who prefer to carry multiple heavy lenses and accessories due to the limited load capacity that a single belt loop may offer.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_328", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm into bright colors and quality, show me the first orange camera case you have from either Sony or Case Logic.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" AND brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Case Logic\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" AND brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Case Logic\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color='orange' AND (brand='Sony' OR brand='Case Logic') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_329", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I ain't a big fan of OP/TECH USA and don't want a bunch of pockets. Get me the least expensive camera case without a ton of storage space.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND pockets <= 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND pockets <= 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'OP/TECH USA' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_480", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack remain comfortable when it is at full capacity?", "long_answer": "The backpack is considered generally comfortable due to its padded straps and ergonomic design, but a few users have indicated that the waist belt might require additional support for heavy loads. It provides the best comfort when it's not overloaded.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_330", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I ain't a fan of yellow and I don't need more than two pockets. Give me your cheapest case that fits these terms, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" AND pockets <= 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" AND pockets <= 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'yellow' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_412", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can I swiftly switch my camera from being carried to mounted on a tripod for landscape photography if I use this case while hiking?", "long_answer": "The lack of a tripod attachment on this camera case precludes the possibility of swiftly shifting to a mounted setup. Consider seeking a case featuring a built-in tripod mount if rapid transitions are critical for your outdoor photography endeavors.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_331", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I like to travel light and I've got this thing for yellow. Could you find me a camera case that's yellow with less than 2 pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND pockets < 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND pockets < 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'yellow' AND pockets < 2;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_481", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the neoprene material of the Soft Pouch offer sufficient protection without adding significant bulkiness?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch utilizes neoprene material which offers ample cushioning to protect your items, ensuring it safeguards effectively while maintaining a slim and travel-friendly profile.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_482", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the camera bag have a compartment that can accommodate a standard-sized camera manual or a small book?", "long_answer": "The camera bag contains multiple compartments intended for camera gear and smaller accessories. However, the side pockets may not be sufficiently deep to hold a standard-sized camera manual or a small book according to reports from some users.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_483", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can this backpack be adjusted to fit mirrorless camera systems?", "long_answer": "Yes, the backpack is designed to accommodate various camera systems, including mirrorless ones. It has adjustable dividers that enable customization of the interior space to securely fit the camera body and lenses specific to mirrorless systems.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_332", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I can't decide between Pelican and Case Logic. Just give me the cheapest camera case from either one.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Case Logic\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Case Logic\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Case Logic\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Pelican', 'Case Logic') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_413", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm somewhat prone to clumsiness and concerned about tearing the case. Is this particular one sturdy enough to reduce that risk?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the nylon fabric used in this camera case is particularly appreciated for its tear-resistant properties. Such durability renders it an ideal option for individuals worried about damage due to inadvertent mishaps.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_333", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I don't really care if my camera case is waterproof or not, but I certainly don't want it in that ugly mica color. Find me one with the least number of pockets that meets these requirements.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color <> 'mica' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_334", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm looking for an AmazonBasics camera case, but I'm not eager to spend a fortune. Which is the least expensive one you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'AmazonBasics' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_484", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this camera case compatible with camera models that are not explicitly listed?", "long_answer": "The camera case is primarily designed for Canon PowerShot A650IS and A720IS models. Therefore, while the case might fit other cameras with similar dimensions, there is no assurance that it will be appropriate for cameras not specifically mentioned.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_335", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Help me out here. I got only 30 dollars left and I need a camera case with either a lock or a drawstring. Find me the cheapest one you guys have!", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_485", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the Case Logic SLRC-202 camera bag suitable for a Nikon D3200 with a zoom lens?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLRC-202 camera bag is designed to be compatible with most SLRs equipped with a zoom lens. Consequently, it will comfortably accommodate the Nikon D3200 in its main compartment, ensuring a good fit for your camera setup.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_336", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm not looking to swim with my camera case or anything, so no need for that water-resistant stuff. But I also don't want to break the bank. What's the cheapest camera case you got without water-resistance and no more than 100 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price <= 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price <= 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND price <= 100 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_414", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I frequently travel. Will this case provide adequate protection for my camera during rigorous transportation situations?", "long_answer": "In challenging transit environments, a camera case constructed from EVA material may not be the best option, given its lack of full rigidity. As a result, it could be prone to impacts, potentially offering less protection for your camera compared to a hard-shell case during particularly rough situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with material described as EVA do not have a function of complete rigidity, which means they might not offer the same level of protection against crushing forces as hard-shell cases do.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "eva", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_486", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the camera sling fit comfortably on individuals with a petite or smaller stature without the need for alteration?", "long_answer": "The comfort of the camera sling on those with a petite or smaller stature varies among users. While some have found it comfortable, others report that it does not fit snugly even when the strap is fully adjusted, potentially necessitating further alterations for an ideal fit.", "short_answer": "varies by person", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_415", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is this camera case a suitable choice if I need it to also function as a standalone tripod holder?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case lacks the free-standing feature essential for tripod support. Its design centers on backpack-style carry, hence it omits the sturdy external framework needed to independently support a tripod.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps lack the capability to stay upright on their own when set down due to their design focused on back wear-ability, unlike hard cases which can be free-standing.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_487", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this camera bag fit an SLR camera body with two additional lenses?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is designed to store an SLR camera body with an attached lens and has a large zippered compartment that can accommodate an extra lens or flash. Depending on the dimensions of the lenses, it may be possible to fit more than one additional lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_488", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can the shoulder strap of this bag be adjusted to accommodate various body sizes?", "long_answer": "The bag's shoulder strap is designed with a cam lock buckle that enables the length to be adjusted, ensuring a comfortable fit across a variety of body shapes and sizes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_416", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this camera case designed to protect my gear from water damage throughout a kayaking excursion?", "long_answer": "Certainly, opting for a waterproof camera case is wise for water-based activities such as kayaking because it safeguards your camera from moisture. Yet, if frequent access to your camera is necessary during the excursion, anticipate exerting additional effort whenever opening the case due to its watertight seals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof property are not suitable for situations where quick access and multiple openings of the case are necessary, as their protective seals can make them less convenient to open frequently.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_417", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm looking for an elegant camera case to give as a present—would this one be suitable?", "long_answer": "Should you be seeking a gift that radiates sophistication, pay close attention to the aesthetic of the camera case. Crafted from nylon, it tends to have a more casual and practical appearance, potentially clashing with the refined, upscale vibe you may desire for a present.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_337", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm not looking for anything fancy, just a simple purple camera case that doesn't have more than one pocket. What's my best bet here?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND color = \"purple\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND color = \"purple\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_418", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Do I need to perform routine maintenance to maintain the case in optimal condition?", "long_answer": "Indeed, choosing a camera case with waterproof features necessitates regular maintenance using water-repellent sprays to ensure it continues to offer optimal water protection over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof attributes feature maintenance requirements such as periodic treatments with water repellent sprays to maintain their high protection level against water.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_419", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does this case accommodate wildlife photography on the go where precision is vital?", "long_answer": "Wildlife photography frequently necessitates agility and accuracy to obtain crisp images of moving animals. This scenario is ideal for active pursuits, but the absence of a tripod connection may pose a drawback when a stable base is needed for exact, clear captures.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_489", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will the Fastpack 200 fit under an airplane seat?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 is crafted to have a compact design, allowing it to fit under the seats of most airplanes. However, it is recommended to verify with individual airline size restrictions to ensure compatibility.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_420", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Will this camera case protect my camera from scratches when I'm also carrying a tripod?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case features a specialized section for your tripod, aimed at safeguarding your camera equipment from possible scratches or harm that may occur from the tripod legs or knobs while in transit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket feature designs that aim to protect camera equipment from scratches or damage potentially caused by tripod legs or knobs, contributing to the overall safety of the stored gear.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_338", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm not a fan of pockets and prefer zippers or locks for my cases. What's the least expensive camera case you have that fits that description?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'locks') AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_490", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is it possible to insert the DSLR Day Holster into a larger non-camera bag for extra protection during travel?", "long_answer": "Yes, the DSLR Day Holster is designed to fit within a larger non-camera bag in order to provide extra protection for its contents while traveling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_491", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the bag likely to become obstructive in crowded areas when filled with gear?", "long_answer": "The bag may become cumbersome in crowded spaces as it tends to protrude outwardly when packed, which could be potentially inconvenient for navigating through busy city settings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_421", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Could the camera case become burdensome if I tote it around during prolonged journeys?", "long_answer": "No, the camera case will not be too heavy because it is crafted from nylon, known for its lightweight design. This is especially advantageous for photographers who frequently travel and must bear their gear for extended durations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_492", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the neoprene pouch provide the same level of protection as a hard case for preventing camera damage from drops?", "long_answer": "The neoprene pouch offers a certain degree of padding that helps protect the camera against damage from minor drops. However, it does not offer the same high level of protection against severe impacts that a hard case would provide.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_422", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case fit my canon rebel t5i with macro lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I've used this case with my Nikon D90 which is similar in size to the canon rebel t5i with macro lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the canon rebel t5i with macro lens has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the canon rebel t5i with macro lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_423", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Following the purchase of the camera case, is there any particular action required prior to its initial outdoor use?", "long_answer": "Certainly, although the camera case possesses water-resistant properties, it is advisable to apply a water repellent spray prior to its first outdoor use to ensure the highest degree of water resistance is achieved.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof attributes feature maintenance requirements such as periodic treatments with water repellent sprays to maintain their high protection level against water.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_493", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Are there designated compartments in the bag for storing memory cards and batteries?", "long_answer": "The bag includes zippered compartments located on the front and rear specifically designed for the storage of small items such as memory cards and batteries, ensuring these essential accessories can be organized and easily accessed.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_494", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Lowepro Flipside 300 capable of accommodating a pro DSLR camera with a 200mm lens attached?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 is specifically designed with the capacity to hold a professional DSLR camera with a lens attached that measures up to 80-200mm f/2.8, indicating that it will indeed comfortably fit a DSLR with a 200mm lens attached.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_495", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the shoulder strap of the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG designed for comfort during extended use?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG features a shoulder strap that is specifically designed with comfort in mind, allowing for the bag to be carried easily over extended periods. User feedback commonly indicates that the strap provides a comfortable experience for all-day use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_424", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is it possible for me to swiftly retrieve my camera from this case when a photo opportunity arises as I stroll about?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case may not be the ideal option if you require quick, one-handed access to your camera while on the go. The design, which includes backpack straps, means you have to remove the backpack to get to your gear, a process that's slower than other cases designed for easier accessibility.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps cannot be used for scenarios where a quick, one-handed operation or access is necessary such as in certain types of event photography, since taking off the backpack can be more time-consuming than simply swinging a shoulder bag around.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_496", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Lowepro Fastpack 200 bag waterproof enough to protect contents from heavy rain?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Fastpack 200 is constructed with durable, water-resistant material that provides a level of defense against moisture and light rain. However, the bag is not entirely waterproof, and therefore, in conditions of heavy rain, it is advisable to use extra protective measures to ensure the complete safety of your gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_339", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm a bit old school, don't really care about this water resistance business. But I love green. Can you find me a camera case that's green and doesn't have water resistance?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' AND water_resistance = 'no';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_497", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "{Does the Ape Case backpack have a system in place to carry and secure a tripod?}", "long_answer": "{The Ape Case backpack is indeed equipped with a strap system designed to carry a tripod safely and securely on its exterior, ensuring that the tripod is well fastened during transport.}", "short_answer": "{yes}", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_425", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this case accommodate a 70-200/2.8 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The case accommodates my Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens perfectly and the 70-200/2.8 lens is similar in size to the 18-200mm lens, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the 70-200/2.8 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the 70-200/2.8 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_426", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will this camera case enhance the comfort of transporting my gear on extended treks?", "long_answer": "Certainly, a camera case with backpack straps is engineered to evenly distribute the weight across your shoulders, improving ergonomics and comfort. This is particularly beneficial for reducing fatigue and strain during prolonged activities like extended hikes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps typically mean that the user can anticipate a high degree of ergonomics and comfort due to the even distribution of weight across the shoulders, reducing fatigue and strain during extended use.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_340", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I totally hate drawstring closure types, they're just not my style. Can you find me the most affordable non-drawstring camera case?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'drawstring' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_341", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Look, I gotta stay within budget and I've got my eye on the Altura Photo brand. Give me the cheapest camera case they have for under 30 bucks.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND price < 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_427", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Will this case accommodate a Canon T31 with a 55mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, the case should fit a Canon T31 with a 55mm lens. I have a Canon L-series 100-400, and they are similar in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon T31 with 55mm lens has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon T31 with 55mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_428", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this case accommodate my Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I placed my Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens into this case and it fits comfortably. Considering the sizes of our cameras are similar, yours should also fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_498", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is this carrying case recommended for heavy travel usage?", "long_answer": "The carrying case is casual and lightweight, designed for everyday use. If you require extensive protection due to heavy travel, it's advised to consider a more durable option as per user recommendations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_499", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the bag provide padding at the bottom for additional protection?", "long_answer": "The bottom of the bag includes padding, which is part of the comprehensive padding throughout the bag, ensuring good shock insulation and protection for the contents inside.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_500", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does this backpack meet the size requirements for airline carry-on luggage?", "long_answer": "The backpack's compact dimensions generally adhere to the carry-on size guidelines provided by most airlines, though passengers should verify with their individual airline to ensure conformity to any specific dimensions and weight limits.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_501", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the sling of this bag designed to be comfortable when carried by hand?", "long_answer": "The bag's sling is designed with the primary intention for it to be worn on the back rather than carried in hand, suggesting that comfort may not be optimized for hand carrying.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_342", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I can't lug around a case that's got more than 2 pockets, also I got only 50 dollars to spare. What's the cheapest you got that meets my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND price < 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND price < 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_502", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the bag durable and resilient against wear and tear during regular usage?", "long_answer": "The bag is generally reported to be durable by users, indicating that it withstands regular use without significant deterioration over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_503", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is it straightforward to customize the internal dividers of the carrying case for various equipment types?", "long_answer": "The internal dividers incorporated into the carrying case are designed to allow easy customization. Consequently, adjusting the configuration to accommodate different types of equipment is a straightforward process for users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_429", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this case appropriate for outdoor photography when frequent storage configuration adjustments are required?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the material is perfect for outdoor photography since it offers the required flexibility, enabling you to easily alter the storage setups according to your needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_430", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I'm organizing a photography excursion in the desert; is it possible for me to employ this case to safeguard my camera against the heat?", "long_answer": "This camera case is unsuitable for very high-temperature settings such as deserts. The neoprene fabric used in its construction may degrade when subjected to intense heat, potentially failing to provide sufficient protection for your camera in these circumstances.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with neoprene material cannot be used for high-temperature applications, as prolonged exposure to extreme heat may compromise the integrity of the neoprene, even though it provides some insulation.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "neoprene", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_343", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I've had some bad experiences with zipper closures and I only trust Canon and Pelican. What's the first camera case you can offer me without a zipper?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Pelican\") AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Pelican\") AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Canon', 'Pelican') AND closure_type != 'zipper' ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_344", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm into \"USA Gear\" and \"Case Logic\" brands, but don't have more than 30 dollars to spare. Tell me the first product from these brands that I can afford.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Case Logic\") AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Case Logic\") AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'Case Logic') AND price <= 30 ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_431", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this case be able to hold a Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens?", "long_answer": "It's unlikely. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it takes up the entire space in the case. If your camera with a long lens is larger in size, it wouldn't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_432", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "My camera gear occasionally suffers bumps and jostles during transport. Will this case provide adequate protection under those circumstances?", "long_answer": "The use of nylon in crafting this camera case renders it perfect for such situations. Its high abrasion resistance allows it to withstand some of the impact and harsh handling during transportation, which aids in protecting your camera gear from possible harm.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_433", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does this camera case possess a luxurious appearance that sets it apart?", "long_answer": "Considering the camera case is crafted from nylon, it might not exude the luxurious aesthetic associated with premium materials such as leather. Nylon, with its typically casual and practical look, may fall short for those in pursuit of a distinctive, upscale aesthetic.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_434", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "As a hobbyist photographer, I'm wondering whether this case might restrict me in any way during outdoor photo shoots?", "long_answer": "Although the case may be suitable for a hobbyist's general use, the lack of a tripod attachment can be restrictive during outdoor shoots where a tripod is needed. This becomes particularly pertinent as your interest in photography evolves to encompass situations where camera stability is essential for achieving the perfect shot.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_504", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this backpack suitable for individuals with a larger build?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with an adjustable harness system which enables it to accommodate individuals of different sizes, making it suitable for those who are taller or have a larger build.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_345", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm looking for a mica-colored camera case that won't cost me more than $30. Can you find me one that fits the bill?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND color = \"mica\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND color = \"mica\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'mica' AND price <= 30;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_435", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can I use this case for my Canon Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, you can. I have used this case with a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens, and your Canon Rebel T3 has a similar size to that, so it will fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_436", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a Canon Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it accommodates it quite well. The Canon Rebel T3 is approximately the same size so it should work just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_346", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm a big fan of Ape Case, but not looking to shell out more than a 100 bucks. Can you find me a suitable Ape Case camera case within my budget?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" AND price <= 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" AND price <= 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Ape Case' AND price <= 100;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_505", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack designed to fit in the overhead compartments of most regional aircraft?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack has a long and slim design that is generally perceived by users as compatible with the overhead compartments on most regional aircraft. However, it is important to verify by checking the size restrictions of the particular airline before travelling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_437", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for my professional photography shoots that involve a variety of accessories?", "long_answer": "If you utilize tools like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods in your professional photography sessions, this specific camera case might not fulfill your requirements. It does not have the capability to attach a tripod, a critical function for mounting accessories and guaranteeing proper illumination and photographic steadiness.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_347", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I ain't got time for those flimsy drawstring closures and I need something waterproof. What's the first product that meets those needs in your camera case line?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'drawstring' AND water_resistance = 'yes' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_506", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is there a neck strap included with the camera pouch that allows for carrying the camera around the neck?", "long_answer": "The camera pouch is specifically designed to accommodate the camera's neck strap. The design allows the pouch to close securely around the camera while the strap is in place, ensuring that the camera can be carried around the neck and remain protected within the pouch.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_348", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Listen, I don't have more than 100 dollars to drop on this. Just give me the first camera case you have that's under my budget.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_438", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm really interested in macro photography; does this case provide any assistance for that type of detailed work?", "long_answer": "Macro photography typically necessitates a stable camera to capture intricate details sharply, yet this camera case lacks a tripod attachment feature, which is crucial for achieving such steadiness.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_507", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag capable of fitting two SLR camera bodies as well as three lenses?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag is specifically designed with enough space to accommodate not just two SLR camera bodies but also up to three lenses, allowing for a comprehensive assortment of photography equipment to be carried in the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_349", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "This isn't rocket science. I need a camera case with a zipper or drawstring closure that comes under 10 dollars. And less of those extra pockets, please. What you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'drawstring')\nAND price < 10\nAND pockets <= 2;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_508", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the bag provide sufficient separate pouches for organizing smaller items such as batteries and chargers?", "long_answer": "Although the bag offers ample space for larger equipment, it falls short in providing a satisfactory number of separate pouches for organizing smaller accessories, as noted by some customers who demand additional compartments for items like chargers and memory cards.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_350", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I don't need a ton of pockets and I hate cases with locks. Find me the cheapest one that fits the bill.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'locks' AND pockets <= 3 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_509", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the base of the Case Logic SLRC-202 fully waterproof?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLRC-202 has a water-proof EVA base that tolerates exposure to the elements and enables the case to stand upright independently. While the base is waterproof, it is important to note that this waterproofing only applies to the base; thus, the entire bag should be shielded from heavy rain or complete submersion in water.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_439", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Will the camera case become overly burdensome to carry during my extensive travels?", "long_answer": "No, the camera case won't be overly burdensome since it's crafted from nylon, known for its lightweight design. This proves especially advantageous for photographers who frequently travel and must transport their gear for extended durations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_440", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I relish capturing images in dynamic settings. Is this case designed to accommodate such activities?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case thrives in dynamic settings. The absence of a tripod attachment in its design diminishes hindrances and facilitates swift, unencumbered access to your camera, ensuring you can snap those transient moments with little to no delay.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_510", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the backpack's interior dividers be reconfigured easily?", "long_answer": "The interior dividers of the backpack are designed to be adjustable, enabling you to rearrange the space to accommodate different sizes and shapes of items that you may need to carry.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_441", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can this bag hold my 70-200/2.8 lens? ", "long_answer": "Sure, it can. If your lens is of similar size to the Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, it should fit nicely into this bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the 70-200/2.8 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the 70-200/2.8 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_511", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack offer protection against pickpocketing on busy city streets?", "long_answer": "The backpack's design is crafted to enhance security and deter pickpocketing, making it a suitable choice for use in urban environments where such protection is desirable.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_442", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is this camera case adequate for safeguarding my gear amidst vigorous outdoor activities?", "long_answer": "When engaging in rugged outdoor activities, you may be better off choosing a camera case that offers a solid structure for enhanced protection. Cases crafted from nylon tend to have a certain degree of flexibility, potentially lacking the structural rigidity needed for these conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_512", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack designed to be water-resistant and does it come with additional protection for use in wet weather conditions?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack is crafted with water-repellent materials to provide some resistance to moisture, and it includes an extra rain cover to enhance its protection against water in various weather conditions, particularly during rain.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_351", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm not really bothered about water resistance, but I only have 10 bucks to spend. What's the cheapest camera case you have without that feature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_443", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can I instantly access my camera during fast-paced sports events coverage?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case isn't suited for circumstances where quick access to your camera is essential, like photographing rapid sports events. The case's backpack straps require you to remove the backpack completely to reach your equipment, potentially leading to missed opportunities in fast-moving shooting situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps cannot be used for scenarios where a quick, one-handed operation or access is necessary such as in certain types of event photography, since taking off the backpack can be more time-consuming than simply swinging a shoulder bag around.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_444", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens?", "long_answer": "No, unfortunately it won't. I use it for my Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses and it fits perfectly, but your setup is larger than mine, so it’s unlikely to fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_513", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the bag large enough to accommodate a camera equipped with a battery grip and additional accessories?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to accommodate a camera with a battery grip and one lens, plus a few small accessories. The space inside the bag is somewhat limited, so fitting multiple lenses or a more extensive camera setup may result in a tight fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_352", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I hate carrying around extra stuff and my favorite colors are mica and green. So, can you find me the cheapest camera case with no extra pockets and in either of these colors?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND color IN (\"mica\", \"green\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND color IN (\"mica\", \"green\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND color IN (\"mica\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND color IN ('mica', 'green') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_353", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I can't stand velcro closures on my cases - it's all zips for me. Could you find the case with the least number of pockets that isn't fastened with velcro?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'velcro' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_445", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will this backpack fit my Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens? ", "long_answer": "It may be a tight fit. I have a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens and it fits perfectly, but that's already quite a full load for the bag. Your T3i with a long lens is probably bigger so it may not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_446", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is it permissible to keep the camera case exposed to direct sunlight for prolonged durations?", "long_answer": "Considering the camera case is made of EVA material, exposing it to direct sunlight for extended periods, leading to excessive temperatures, may not be advisable. The case may deform under such circumstances, hence it is prudent to keep it in a shaded or cooler area.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with material described as EVA are not suitable for extreme temperature scenarios such as very high heat that might exceed their thermal tolerance, where the material could potentially deform.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "eva", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_514", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is there sufficient space in the camera case for both the camera and a bulky camera strap?", "long_answer": "The case is primarily designed to hold the camera snugly, with limited additional space. Accommodating a bulkier camera strap inside the case might be challenging due to the lack of extra room for bigger accessories.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_354", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm debating between Ape Case and AmazonBasics. But I don't need any of that water resistance feature. Can you find the one with the fewest pockets from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Ape Case', 'AmazonBasics') AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_515", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG accommodate DSLR camera bodies and lenses from brands other than Canon?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG has the capacity to accommodate DSLR camera bodies and lenses from a variety of brands, not solely Canon models. Compatibility with non-Canon equipment is contingent upon the dimensions of the camera and lenses; hence, it is essential to verify that the sizes of your gear align with the bag's dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_516", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can the Pelican 1200 Case with Foam accommodate a GoPro camera?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case with Foam is specifically designed to carry and protect GoPro cameras and other expensive or delicate electronic devices, offering excellent protection attributed to its sturdy construction as reported by numerous customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_447", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Will this case work for my Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8?", "long_answer": "Yes, your Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 should fit. I have a Nikon D5000 with a battery grip, which have similar size to yours.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_448", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Will this backpack fit a 50-500 Sigma lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, the backpack should fit a 50-500 Sigma lens. It fits my Canon 10-22mm lens comfortably and the sizes are comparable.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_449", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I possess a compact travel tripod; can it be accommodated in the camera case seamlessly?", "long_answer": "Certainly, a compact travel tripod should fit snugly into the camera case's specialized tripod compartment, given that it is crafted to hold tripods of this kind, contingent on them adhering to the pocket's size constraints.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod compartment cannot be used for conveniently storing larger professional tripods that exceed the size limitations of the pocket, which could lead to inconvenience or the need for additional carrying solutions for such equipment.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_517", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Are the metal buckles and clasps on this bag designed to be durable?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with solid metal buckles and clasps, which serve to improve its durability, highlighting the bag's robust construction with a focus on long-lasting use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_355", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Green is my jam! Dig out the first camera case you got in that color.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_356", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Not a big fan of too many pockets and I don't care about the water resistance fuss. Give me the simplest case you got with no more than two pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets <= 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets <= 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_357", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I have a pure disdain for Canon and the color purple. So, hit me with the first camera case you've got that isn't from Canon and isn't purple.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" AND NOT color = \"purple\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" AND NOT color = \"purple\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand <> 'Canon' AND color <> 'purple' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_518", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the case designed as a hard shell carrying case?", "long_answer": "The case does not qualify as a hard shell carrying case. Instead, it is a soft carrying case that provides a degree of protection while also ensuring the case is not heavy.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_519", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does the customer feedback suggest that the quality of the Canon bag justifies its price?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback indicates that the price of the Canon bag is considered reasonable by the majority of customers, taking into account its quality of construction and the reputation of the Canon brand.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_358", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Look, I'm a sucker for purple, and I don't want to spend more than 10 bucks. Get me the cheapest purple camera case that you have.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' AND price <= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_450", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm concerned about my camera getting damp during my hikes. Can these cases guarantee that my camera remains dry, even in a downpour?", "long_answer": "Indeed, our camera cases are designed to protect your camera from water exposure, ensuring they are highly effective at maintaining your camera's dryness, even amidst heavy rain. However, the absence of gas exchange implies that, although your gear will remain dry from external conditions, condensation may accumulate inside the case due to restricted airflow.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof features do not have the function of gas exchange, meaning that while they keep water out, air circulation is generally limited, which could potentially cause issues with condensation.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_359", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I can't stand purple and I really don't need any extra pockets. Just show me the simplest camera case you have that's any color but purple.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'purple' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_520", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Do users generally find the Double-Throw latches of the case easy to open?", "long_answer": "Users report varied experiences with the Double-Throw latches on the case, with the prevailing opinion suggesting that although the latches are secure, they can be somewhat difficult to open at first due to stiffness.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_360", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm feeling fancy and I'm only interested in OP/TECH USA or Pelican. What's the first purple camera case you got from these brands?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Pelican\") AND color = \"purple\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Pelican\") AND color = \"purple\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' AND (brand = 'OP/TECH USA' OR brand = 'Pelican') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_361", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I ain't gonna spend more than 10 dollars on a camera case and I only trust USA Gear. Can you find something like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND brand = \"USA Gear\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND brand = \"USA Gear\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand = 'USA Gear';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_451", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can this case fit a Canon Powershot SX50 HS? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. I own a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits perfectly. The size of your camera is similar to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon Powershot SX50 HS has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon Powershot SX50 HS fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_452", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does this camera case accommodate rapid location changes during shoots?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is designed to facilitate quick movements and location transitions during shoots. Its lack of a tripod attachment enhances mobility and convenience on the go, ideally suiting a dynamic shooting style.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_362", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I've got 50 dollars to spare and I don't want any Sony gear. Hunt me down a camera case with the fewest pockets possible within this price range.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND NOT brand = \"Sony\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND NOT brand = \"Sony\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND NOT brand = \"Sony\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand <> 'Sony' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY pockets LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_453", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for hiking where comfort is key, yet I still need frequent access to take photos?", "long_answer": "A camera case equipped with backpack straps is excellent for comfort during activities such as hiking. However, it may not offer the convenience required for taking frequent photos due to its limited instant accessibility, unlike sling bags, which provide quicker access to your camera.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps do not have a function of instant accessibility compared to certain sling bags which can provide faster access to equipment for those who need to switch gear quickly and frequently.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_454", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case offer adequate protection for my camera should it incidentally come into contact with objects while I'm exploring a new city?", "long_answer": "Although the camera case featuring a belt loop offers elementary protection, it isn't built to absorb major impacts. Should you have a tendency to knock into objects or expect a greater chance of collision, a sturdier case would be advisable for safeguarding your camera.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop cannot be used for securely storing the camera while engaging in activities with a high likelihood of impact, such as rock climbing or mountain biking, where a tougher case may be necessary.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_363", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I'm not planning to get my camera wet, so water resistance doesn't really matter. What's the cheapest camera case you have without that feature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_364", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I want a camera case that's red or green, and has less than 2 pockets. I ain't too flashy, got any cheap ones to recommend?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"green\") AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"green\") AND pockets < 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"green\") AND pockets < 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('red', 'green') \nAND pockets < 2 \nAND price < 20;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_455", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Will this case fit my 50-500 Sigma lenses?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. I use it for my Canon 70D with 70-250 lens. The sizes of your lenses should be similar so, it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_521", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack have dedicated compartments suitable for storing clothes?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack features a variety of compartments and pockets which are versatile enough to accommodate personal items, including a change of clothes, in addition to equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_365", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I've got a thing for camera cases in either purple or mica with as few pockets as possible. Can you find the one that fits my preference?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag` with asin: B009GYIKHQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"mica\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"mica\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"mica\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('purple', 'mica') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_456", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can I use this bag for my Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "I don't believe so. The bag is designed to accommodate a Nikon D3500, and your Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens is larger than that camera. Therefore, it's likely it won't fit properly.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_457", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can I easily remove the camera case if I'm in a densely populated area such as a concert or festival?", "long_answer": "No, if the camera case features a carrying option with a belt loop, it might not be the most suitable choice for crowded environments. Rapidly detaching the camera case from a belt might prove impractical in densely populated events, rendering it a less advisable option for professional use in these scenarios.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop are not recommended for professional use in environments where quick removal of the camera case from the belt is not practical, such as densely packed crowd events where reaching down consistently might not be feasible.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_458", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "When I have to carry my camera across regions that are subject to significant vibrations, for instance, when riding a motorcycle, would you recommend this case for that purpose?", "long_answer": "For transporting your camera through high-vibration zones like those encountered when riding a motorcycle, a camera case with a shoulder strap might not be adequate. The case's movement may not prevent vibrations from reaching the camera. A sturdier, more rigid case would be better suited to these conditions, reducing movement and safeguarding your camera against potential harm.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap cannot be used for circumstances where a rigid case is necessary due to extreme conditions or when full immobility of the equipment is required, as the mobility afforded by straps may not provide sufficient protection in these scenarios.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_522", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can the strap be adjusted to accommodate wearers of different body sizes?", "long_answer": "The sling is designed with adjustable shoulder and waist straps, allowing it to be modified for a custom, comfortable fit suitable for a range of body sizes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_459", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag accommodate my Canon 70-200 F4 lens? ", "long_answer": "I'm sorry, but this bag is designed to fit a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens which is smaller than the 70-200 F4 lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens might not fit in this bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_523", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Where is the Pelican 1200 Case manufactured?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case is manufactured in the United States, and this fact is often a source of satisfaction for consumers.", "short_answer": "USA", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_460", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "As a hobbyist photographer, I'm wondering whether this case would impose any limitations on my outdoor shoots?", "long_answer": "While the case may be suitable for a hobbyist's general use, the lack of a tripod attachment could be restrictive during outdoor photo shoots where a tripod is essential. This becomes particularly relevant if your interest in photography expands to include situations where camera stability is vital for obtaining the perfect shot.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_366", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I don't need any extra pockets and I rather fancy the color orange or black. Get me the cheapest camera case available in those colors and without pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND color IN (\"orange\", \"black\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND color IN (\"orange\", \"black\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND color IN (\"orange\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND (color = 'orange' OR color = 'black') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_367", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm not a fan of Canon and need a camera case that can withstand some water. Find me the best non-Canon option you have, pronto!", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)` with asin: B00WUIIH8W", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Canon' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_368", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I've got a thing for Lowepro and I only use cases with locks or zippers. What's the first product that matches my criteria?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack` with asin: B000YA33DC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Lowepro' AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'zipper') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_461", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case that has a premium feel to it. Would you suggest this particular model?", "long_answer": "If you're in pursuit of a camera case that exudes a 'premium touch,' the tactile feel of this nylon-made case might not align with your desires. While nylon stands out for its durability and functionality, it lacks the opulent sensation often associated with high-end materials like leather.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_369", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm looking for something vibrant. Can you find me the cheapest purple or green camera case you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"green\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"green\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('purple', 'green') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_462", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I like to snap pictures swiftly without much setup or equipment; would this camera case suit my needs?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is perfect for photographers such as yourself who prioritize speed and simplicity. With the lack of a tripod attachment, it is intentionally crafted to be light and handy for those swift, spur-of-the-moment shots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_370", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm not really into bulky cases, but I do have a thing for teal and green. Can you find me one of your camera cases with less than average pockets in those colors?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND color IN (\"teal\", \"green\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND color IN (\"teal\", \"green\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('teal', 'green') AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases);"}}
{"id": "search_qa_371", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I got a thing for purple! Can you dig up the cheapest purple camera case in your inventory?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_463", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for me when I aim to reduce movement and maintain quietness during shooting in tranquil settings?", "long_answer": "In environments where minimal movement and noise are imperative, utilizing a camera case with a handle or one that can be secured snugly against your body is preferable to having one with a shoulder strap that could swing and generate noise.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not recommended for situations where stealth is necessary, as the motion of a dangling strap might draw unwanted attention or noise, unlike a case that is carried by a handle or secured closer to the body.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_464", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Will this camera bag fit my Canon EOS 7D? ", "long_answer": "Yes, the product fits with Nikon D3500 and your Canon EOS 7D is similar size with Nikon D3500, so your camera will fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS 7D has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS 7D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_465", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this case be able to hold my Canon T31 with a 250mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. The Nikon D3500 fits in the case and your Canon T31 with 250mm lens is almost the same size, so it should fit comfortably as well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon T31 with 250mm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon T31 with 250mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_372", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I need a camera case with a zipper and it better be water-resistant too. What's the first one that comes up?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'zipper' AND water_resistance = 'yes' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_466", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does this camera case facilitate easier transportation when I frequently travel?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is designed with backpack straps to cater to those frequently on the go, offering superior comfort with its ergonomically effective weight distribution, making the transportation of your camera equipment more comfortable and convenient.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps typically mean that the user can anticipate a high degree of ergonomics and comfort due to the even distribution of weight across the shoulders, reducing fatigue and strain during extended use.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_467", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case with a premium feel; would you suggest this particular model?", "long_answer": "If you're in pursuit of a 'premium touch', the tactile sensation of this camera case might fall short of your expectations, given its nylon composition. While nylon boasts durability and practicality, it lacks the opulent feel associated with high-end materials like leather.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_468", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is this case suitable for a wedding photographer to tote around?", "long_answer": "Given that a professional appearance is typically expected at weddings, a camera case equipped with backpack straps might not conform to the stringent dress code, since it could be perceived as overly informal for such occasions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are not recommended for situations that demand rapid gear changes or a professional appearance that aligns with formal event dress codes, as a backpack might be viewed as too casual or cumbersome in such environments.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_469", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is it feasible to bring this camera case on a kayaking excursion to shield my gear from water damage?", "long_answer": "As this camera case lacks waterproof capabilities, it cannot offer an airtight seal essential for safeguarding your camera in a moist setting. Thus, it is recommended to seek a camera case equipped with waterproof properties prior to embarking on a kayaking adventure.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_524", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Are the built-in memory card pockets on this storage device secure?", "long_answer": "The built-in memory card pockets on this device may not ensure a secure fit for all memory card types, potentially resulting in the cards slipping out upon opening the compartment. Users are recommended to consider alternative secure storage solutions for their memory cards.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_470", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will my T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens fit in this backpack?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. I have a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and your camera is around the same size, so it should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_373", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I'm gonna be using this case outdoors and I need it to keep my camera dry no matter what, plus accessible with either a drawstring or zipper. Whip up the best option for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'zipper') ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_525", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera compartment of the bag large enough for a pro-sized SLR camera body?", "long_answer": "The camera compartment, with dimensions of 7.9 x 3.8 x 7.9 inches, is designed to fit most standard SLR camera bodies along with a standard lens. While many cameras will fit, there is a possibility that particularly large or professional-sized SLR bodies may have a tighter fit and might not be as easily accommodated.", "short_answer": "maybe", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_526", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "What is the durability of the bag's material?", "long_answer": "The material used for the bag is nylon, a fabric recognized for its durability. Feedback from the majority of customers indicates that the bag lives up to this expectation, showcasing its ability to withstand wear and tear over time.", "short_answer": "very durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_374", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I don't get why camera cases have zippers but aren't water resistant. Anyway, show me the cheapest zippered case that's not water resistant.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras` with asin: B005VTIMEQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'zipper' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_527", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the backpack able to reliably stand upright on its own when placed on various surfaces?", "long_answer": "The backpack may not stand upright consistently on its own, particularly if the surface is uneven or the backpack is not completely filled with items.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_471", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Will this camera case provide adequate protection for my camera during photography sessions in snowy environments?", "long_answer": "During snowy conditions, in instances where the case might encounter wet snow or thawing ice, its lack of waterproofing could pose an issue. It provides marginal protection, and the case could be compromised by moisture from the snow, potentially endangering your camera. For optimal protection of your camera in snowy environments, it is advisable to opt for a case specifically designated as waterproof.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_472", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Canon t5i with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I am using it for my Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses and it fits comfortably. Your Canon t5i with a 300mm lens appears to be around the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "search_qa_375", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm not a fan of drawstring closures but I do like the brand USA Gear. Can you find me a case from them that has a different type of closure?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR` with asin: B005J09OXU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND closure_type != 'drawstring';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_376", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I want my camera case to be a bit funky, either green or yellow. What's the cheapest one you guys have in these colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"yellow\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"yellow\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"yellow\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('green', 'yellow') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_377", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I cannot stand drawstring closures and I've only got 50 bucks to spare. Dig up the cheapest non-drawstring camera case you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'drawstring' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_473", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Will the Canon Rebel T3 fit into this bag?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Canon Rebel T3 should fit. This bag is compatible with the Nikon D3500 and the Canon Rebel T3 is roughly the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_528", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can the case be secured using a padlock?", "long_answer": "A padlock can be used to enhance the case's security. It is advised, especially for those traveling with firearms by air, to select a lock that has a longer shackle to accommodate the case's specific design requirements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_378", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I hate the color mica and I'm always around water, so I need a water-resistant camera case, but not in mica color. Also, I don't need too many pockets. Tell me, what's the simplest one you've got there?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' \nAND color != 'mica' \nORDER BY pockets ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_379", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I don't care about the water-resistance, but I do want a black or orange camera case, with the fewest pockets possible. What's your pick?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"orange\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"orange\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"orange\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('black', 'orange')\nORDER BY pockets ASC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_380", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm a bit low on cash and I need a camera case that can handle some water. Can you find me the cheapest water-resistant case you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_474", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can I use this backpack for my Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8?", "long_answer": "Yes, you can. I use this backpack for my Canon 70D with 70-250 lens and your camera setup has similar dimensions with mine. It should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_475", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for photographers who frequently need to move swiftly and transition between various locations?", "long_answer": "Indeed, it is ideal for photographers on the move. The case, crafted from lightweight materials, adapts to the photographer's requirements, ensuring effortless and swift transport while still providing ample protection.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with canvas material feature a lightweight and adaptable form factor which enhances comfort for photographers by not adding significant weight or bulkiness, thereby ensuring convenient transportation.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "canvas", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_381", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm a stickler for USA Gear. Tell me the first camera case you have from them.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR` with asin: B005J09OXU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_529", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the Velcro flap closure on the camera bag reliable for holding a camera snugly, regardless of the camera size?", "long_answer": "The Velcro flap closure is designed to provide a secure fit due to its large surface area. However, the level of security may diminish if the camera approaches the upper size limit, resulting in a tighter fit and potentially less reliable Velcro adherence.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_382", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm after a drawstring camera case but I ain't looking to pay more than the average price. Can you find me the cheapest one that ticks both boxes?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring' \nAND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) \nORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_530", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG gadget bag large enough to fit a DSLR with an attached lens and multiple additional lenses?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG gadget bag is specifically designed to allow for the storage of up to two SLR camera bodies, three lenses, and various accessories, ensuring ample space for a DSLR with an attached lens and several other lenses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_531", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Are custom engraved nameplates available for purchase for this case?", "long_answer": "Custom engraved nameplates can be obtained for this case but at an additional cost. These nameplates allow for personalization and can assist in identifying the case and its contents.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_476", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for my landscape photography excursions, during which I frequently employ a tripod to ensure stability?", "long_answer": "Given that this camera case lacks a tripod attachment, it is better suited for photographers who value mobility over the use of tripods for tasks like long exposure or time-lapse photography. Should your photography often involve a tripod, consider seeking out cases equipped with this particular function to meet your requirements.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_477", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this bag fit my Canon T31 with a 250mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it for my Nikon D3500, which is around the same size as your Canon T31 with a 250mm lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon T31 with 250mm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon T31 with 250mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_383", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Look, I only have both Sony and Case Logic on my mind right now, but I absolutely don't want any additional pockets. Find me the most affordable option from these two brands, alright?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Case Logic\") AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Case Logic\") AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Case Logic\") AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'Case Logic') AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_384", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I've nailed down my search to two brands, USA Gear and AmazonBasics, but I also want the case to be green. Sort it out and give me the cheapest option you got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"AmazonBasics\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"AmazonBasics\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'AmazonBasics') AND color = 'green' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_478", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I intend to film in the Arctic; can this case ensure my camera remains functional in the frigid temperatures?", "long_answer": "When photographing in the Arctic, it is essential to use a case offering superior thermal insulation. The nylon camera case in question is not intended for extreme temperature protection. Opting for a case made with materials specifically crafted to shield against the intense cold found in these areas would be advantageous.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_532", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the Canon SLR Gadget Bag large enough to accommodate a DSLR camera with a zoom lens attached?", "long_answer": "The Canon SLR Gadget Bag has a fully padded main compartment specifically designed to carry a DSLR camera with a zoom lens attached, along with extra space to store additional lenses and accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_479", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Does the camera case have a compartment where I can safely stow a tripod without risking damage to my lenses?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the case is equipped with a dedicated pocket designed specifically for holding a tripod. This compartment prevents the tripod from touching your lenses and other sensitive gear, thus protecting them from potential harm.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket feature designs that aim to protect camera equipment from scratches or damage potentially caused by tripod legs or knobs, contributing to the overall safety of the stored gear.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_533", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 backpack suitable for navigating through crowded urban environments?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack features a compact design, which enhances its suitability for use in crowded urban environments, allowing for easier maneuverability through tight spaces.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_534", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Fastpack 200 include dedicated tripod straps?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack lacks specific straps meant for securing a tripod, which necessitates users to either carry a compact tripod within the bag or create their own solutions to attach it externally.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_385", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I've got no more than 30 bucks to spare and I'm hooked on USA Gear. What's the camera case with the least pockets they got that I can afford?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"USA Gear\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"USA Gear\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"USA Gear\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND price <= 30 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_480", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this case hold a Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it can. I have the Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens which fits perfectly. Your Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens has similar dimensions, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_535", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this bag designed to function both as a handbag and a camera bag for daily use?", "long_answer": "This bag is indeed designed to serve dual purposes, functioning as a handbag and a camera bag for daily utility. It provides ample space for both camera equipment and personal belongings, which is further facilitated by its removable camera box feature allowing for versatile use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_481", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for someone seeking a fashionable accessory to complement their attire?", "long_answer": "The camera case prioritizes functionality, emphasizing comfort during use, but might not meet the expectations of those seeking a high-fashion look. Its design, featuring a shoulder strap, favors practicality over luxury.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap fail to meet the requirements for users seeking a fashionable accessory, as the strap's primary focus is on functionality and comfort over luxury aesthetics.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_482", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does this camera case possess a luxurious appearance that sets it apart?", "long_answer": "Considering the camera case is constructed from nylon, it may not impart the same luxurious aesthetic associated with premium materials such as leather. Nylon typically presents a casual and practical look, potentially falling short of the expectations of those in search of a distinctive, upscale appearance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_536", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack provide comfort when worn for long durations?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack is generally considered comfortable for extended use, owing to its padded sling strap that facilitates the easy rotation of the bag for swift access to equipment. This ergonomic design feature enhances comfort and convenience for the user while on the move.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_483", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Canon T31 with a 250mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. I use this for my Nikon D3500 and they are similar in size so your Canon T31 with a 250mm lens should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon T31 with 250mm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon T31 with 250mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_537", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG camera bag also suitable for storing and transporting video equipment?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag is designed with spacious and customizable compartments which can accommodate an array of video equipment, making it versatile enough for carrying both photography and video gear as needed.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_538", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does the bag include dedicated compartments for storing small accessories like batteries and cables?", "long_answer": "The bag features several additional pockets and compartments specifically designed to organize and store small accessories such as batteries and cables, making it convenient for carrying these items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_484", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Nikon D3500 and it fits the bag perfectly. Your small prime lens should have a similar size and should also fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_539", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Will the Flipside 300 backpack attract unwanted attention due to its appearance resembling a typical camera bag?", "long_answer": "The Flipside 300 backpack boasts a discreet and inconspicuous design, differentiating it from typical camera bags, which benefits photographers seeking to carry expensive gear without drawing attention.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_540", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "How effective is the Lowepro Flipside 300's design in securing camera gear against theft and accidental drops?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is designed with body-side access that places the camera gear against the wearer's back, which many customers consider to be a secure way of carrying their equipment. It offers protection against theft due to the less accessible position of the gear and also minimizes the risk of accidental drops by keeping the gear snugly in place.", "short_answer": "very effective", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_485", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can this pouch hold a Nikon v2 with a 70-300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, I believe it could. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits perfectly. The Nikon v2 with a 70-300mm lens is similar in size to mine, so it should fit as well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Nikon v2 with 70-300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Nikon v2 with 70-300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_486", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 55-250 usm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case should fit the Canon 55-250 usm lens. I have used it with my Nikon D3500 which is a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 55-250 usm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 55-250 usm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_541", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the appearance of the Lowepro Fastpack 200 backpack discreet or does it resemble a specialized camera bag?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Fastpack 200 backpack is favored for its design that mimics a standard backpack, thereby providing a discreet appearance over the look of a typical specialized camera bag.", "short_answer": "Discreet appearance", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_542", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is the Soft Pouch fully waterproof and suitable for use during heavy rainfall while hiking?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch is not entirely waterproof. It provides adequate protection against light moisture and humidity, which may suffice for hiking in conditions like mist or a light drizzle. Still, it's not recommended for use during heavy rain to prevent damage to the contents, such as a camera.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_487", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "My camera gear occasionally suffers bumps and jolts during transport. Will this case offer adequate protection under those circumstances?", "long_answer": "The selection of nylon for crafting this camera case renders it perfect for these situations. Its robust resistance to wear ensures it can mitigate some of the force and harsh handling during transport, thus protecting your camera gear from possible harm.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_543", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is this camera case priced reasonably compared to competitive brands?", "long_answer": "The consensus among users is that the camera case offers good value for its cost, indicating that it is reasonably priced when compared to similar products from other brands.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_386", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I hate messing with those button and magnet closures. Do you have a camera case that either has a drawstring or zipper? Just give me one option to start with.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('drawstring', 'zipper') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_544", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Fastpack 200 have additional storage for items other than camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 is designed with dual compartments that not only accommodate your camera equipment but also offer sufficient space for storing personal items and various accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_387", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm not looking to splash too much cash and I prefer lock closures. Which camera case under 10 dollars has a locking mechanism?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type = \"locks\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type = \"locks\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND closure_type = 'locks';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_545", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack capable of holding a variety of photography gear and a laptop?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack is specifically designed with ample interior space and adjustable, thickly padded dividers to store a range of photography equipment, making it versatile for various photography styles. Additionally, it has a dedicated compartment capable of accommodating laptops up to 16 inches, reinforcing its functionality for photographers who also need to carry a laptop.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_488", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Would this case ensure that the camera and its components remain immobile within the bag, preventing any shifting?", "long_answer": "Should immobilizing the contents within the bag be critical, a case offering less elasticity than nylon is advisable. Nylon’s pliability may permit slight movement of the camera and its parts, which contradicts the necessity of having the camera entirely stationary in the case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_546", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG Camera Bag priced competitively compared to similar camera bags?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG Camera Bag is known to be priced competitively and is seen as providing great value for its quality, especially when considering the higher cost of professional camera bags with which it may be compared.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_547", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the backpack design allow for rapid camera access without needing to remove it?", "long_answer": "The backpack features a side-entry compartment, which facilitates fast and easy access to your camera. One can swiftly swing the backpack around to the front to retrieve the camera without having to take off the backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_388", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I've got enough stuff to carry around and I'm not planning any underwater photography. What's the id of the simplest camera case you've got with only up to 2 pockets and no water resistance?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_489", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Nikon v2 with a 70-300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case should fit your Nikon v2 with a 70-300mm lens comfortably. My Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens fits perfectly, and I believe the dimensions of your Nikon are similar to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Nikon v2 with 70-300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Nikon v2 with 70-300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_548", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case classified as waterproof?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case is not classified as waterproof according to its product metadata. While it is described as durable and may provide some protection from the elements, it should not be relied upon to offer complete water resistance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_389", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm interested in a mica-colored camera case, but only if it's made by Case Logic or OP/TECH USA. Which of their products is the least expensive?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"OP/TECH USA\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"OP/TECH USA\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color='mica' AND (brand='Case Logic' OR brand='OP/TECH USA') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_390", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I can't stand velcro and I don't need any pockets. What's the first camera case you have that meets my needs?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'velcro' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_549", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack have a design that helps prevent theft?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with a body-side opening that enhances security by making it harder for potential thieves to access the zipper while the backpack is being worn.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_391", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I want a red camera case but I don't need a lot of pockets cluttering it up. Show me the one with the least number of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_550", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the AmazonBasics Sling Backpack capable of standing upright without additional support?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Sling Backpack features rubber feet that are specifically designed to enable the backpack to stand upright on its own, providing convenience and stability.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_551", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "What is the texture of the interior of the Ape Case Cubeze?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze is constructed with a nylon interior, which might feel closer to plastic than soft fabric. Despite the texture, its design prioritizes the durability and protection of the contents.", "short_answer": "nylon", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_392", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I've got a thing for green and red. Fetch me the cheapest camera case you got in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"red\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"red\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"red\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('green', 'red') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_490", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the camera case have a compartment where I can safely stow a tripod without risking damage to my lenses?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the case features a designated pocket specifically for storing a tripod. This compartment ensures the tripod remains separate from lenses and other sensitive equipment, thus protecting them from potential harm.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket feature designs that aim to protect camera equipment from scratches or damage potentially caused by tripod legs or knobs, contributing to the overall safety of the stored gear.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_552", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the case's padding effective in providing shock protection for the camera?", "long_answer": "Based on customer feedback, the case's padding is considered sufficient to safeguard the camera from bumps and minor impacts, thereby offering effective shock protection.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_553", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this bag considered durable and appropriate for everyday professional use, specifically for carrying camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The bag is frequently described by customers as sturdy and well-constructed, making it a suitable option for everyday professional use, particularly for those who need to carry a robust collection of camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_393", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm only interested in Ape Case and Canon. Show me the first product ID from either of these brands for camera cases.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Canon\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Canon\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Ape Case', 'Canon') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_394", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm not dropping more than 100 dollars on this and I need it to be green. Now, can you find me a camera case that can fit those requirements?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND color = 'green';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_554", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the case designed to be portable for travel purposes?", "long_answer": "The case is designed with portability in mind, being both compact and lightweight to facilitate ease of travel and carrying it around with minimal effort.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_491", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a Canon 55-250 usm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it works well. I use it with a Nikon D3500, and since those two are comparable in size, your Canon 55-250 usm lens should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 55-250 usm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 55-250 usm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_555", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the bag feature a compartment specifically designed for discreetly carrying small items?", "long_answer": "The bag includes a small compartment situated at its bottom, which is designed to carry small items such as battery packs and may not be immediately noticeable.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_395", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm looking for a cheap camera case from Altura Photo, and I don't need tons of pockets. Find me something below 30 dollars with the fewest pockets.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND price < 30 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND price < 30 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND price < 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND price < 30 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_396", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I don't need any fancy water resistance or anything, I just need a cheap camera case with as many pockets as possible for under 10 bucks. What do you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price < 10 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price < 10 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price < 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND price < 10 ORDER BY pockets DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_556", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the Sony LCS-CST case designed with a shoulder or neck strap for carrying?", "long_answer": "The Sony LCS-CST case is not equipped with a shoulder or neck strap. Instead, it features a belt loop and a ring meant for attaching a carabiner clip or a compatible strap, provided you already possess one.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_557", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can the main compartment of this product accommodate a DSLR camera with a zoom lens attached?", "long_answer": "The main compartment is reported by customers to adequately fit a DSLR camera with a zoom lens attached, although the capacity for additional gear is contingent on the dimensions of the zoom lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_492", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for individuals with back issues?", "long_answer": "Considering that uneven weight distribution may negatively impact those with back problems, a camera case sporting a shoulder strap may not be the best option. It might worsen pain or discomfort; therefore, it is advisable to seek cases providing alternative carrying methods to reduce back strain.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not suitable for users who may have medical conditions or pain that is exacerbated by carrying weight on one side of the body; other carrying options may be better in these cases.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_558", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack offer customizable gear organization options?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack features a customizable interior complete with Velcro dividers, allowing you to personalize the arrangement of your camera and accessories. Additionally, it provides a removable accessory pouch to further aid in organizing your gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_397", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I'm not a fan of buckles or anything too complex. Get me the details of your least bulky, zippered or drawstring type camera case.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'drawstring') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_398", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I've got a thing for red and hate lugging around too much stuff. Can you find me a red camera case with no more than one pocket?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND pockets <=1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_559", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the camera easily accessible from the bag for immediate use without needing to remove the bag?", "long_answer": "The sling design of the bag facilitates easy and rapid access to the camera, enabling photographers to capture spontaneous shots without having to take off the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_493", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can I mount my camera onto a tripod without taking it out of its case?", "long_answer": "As this specific camera case lacks a tripod attachment, it won't offer the convenience of a built-in tripod mount. If you intend to use a tripod, you'll have to take your camera out of the case first, potentially adding extra time and effort to your setup process.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_399", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm partial to \"Case Logic\" and \"OP/TECH USA\". Which is the cheapest camera case from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"OP/TECH USA\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"OP/TECH USA\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'OP/TECH USA') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_560", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the backpack water-resistant and does it come with a rain cover for additional protection?", "long_answer": "The backpack is made with water-resistant nylon material and also includes a built-in rain cover to provide extra protection in case of rainstorms.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_561", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is there more than one color option available for this case?", "long_answer": "The product listing specifies the case as being black, but some users have reported it to also have a dark green color aspect. There seems to be only one color variant available according to current information.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_562", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack come with a dedicated rain cover for all-weather protection?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is designed to be slightly water-resistant, which can handle minor rain. However, it does not include a dedicated rain cover for heavy rain or snow conditions. In such extreme weather, additional precautions like using a plastic bag are recommended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_494", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I frequently photograph events where swift lens changes are necessary; would this case accommodate that?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, this case may not be ideal for situations demanding swift, single-handed use, such as event photography. Its backpack strap configuration necessitates additional time to take off the case and retrieve equipment, unlike a shoulder bag, which can be easily swung forward for quick access.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps cannot be used for scenarios where a quick, one-handed operation or access is necessary such as in certain types of event photography, since taking off the backpack can be more time-consuming than simply swinging a shoulder bag around.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_563", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Do customers commonly experience problems with the zippers on this bag?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback generally indicates that the zippers on this bag are reliable, with most users not encountering any problems.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_495", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I frequently engage in street photography and require easy mobility; would this camera case be appropriate for that purpose?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is crafted for active shooting settings like street photography, offering mobility and swift access to your camera, as it omits a tripod attachment that might impede your movements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_564", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "How many extra lenses or flashes can the backpack accommodate in addition to the main camera body?", "long_answer": "The backpack has the capacity to accommodate 2-4 extra lenses or flashes along with the main camera body. It also features compartments and removable accessory pouches to help with the organization of these items.", "short_answer": "2-4", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_565", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the case designed to be waterproof?", "long_answer": "The product description does not mention any waterproof capabilities, suggesting that the case is not designed for significant water exposure. Customer feedback has not highlighted this as a feature, further indicating that waterproofing is not a central aspect of the product.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_566", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is a rain cover included with the Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack is equipped with a built-in rain cover that can be quickly deployed to enhance the backpack's water resistance during inclement weather conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_567", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the shoulder strap of this bag adjustable to accommodate various body sizes?", "long_answer": "The bag's shoulder strap is designed with a cam lock buckle, allowing for easy adjustments. This means it can be configured to fit comfortably across the shoulder or body, making it suitable for individuals of different sizes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_496", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon EOS Rebel T5?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. I own a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits perfectly. The size of the Canon EOS Rebel T5 is almost identical to the Canon 70D, so your camera should fit nicely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T5 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T5 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_497", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can I use this case for my Canon 1100D? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits perfectly. The Canon 1100D is similar in size, so it should also fit well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon 1100D has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon 1100D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_498", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag hold a Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit your camera. I use it for my Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens which is roughly the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_568", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 designed to resemble a regular backpack to deter theft?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 is purposefully designed to mimic the appearance of a regular backpack rather than a typical camera bag, which can be beneficial for users who wish to avoid drawing attention to the valuable equipment they are carrying.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_499", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this case fit my A-99 with a vertical grip?", "long_answer": "Based on the dimensions the case works well with the Nikon D3500, and your A-99 with a vertical grip has a similar size. Therefore, your camera should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the A-99 with vertical grip has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the A-99 with vertical grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_500", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is this camera case durable enough to withstand frequent use in outdoor environments where it could be subjected to rough handling?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is made of nylon, a fabric renowned for its resistance to abrasion. This attribute renders it ideal for situations where the case might be subject to constant friction or harsh treatment, thus guaranteeing its longevity during routine exposure to the outdoors.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_501", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I intend to film in the Arctic; can this case protect my camera from the extreme cold?", "long_answer": "When photographing in the Arctic, it is essential to use a case with superior thermal insulation. The nylon camera case mentioned does not offer specialized protection against extreme temperatures. It is advisable to opt for a case crafted with materials specifically designed to shield against the intense cold prevalent in such environments.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_400", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I ain't a fan of Velcro closures, seriously. Now, can you find me the cheapest camera case from either Case Logic or Ape Case, but no Velcro, ok?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Ape Case\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Ape Case\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Ape Case\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'Ape Case') AND closure_type != 'velcro' AND price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'Ape Case') AND closure_type != 'velcro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_569", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can the Case Logic SLR Sling accommodate small personal items such as a wallet and phone?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLR Sling is designed with multiple compartments that can be used to store small items. However, the size of personal items that can be comfortably stored is restricted as the pockets are rather tight, which may not be ideal for bulkier items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_401", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Listen, I've only got 50 dollars and I'm dead set on OP/TECH USA. What's the cheapest camera case you've got from them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 50 AND brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 50 AND brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_402", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I ain't interested in any fancy waterproof cases or ones with pockets. Give me the cheapest, simplest camera case you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_502", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does this camera case offer a convenient carrying option without sacrificing too much style?", "long_answer": "This camera case comes equipped with a shoulder strap for comfortable and convenient daily use. It is important to mention, though, that its design prioritizes practicality over a sleek or luxurious aesthetic that some users may prefer.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap fail to meet the requirements for users seeking a fashionable accessory, as the strap's primary focus is on functionality and comfort over luxury aesthetics.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_570", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the memory foam lining in the bag's interior lid provide protection for a camera's LCD screen?", "long_answer": "The memory foam lining found in the interior lid of the camera bag serves to cushion and shield the delicate LCD screen of a camera, an aspect that has been well-received by many customers for the protection it offers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_403", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I don't like camera cases with too many pockets nor with lock closures, they're just not for me. Now, find me the cheapest case that falls under the average pocket count and doesn't have any damn locks.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'locks'\nAND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases)\nORDER BY price ASC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_404", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I need a camera case that's either purple or mica, but it MUST be water-resistant. Oh, and more pockets the better. But I want the one with the least number of pockets among such options. Can you help me find it?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag` with asin: B009GYIKHQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"mica\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"mica\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"mica\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('purple', 'mica') AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_503", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this camera case provide quick access to my collapsible travel tripod while hiking?", "long_answer": "Indeed, if your collapsible travel tripod conforms to a standard shape and size, it ought to slide into the camera case's specially designed tripod pocket, ensuring swift access throughout your outdoor excursions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket do not have a function of accommodating very large or unusually shaped tripods that require more space or alternative attachment mechanisms than the pocket provides.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_504", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon EOS Rebel T5?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The Canon EOS Rebel T5 has similar dimensions to the Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the case fits that model perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T5 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T5 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_505", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Will this case accommodate a Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, it will not. I have tested with a Canon 10-22 mm lens which already completely fills the camera bag. The Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has a larger size which I think won't fit in this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_571", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the sling design of the camera bag effective for quick camera access?", "long_answer": "The sling design of the camera bag is widely appreciated by customers for its user-friendliness, especially when it comes to quick access to the camera, suggesting that the design serves its intended purpose effectively.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_572", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack come with a removable storage solution for additional items?", "long_answer": "The backpack features a removable accessory pouch, which serves as a convenient option for organizing extra items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_506", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for those who prioritize convenience above maximum protection against the elements?", "long_answer": "Certainly, should convenience and ease of access take precedence over safeguarding against water and harsh elements, this camera case is an appropriate option. It forgoes waterproof features to allow for simpler, more accessible handling of your camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_507", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Nikon D7100 with 18-300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The case is designed to accommodate the Canon L-series 100-400, and the size of your camera and lens combination is similar.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Nikon D7100 with 18-300mm lens has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Nikon D7100 with 18-300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_573", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera bag designed with a flat bottom that allows it to stand upright independently?", "long_answer": "The camera bag features a sling design which does not incorporate a flat bottom, hence it lacks the ability to remain upright on its own when placed down.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_574", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "How many SLR camera bodies can the Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag accommodate?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag is specifically designed to accommodate up to two SLR camera bodies, in addition to 2-3 lenses and various camera accessories.", "short_answer": "two", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_575", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Does the Ape Case Cubeze camera insert come equipped with external pockets for additional storage?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze camera insert is designed solely for placement within another bag and lacks external pockets for the storage of small items such as memory cards.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_405", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Alright, here's the deal. I've got 50 dollars and I want a red camera case. What's the cheapest option you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 50 AND color = \"red\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 50 AND color = \"red\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_508", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "My camera gear often suffers bumps and jostles during transport. Will this case provide adequate protection under those circumstances?", "long_answer": "The use of nylon in constructing this camera case renders it perfectly suited for challenging conditions. Its excellent abrasion resistance enables it to withstand and cushion some of the impacts and harsh handling experienced during travel, thereby protecting your photographic gear from possible harm.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_576", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the sling bag comfortable and stable during activities like biking?", "long_answer": "This sling bag is intended for use during activities and is generally perceived as stable and comfortable while performing actions such as biking, although comfort levels can differ among individuals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_577", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this bag suitable and practical for daily hikers to use?", "long_answer": "The bag has been regarded as practical for daily hikers based on feedback from users. They have highlighted its sturdiness, manageable size, and the ability to protect camera gear effectively on hiking trips. ", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_406", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I don't need all the extra pockets, just something that locks. What's the cheapest camera case you got that matches this?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets < 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets < 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'locks' AND pockets = 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_578", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can the Pelican 1200 Case be used to securely store and transport hard drives?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case is specifically designed to be suitable for storing hard drives, thanks to its watertight design and shock-resistant properties, which ensure the safety and security of electronic devices like hard drives during transportation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_509", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can I adjust the case by myself, or will I require assistance from someone else?", "long_answer": "You can adjust the case by yourself effortlessly. The camera case features user-friendly and adaptable backpack straps that you can swiftly alter to achieve the perfect fit for your comfort and support.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps feature adjustable elements that accommodate varying body types, which is a testament to their design versatility for personalized comfort and support.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_579", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is a waist strap included with the ACPRO2000 for additional support?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 comes equipped with a waist strap that provides additional support, enhancing comfort for the user.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_580", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the Ape Case Cubeze 37 capable of storing a DSLR along with 1-2 spare lenses?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze 37 is specifically designed to store a DSLR camera and has the capacity to fit 1-2 spare lenses, with the caveat that the size of the lenses affects the fit. The adjustable interior padding can be reconfigured to protect and accommodate the camera equipment properly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_510", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is this case engineered to reduce strain while carrying heavy camera equipment?", "long_answer": "For bulky camera equipment, a camera case featuring a hand grip may not be optimal for minimizing strain. The grip centralizes the load on a single point, potentially exacerbating fatigue. A preferable choice is a case with multiple carrying options that more equally spread out the weight, including a shoulder strap or waist belt.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip cannot be used for evenly distributing the weight across the photographer's body which is essential when carrying heavy gear over long periods, as the grip focuses the entire weight on one hand or wrist.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_581", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is there a dedicated side pocket on the Fastpack 200 for carrying a standard water bottle?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 features a side pocket specifically designed for the purpose of carrying a standard water bottle.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_582", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Are the internal dividers of the ACPRO2000 backpack adjustable to accommodate various gear?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 backpack comes with several padded dividers that are movable, allowing for customization based on the specific needs of your gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_407", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I've got a thing against the color red. Can you find me the cheapest camera case that's not red?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"red\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"red\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"red\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'red' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_408", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm seeking a case for my camera, specifically from OP/TECH USA and it's gotta be in red or orange. Get me the product details.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND color IN (\"red\", \"orange\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND color IN (\"red\", \"orange\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' AND (color = 'red' OR color = 'orange');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_583", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the bag include adjustable padded inserts for equipment protection?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with adjustable padded dividers, enabling the customization of protection to securely fit various items of equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_409", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm going for a non-yellow case from Pelican. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND NOT color = \"yellow\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND NOT color = \"yellow\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND NOT color = \"yellow\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Pelican' AND color != 'yellow' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_511", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon 5DII?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. It can accommodate my Nikon D3500 just right, and the Canon 5DII is quite similar in size to the Nikon D3500.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5DII has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5DII fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_410", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I can't stand zippers and need a camera case that's cheap. Pull up the cheapest one that's 30 dollars or less and doesn't have a zipper.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND price <= 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND price <= 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND closure_type != 'zipper' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_512", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this case accommodate a Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "No, the Canon 70-200 F4 lens is larger than the Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens which is what this case is designed for. It will be too tight.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_584", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the Ape Case backpack remain comfortable when it is packed to its full capacity?", "long_answer": "The comfort of the Ape Case backpack when fully packed is generally affirmed by most users, attributing the comfort to its adjustable harness system. Optimal comfort is achieved by balancing the load evenly and making use of the sternum strap.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_585", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "What size bag should I purchase for a full-frame DSLR camera to ensure proper fit?", "long_answer": "You should consider ordering a bag that is one size larger than you might for smaller camera models when you have a mid-sized or full-frame DSLR, to guarantee that there is enough space for all your equipment and that it fits comfortably. It is important to compare your camera's dimensions with the interior dimensions of the bag listed to make the appropriate choice.", "short_answer": "one size up", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_411", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm after a purple camera case that can handle some water. Find me the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_513", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "If I inadvertently spill a beverage on my camera bag, will my camera remain protected?", "long_answer": "The case material possesses a degree of water resistance sufficient to shield your camera from minor spills. Nevertheless, it isn't fully waterproof, hence prompt spill cleanup is advisable to prevent possible damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_586", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the side-entry compartment of this product easily accessible for right-handed individuals?", "long_answer": "Despite the compartment being located on the left side, the design intends to be convenient for all users, with right-handed individuals typically adapting quickly to its accessibility.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_587", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "What is the feedback from customers regarding the long-term durability of this bag?", "long_answer": "Based on customer feedback, the bag has demonstrated high durability, furnishing years of dependable use for many users.", "short_answer": "high durability", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_514", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Will this bag accommodate my Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens?  ", "long_answer": "Yes, this bag should be able to store your Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens. I have a Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8 and they fit just fine. Your set has a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_588", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this backpack larger or smaller compared to standard camera bags?", "long_answer": "The backpack is created with a design focus on being compact, allowing for adequate storage of camera equipment, yet maintaining a smaller size than what some users may anticipate from a typical camera bag.", "short_answer": "smaller", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_589", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "How easy is it to open the Double-Throw latches on the Pelican 1200 case?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 case is equipped with Double-Throw latches that are specifically designed to be easy to use, thereby facilitating a smoother opening experience than traditional latches offer.", "short_answer": "very easy", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_590", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "How well does the Pelican 1200 Case protect its contents from damage when dropped or subjected to impacts?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case is specifically designed with an open cell core and solid wall construction to offer superior impact resistance. This design has been frequently reported by customers to be effective in safeguarding their belongings against damage from accidental falls and impacts.", "short_answer": "highly effective", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_591", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack capable of accommodating a 16-inch laptop?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack is designed with a compartment specifically for laptops, and it can indeed hold laptops up to 16 inches in size, ensuring compatibility with full-sized laptops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_592", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this case equipped with a shoulder strap for carrying?", "long_answer": "The case is not equipped with a shoulder strap; instead, it is designed with a belt loop to facilitate attachment to a belt.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_515", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this case suitable for outdoor photography sessions in all weather conditions?", "long_answer": "For everyday outdoor activities, choosing a nylon camera case is practical because of its sturdy and light construction. That said, in situations where you expect to encounter harsh temperatures, it's important to note that nylon doesn't provide optimal insulation for such extremes. In these cases, a camera case with improved thermal protection would be advisable for severe climate conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_412", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I hate fumbling around for my stuff. Give me your cheapest orange camera case with less than two pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND color = \"orange\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND color = \"orange\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND color = \"orange\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'orange' \nAND pockets < 2 \nAND price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases WHERE color = 'orange' AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_516", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "May I bring this case aboard a boat without concern that splashes from the waves will harm my camera?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is engineered with waterproof features to protect your camera from water splashes, making it suitable for use on a boat without concern for water exposure. However, bear in mind that although it safeguards against water damage, it is not designed to withstand crushing forces, so take care to avoid strong impacts or pressure.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof elements fail to meet the requirements for being entirely crush-proof; while they can protect against water, they may not withstand being subjected to heavy weights or forces without additional rigid structural features.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_593", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the Ape Case Cubeze of comparable quality to higher-priced camera bags?", "long_answer": "According to customer feedback, the Ape Case Cubeze offers quite good quality that can stand up to more expensive camera bags, providing a viable, less cumbersome, and more affordable alternative for photographers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_594", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the shoulder strap cell phone holder accommodate larger modern smartphones?", "long_answer": "The shoulder strap pocket is designed for smaller phones or portable music players and may not be sufficient to hold larger modern smartphones, which would likely need to be carried in the main compartment of the bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_517", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is this camera case tailored for travel photographers who require swift setup at multiple locations?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this case is especially apt for travel photographers who require the ability to move quickly and seize fleeting moments, foregoing the extra setup that tripods necessitate. Without a tripod connector, the case appeals to those who prioritize portability and quickness above the stabilizing benefits offered by tripods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_595", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Does the camera case offer sufficient protection for everyday use for specific Canon camera models?", "long_answer": "The case is specifically padded to fit certain Canon camera models, offering a satisfactory level of protection for routine, everyday usage. Nevertheless, those in need of more extensive, heavy-duty protection may need to explore sturdier alternatives.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_596", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the case have a dedicated storage compartment for extra batteries?", "long_answer": "The case includes an internal slip pocket that is primarily designed for storing a lens cap; however, it may accommodate small items, such as an additional memory card. There is no specialized compartment specifically intended for extra batteries or a large amount of additional gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_597", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will the bag accommodate an SLR camera with an attached battery grip?", "long_answer": "The bag is specifically designed to hold standard SLR camera bodies and lenses. While it accommodates these items well, additional attachments such as a battery grip may make the camera too large to fit properly within the bag's hammock system.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_598", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is there a shoulder strap included with the AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case comes with a shoulder strap, providing an additional carrying option besides the built-in belt loop.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_518", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Could my camera potentially fall if I don't constantly hold it with this case?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the risk of accidental drops is higher since the case is engineered with just a hand grip, necessitating continuous holding due to the absence of a securing mechanism such as a neck or cross-body strap.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip do not have a function of securing the camera to the body like a neck strap or cross-body strap, potentially increasing the risk of accidental drops if the user does not maintain a constant grip.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_599", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can the Caselogic SLRC-202 accommodate a DSLR with a kit lens attached along with two extra lenses and various accessories?", "long_answer": "The Caselogic SLRC-202 is reported by most customers to have the capacity to store a DSLR with a lens attached, in addition to two extra lenses and various camera accessories, with the assumption that the lenses are of typical size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_519", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can I store my Canon 55-250 usm lens in this backpack?", "long_answer": "Yes, you can. This backpack is big enough for a Nikon D3500, and your Canon 55-250 usm lens is about the same size, so it should fit without any issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 55-250 usm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 55-250 usm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_413", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I can't stand the color orange! Can you help me find a camera case from either Pelican or AmazonBasics that's any color but that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)` with asin: B0002INQT2", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" AND brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"AmazonBasics\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" AND brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"AmazonBasics\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'Pelican' OR brand = 'AmazonBasics') AND color != 'orange';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_414", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I hate the color black and I don't really care about water resistance. Shoot me the product ID for the camera case with the least pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"black\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"black\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'black' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_520", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon t5i with a 300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, the case fits perfectly with my Canon 10-22mm lens. Since your Canon t5i with a 300mm lens is similar in size, it should fit as well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_521", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not. The case fits my Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens perfectly but the Canon 70-200 F4 lens is larger so it wouldn't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_522", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Will this case protect my camera in the event that it is accidentally dropped into a pool?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the case features water-resistant components designed to shield your camera from water damage in the event of submersion. Nevertheless, it is crucial to understand that despite its ability to prevent water penetration, without enhanced rigid structural elements, the case might not offer ample protection against substantial impacts or heavy pressure, such as from a drop or being compressed.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof elements fail to meet the requirements for being entirely crush-proof; while they can protect against water, they may not withstand being subjected to heavy weights or forces without additional rigid structural features.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_600", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the black color of the backpack effective at hiding dirt?", "long_answer": "The backpack's black color is practically chosen to conceal dirt, making it a suitable option for those who often use the backpack outdoors where it is prone to getting dirty.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_415", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I've taken a liking to USA Gear but I only want it in black or mica. Got any camera case like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR` with asin: B005J09OXU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"mica\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"mica\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'mica');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_601", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this camera bag accommodate a Canon T5 with a 40mm, 18-55mm, and 75-300mm lens, and additional accessories?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to fit a Canon T5 camera along with multiple lenses, including but not limited to a 40mm, an 18-55mm, and a 75-300mm lens. It also has space for additional accessories due to its main camera compartment and additional large compartment, as evidenced by customer experiences.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_602", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "How quickly can I access my camera using this backpack's sling design?", "long_answer": "The backpack's sling design facilitates rapid rotation from the back to the front, allowing for fast and convenient access to your camera gear without having to remove the backpack completely.", "short_answer": "fast and easy", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_523", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Do I need to conduct routine maintenance on the case to guarantee that my tripod remains secure while in use?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the case comes with a tripod attachment that utilizes a hook and loop fastener. With time, this kind of fastener may accumulate debris or its adhesive properties might diminish. Therefore, for a stable tripod grip, it's crucial to clean and care for the fastener at regular intervals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with tripod attachment using hook and loop fastener lack the capability to maintain a secure grip if the fastener becomes clogged with debris or loses its adhesive quality through wear and tear, indicating that periodic maintenance of the fastener is essential.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "hook and loop fastener", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_603", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the backpack have a dedicated system for attaching a tripod?", "long_answer": "The backpack features a dedicated tripod storage system, complete with a foldout holder that's hidden when not in use. It also has a quick-release buckle partnered with a strap that can secure a compact tripod or monopod to the side of the bag, offering a practical solution for carrying such equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_524", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm looking for an elegant camera case to give as a present; would this one be suitable?", "long_answer": "If you're seeking a gift that radiates sophistication, take into account the visual appeal of the camera case. Crafted from nylon, it typically presents a more relaxed and functional style, potentially not matching the upscale, sophisticated look you desire in a present.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_525", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this case protect my camera against accidental drops?", "long_answer": "Definitely, the EVA material employed in crafting this camera case is specifically engineered to cushion impacts and guard against damage due to inadvertent falls, offering an additional measure of protection for your camera throughout daily use and while traveling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with material described as EVA are ideally used for travel and portable applications, thanks to their ability to protect equipment from common hazards while remaining light and easy to handle.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "eva", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_526", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can I rely on this case to maintain my camera's form while it's in my bag?", "long_answer": "Should retaining your camera's shape within your bag be a concern, bear in mind that the nylon fabric of this case offers inherent pliability and may not uphold a stiff structure when compressed, potentially permitting slight alterations to the camera's form.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_527", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I intend to embark on a desert photography journey. Is this case adequate for shielding my camera against sand and dust?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is appropriate for a desert photography adventure. Its design emphasizes a balance of compactness and practicality under arid conditions, providing safeguards against sand and dust. However, bear in mind that although it is tailored for dry settings, it is not designed for scenarios involving submersion or significant exposure to moisture.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_604", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "How satisfied are customers with the customer service response when dealing with issues related to the bag?", "long_answer": "Customers who have experienced issues with the bag and subsequently contacted customer service typically report satisfaction with the level of support and response they receive.", "short_answer": "satisfied", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_416", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I can’t stand bulky camera cases, but I need it to be water-resistant. What’s the least pocket-ridden option you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_417", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I can't stand velcro closures and I'm not looking to blow more than a hundred bucks. Give me the first product that meets these preferences, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND price <= 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND price <= 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'velcro' AND price < 100 ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_528", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this camera case enable swift transitions should I need to capture a shot promptly?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case design incorporates a quick-access feature for your tripod. The hook-and-loop fastener facilitates swift transitions from transporting your camera to setting it up for photography, guaranteeing that you capture those essential shots without delay.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with tripod attachment using hook and loop fastener are known for offering flexible and convenient access to tripods, enabling quick transitions from mobile to static photography without the need for complicated attachment procedures.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "hook and loop fastener", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_605", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the black-colored backpack resistant to visible dirt, and is it considered stylish by customers?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed in black, a color that doesn't easily show dirt, which is frequently noted by customers. Additionally, its sleek design is often regarded as fashionable among those who have purchased it, suggesting it is both practical and stylish.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_529", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate a 15 1/2 inches long lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case should perfectly fit a 15 1/2 inches long lens. It is designed to fit a Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens which is similar in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the 15 1/2 inches long lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the 15 1/2 inches long lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_530", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is it possible to bring this camera case on a kayaking excursion to safeguard my gear against water damage?", "long_answer": "Since this camera case isn't waterproof, it can't guarantee a watertight seal to safeguard your camera in a damp setting. Consequently, it's wise to seek out a camera case designed with waterproof capabilities prior to embarking on a kayaking adventure.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_606", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the camera case fully waterproof and weatherproof?", "long_answer": "The case offers a degree of protection against light rain and dust, but it is not fully waterproof or designed to provide extensive weatherproofing.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_418", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Listen, I don't need any of that fancy water-resistance nonsense. Just get me the cheapest case from Lowepro or AmazonBasics, got it?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras` with asin: B005VTIMEQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"AmazonBasics\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"AmazonBasics\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'Lowepro' OR brand = 'AmazonBasics') AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_531", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case fit an A-99 with a vertical grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, the case should fit an A-99 with a vertical grip. I have a Nikon D3500 which is a similar size and it fits fine in this case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the A-99 with vertical grip has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the A-99 with vertical grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_532", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can this case fit a Canon T3i with 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it with my Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens which is around the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon T3i with 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon T3i with 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_419", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I don't want any frilly closures like locks, and I don't give two hoots about water resistance either. What's the plainest camera case you got that fits these criteria?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'locks' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_607", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the camera pouch design allow for continued use of a neck strap?", "long_answer": "The camera pouch has been designed such that it can close around a neck strap, enabling the user to maintain the use of the strap while the camera is inside the pouch.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_420", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm looking for a Canon camera case and I've got a thing for mica, gotta have it in mica. But here's the kicker, I don't want a bunch of pockets. Could you find the one with the least pockets for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND color = \"mica\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND color = \"mica\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Canon' AND color = 'mica' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_608", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can the waist belt of this backpack be detached?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with a waist belt that can be detached, providing versatility in how the backpack can be worn. This attribute helps with weight distribution and increases the comfort of the wearer.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_533", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can this camera case withstand frequent usage in outdoor environments where it may be subjected to rough handling?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is made of nylon, a material renowned for its resistance to abrasion. This renders it especially appropriate for situations where the case might be subject to constant friction or harsh treatment, guaranteeing its longevity during routine outdoor activities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_609", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack provide comfort for extended hiking durations?", "long_answer": "Users generally find the backpack suitable for long hikes, primarily due to features like the adjustable sternum strap and waistbelt which assist in evenly distributing the carry weight. Nevertheless, perceived comfort may vary based on individual preferences and the specific load being carried.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_610", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can the Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack hold a pro DSLR with an attached lens?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack is specifically designed to carry a professional DSLR camera with a lens (up to 80-200mm f/2.8) already attached, in addition to accommodating 2-4 extra lenses or flashes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_611", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the main compartment of this bag large enough to accommodate a full-sized DSLR and multiple lenses?", "long_answer": "The bag's main compartment includes adjustable dividers and is crafted to house a full-sized DSLR attached to a standard zoom lens, as well as provide space for additional lenses. However, the degree of snugness in fit may vary based on the particular dimensions of your camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_421", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm looking for a purple camera case, and I don't want to shell out more than 10 bucks. Can you find one that fits my budget?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND color = \"purple\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND color = \"purple\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' AND price <= 10;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_534", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Canon EOS Rebel T5?", "long_answer": "Yes, it definitely should. This case is designed to fit the Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and your Canon EOS Rebel T5 is about the same size, so it should fit well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T5 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T5 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_612", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Do the zippers on this backpack tend to break or catch easily?", "long_answer": "The backpack's zippers are typically of good quality, but caution should be exercised when using them around corners to prevent breakage or the zipper from catching on material.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_613", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "How quickly can a camera be accessed from the side-entry compartment of the backpack?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with a side-entry compartment that permits rapid access to the camera, enabling photographers to retrieve their gear swiftly without the need to take off the backpack, which is an advantage in situations where speed is crucial.", "short_answer": "very quickly", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_422", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I've got 50 dollars and I need a camera case with either a drawstring or velcro closure. Here's the kicker, I need one with the fewest pockets. What have you got that fits the bill?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND price <= 50 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND price <= 50 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND price <= 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'velcro') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_535", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon T3i with a 300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit your Canon T3i with a 300mm lens since it's similar in size to the Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens, which fits well in this case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon T3i with 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon T3i with 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_536", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for my landscape photography excursions where I frequently rely on a tripod to ensure stability?", "long_answer": "Given that this camera case lacks a tripod attachment, it is better suited for photographers who value portability and seldom rely on tripods for tasks like long exposure or time-lapse photography. Should your photography often involve a tripod, consider exploring cases equipped with this particular capability to meet your requirements.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_614", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the slimline protection of this holster designed to fit inside a standard non-camera bag such as a backpack or purse?", "long_answer": "The slimline protection of the holster is specifically designed to allow the holster to be inserted into a variety of non-camera bags of typical size, including backpacks and purses, enabling easy integration with the user's preferred bag choice.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_423", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I don't need all those extra pockets. Just find me the cheapest case you have with one pocket or less.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_424", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "My gear can't handle a splash, let alone a downpour. I need the cheapest water-resistant camera case you have. Got something for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_537", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this case handle 50-500 Sigma lenses?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Nikon D5000 with battery grip and it fits perfectly. Considering your 50-500 Sigma lenses have a similar size, it should work just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_538", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I frequently shoot in windy conditions; can I effectively use this case?", "long_answer": "Camera stability is crucial in windy conditions, particularly for disciplines such as landscape photography, where even slight motion can result in blurred photos. Regrettably, this case lacks a tripod attachment, potentially rendering it less proficient at maintaining camera steadiness in these circumstances.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_539", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is this camera bag appropriate for individuals with back issues?", "long_answer": "Considering that uneven weight distribution can negatively impact individuals with back problems, a camera case equipped with a shoulder strap may not be the best option. This type of case has the potential to worsen pain or discomfort; hence, seeking out cases with alternative carrying methods that reduce back strain is advisable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not suitable for users who may have medical conditions or pain that is exacerbated by carrying weight on one side of the body; other carrying options may be better in these cases.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_540", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "No, this case likely won't be able to accommodate your Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens. I've tried it with a Canon 70D with a 70-250 lens and it barely fit. If your device is larger, then it definitely won't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_425", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm not a fan of Altura Photo. Find me a drawstring camera case from any other brand, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Altura Photo' AND closure_type = 'drawstring';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_541", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can the Canon EOS Rebel T1i fit into the OP/TECH USA soft pouch? ", "long_answer": "Yes. The pouch works well with the Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, which is similar in size to the Canon EOS Rebel T1i, so it should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T1i has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T1i fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_426", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I've got a thing for black and red. Can you find me the cheapest camera case in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"red\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"red\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"red\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('black', 'red') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_615", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the backpack's interior improve visibility for locating items in low-light conditions?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed with a Hi-Vis yellow interior which enhances the visibility, specifically aiming to assist in locating smaller items when the light is insufficient.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_542", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm somewhat accident-prone and concerned about tearing the case. Is this particular one durable enough to reduce that possibility?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the nylon fabric used to construct this camera case is highly prized for its tear-resistant properties. This robustness renders it a superb option for individuals worried about damage due to inadvertent mishaps.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_427", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I don't want any extra pockets on my camera case, but water resistance is a must. Can you dig up the cheapest one that checks these boxes?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_543", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can I use this case for my Nikon v2 with a 70-300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case should fit your Nikon v2 with a 70-300mm lens. It's similar in size to the Canon 70D with a 18-55mm lens, which fits this case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Nikon v2 with 70-300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Nikon v2 with 70-300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_428", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm working with a limited budget here, and I'm looking for a camera case from either USA Gear or Case Logic, with either drawstring or velcro closure. Can you find the least expensive option for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"USA Gear\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"USA Gear\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"USA Gear\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'Case Logic') \nAND closure_type IN ('drawstring', 'velcro') \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_616", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG camera bag designed to be compact for easy management?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag is specifically designed to offer a spacious interior for storage while maintaining a compact form. This design ensures a balance between sufficient carrying capacity for photography equipment and portability for the user.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_429", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case with a drawstring closure. Now, don't make me break my bank, show me the least expensive one you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_430", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I want a purple camera case, but not one packed with too many pockets. Which is the most affordable one that has less pockets than average?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_544", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this case designed to be comfortable to carry for prolonged durations during a city tour?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case should be suitable for prolonged carrying on urban excursions, as the backpack straps facilitate balanced weight distribution over your shoulders, though it may not be the most compact choice for navigating densely populated city settings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps fail to meet the requirements for a low-profile carry option in crowd-intensive settings due to their bulkier design when compared to more streamlined cases or bags.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_617", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the bag equipped with an integrated rain cover for protection in wet conditions?", "long_answer": "The bag is not sold with an official rain cover included, which suggests it is susceptible to water damage in rainy conditions; therefore, precautions such as seeking shelter or using a separate rain cover are recommended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_545", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will the camera case provide complete protection for my equipment during heavy rainfall?", "long_answer": "Although the camera case is constructed from a sturdy material, it should be noted that typical cases fashioned from this material offer only fundamental water resistance. To achieve full waterproofing, extra measures must be implemented to guarantee that your gear remains dry during torrential downpours.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_618", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "What type of closure mechanism does the Soft Pouch have?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch is equipped with non-marring snaps located at the bottom, which are used to secure the flap cover and close the pouch.", "short_answer": "non-marring snaps", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_619", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Are the dividers inside the backpack customizable to fit different sizes of gear?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with interior adjustable dividers, which means you can arrange the main compartment's space to accommodate your particular gear, no matter its specific size or shape.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_546", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm concerned about how long it takes to stow my gear; will this case expedite the packing process?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case prioritizes efficiency. Designed for increased speed in camera storage, it eliminates the hassle of external attachments such as tripods. This allows for quick packing of your equipment, ensuring you don't miss a moment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_547", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can I safely assume that this case will protect my camera from any harm during a day at the beach?", "long_answer": "Certainly, your camera ought to stay safe from water-related incidents like sea spray or unintended submersion with this waterproof camera case. It's important to recognize, though, that while the case does offer protection against water and sand, it isn't entirely crush-resistant. Caution is recommended to avoid circumstances where the case could be subjected to significant pressure or weight, as this could lead to damage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof elements fail to meet the requirements for being entirely crush-proof; while they can protect against water, they may not withstand being subjected to heavy weights or forces without additional rigid structural features.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_431", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I don't want anything fancy, no OP/TECH USA stuff and no more than one pocket. Find me the cheapest camera case with those requirements, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand <> 'OP/TECH USA' AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_548", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can this camera case withstand frequent use in outdoor environments where it may be subjected to rough treatment?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is made from nylon, a material renowned for its resistance to abrasion. This quality renders it especially appropriate for situations where the case might undergo frequent friction or harsh treatment, guaranteeing its longevity during consistent outdoor usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_432", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I've got a thing for mica colored stuff. Do you have any camera case in that color?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag` with asin: B009GYIKHQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'mica';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_620", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will the Pelican 1200 Case accommodate larger DSLR cameras and various lenses?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case may not have sufficient space for larger DSLR cameras and several lenses. To ensure compatibility, one should measure their camera equipment and check against the case's interior dimensions before deciding to use it for storage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_549", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this camera case be burdensome to carry if I'm frequently on the move and need to access my camera often?", "long_answer": "No, it won't be cumbersome. The camera case features a hand grip that is particularly beneficial for photographers who are constantly on the move and often need to access their camera. It offers a reliable and convenient method to handle your camera while you're on the go.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip are ideally used for short-duration photography sessions or scenarios where the camera needs to be frequently accessed and then quickly stowed away again.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_433", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I ain't into fancy camera cases with zillion pockets and weird lock mechanisms. Find me the cheapest one with no more than one pocket and without lock as a closure.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases \nWHERE pockets <= 1 AND closure_type <> 'locks' \nORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1) \nAND pockets <= 1 AND closure_type <> 'locks';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_434", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I can't go over 50 bucks and I need a camera case with a zipper. Preferably with the least amount of pockets. What's my best option here?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND closure_type = 'zipper' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_435", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I ain't in need of something fancy, just a basic AmazonBasics camera case with 1 or 2 pockets max. What's the cheapest you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND pockets <= 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND pockets <= 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'AmazonBasics' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_550", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this bag fit a d3300?", "long_answer": "Yes, it would fit. I use it on my Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens, and that's about the same size as your d3300.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the d3300 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the d3300 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_551", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense?", "long_answer": "No, it will not. I have a Nikon D3500 which just fits, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense is larger than my device.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_621", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the velcro closure of the product durable over prolonged use?", "long_answer": "The velcro closure is designed to be durable, yet it is subject to wear and tear like any other velcro material, potentially leading to a reduction in its gripping power over an extended period.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_552", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can this case fit a Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Nikon D5000 with a battery grip and it fits well. Since your Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom is similar in size to my Nikon D5000, it should also fit into this case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_553", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Will my Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fit in this backpack?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The bag comfortably fits a Canon 70D with a 70-250 lens, which is about the same size as your Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_622", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can the Case Logic SLRC-205 camera bag be used to carry items other than camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLRC-205 camera bag, though primarily designed for transporting camera gear, offers additional compartments that allow for the storage of small personal items, thereby extending its utility beyond just camera equipment carrying needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_554", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Will my Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fit in this backpack?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The bag fits my Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8 and your camera lens has similar dimensions so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_623", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "What is the durability level of the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG concerning material and padding?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG utilizes durable materials in its construction. It includes full padding and reinforced structure, which is reflected in customer feedback indicating satisfaction with the level of protection it offers for camera equipment.", "short_answer": "durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_624", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the camera bag include additional compartments for non-camera related accessories?", "long_answer": "The camera bag comes equipped with extra storage facilities specifically designed to accommodate accessories that are not necessarily related to camera equipment. These compartments can be utilized to store various items that one might need to carry along with the camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_436", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm a sucker for teal but I hate bulky cases. What's the cheapest teal camera case you have that has less pockets than average?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'teal' AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_625", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this backpack capable of storing a full-frame DSLR camera without modifications?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed to accommodate a full-frame DSLR camera, but in instances where a battery grip is attached or larger lenses are used, adjustments may be necessary, which could limit the amount of additional gear you can carry.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_437", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I've had it with Altura Photo, their products just don't cut it for me. Give me the ID of a camera case from any other brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Altura Photo' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_555", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon t5i with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The case is designed to fit a Nikon D5200 with two lenses, so your Canon t5i with a 300mm lens, being of similar size, should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "search_qa_438", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I ain't a fan of flashy colors and don't need a ton of pockets. Plus, the average case has too many pockets. What's the cheapest camera case you got without all the frills and doesn't come in mica?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND NOT color = \"mica\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND NOT color = \"mica\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND NOT color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'mica' AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_626", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the bag capable of holding two camera bodies and multiple lenses simultaneously?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to accommodate one to two camera bodies and one to two lenses. Although it is possible to fit two camera bodies and multiple lenses, the comfort and ease of fitting such gear will vary based on the dimensions of the equipment, potentially making it a tight fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_627", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can the bag branded for Canon cameras also accommodate other camera brands?", "long_answer": "The bag, despite being branded for Canon, has proven adaptable as customers have successfully used it with numerous other camera brands, evidencing its versatility to house a range of cameras and associated gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_439", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm all about convenience and easy access, mate. Get me the camera case with the least pockets and a velcro closure.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'velcro' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_628", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is there a risk of the case's belt loop snapping open during normal use?", "long_answer": "Despite concerns from some customers about the belt loop's strength, it is designed to remain secure when attached correctly during standard usage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_629", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does this bag become difficult to carry when filled with a heavy load of gear?", "long_answer": "The sling is crafted to offer ease of movement; however, when loaded with a significant amount of gear, some users have observed that it can become cumbersome, a trait typical of most camera bags.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_556", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Will this backpack fit my Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, it would not fit perfectly. I use my Canon 70D with 70-250 lens and it just fills the bag. Your Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens is larger than mine so it would not be a good fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_557", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is this case designed to withstand high-humidity environments, such as those near waterfalls or beaches?", "long_answer": "The absence of waterproofing in this camera case renders it incapable of fully protecting against humidity or water spray intrusion. In areas with elevated humidity levels, like around waterfalls or on beachfronts, there is a heightened possibility of moisture infiltrating your camera. Opting for a waterproof case would be a more secure selection in such environments.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_630", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "How quick and convenient is the camera retrieval from the backpack's side entry compartment?", "long_answer": "The backpack's design includes a side entry compartment which provides the convenience of quickly retrieving the camera without requiring the user to remove the backpack.", "short_answer": "quick and convenient", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_631", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the backpack designed to comfortably handle very heavy loads?", "long_answer": "The backpack is engineered to evenly distribute weight; however, there are customer reports suggesting that the straps may not be sufficiently robust to comfortably manage very heavy loads, implying that care should be taken when packing.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_632", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the appearance of the Lowepro Passport Sling similar to that of a traditional camera bag?", "long_answer": "The design of the Lowepro Passport Sling is distinctive and modern, differing from the conventional look of a traditional camera bag, thus offering a subtle way for photographers to transport their gear without attracting undue attention.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_558", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this camera case designed to protect my equipment in extremely cold conditions?", "long_answer": "Although the camera case is constructed from robust material, it should be acknowledged that its nylon fabrication may not provide the best insulation in intensely cold environments. For exposure to severe cold, selecting a case designed with specialized thermal materials would be advisable to better safeguard your camera gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_559", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will this fit my Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens and it fits perfectly, but your camera setup seems to be larger, so it might not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_560", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Would the Lowepro Fastpack 200 fit my Nikon v2 with a 70-300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it for my Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens which has similar dimensions to your Nikon v2 with a 70-300mm lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Nikon v2 with 70-300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Nikon v2 with 70-300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_633", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the camera case remain rigid and maintain its shape when not containing a camera?", "long_answer": "The camera case is constructed with cloth-covered foam, a material that ensures the case retains its shape even when it is not holding a camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_634", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the shoulder strap of the bag replaceable in the event of damage?", "long_answer": "The shoulder strap is designed to be removable, thereby allowing it to be replaced in the event it becomes damaged. Any strap that is compatible can be used as a substitute.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_440", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I can't be fumbling around with too many pockets and absolutely no velcro. What's the cheapest camera case you have that only has up to 2 pockets and anything but a velcro closure?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type <> 'velcro' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_635", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the AmazonBasics Camera Case listing specify both internal and external dimensions?", "long_answer": "Yes, the AmazonBasics Camera Case listing specifies both internal and external dimensions. The internal dimensions are 4.3 inches by 2.5 inches by 0.9 inches, and the external dimensions are 4.9 inches by 3.2 inches by 1.6 inches.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_441", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm not looking to ruin my gear in a little rain, but I hate those drawstring closures. Find me a water-resistant camera case with the fewest pockets, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND closure_type != 'drawstring' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_636", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is there a dedicated laptop compartment in the Lowepro Flipside 300 camera backpack?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 camera backpack is designed primarily for carrying camera gear and therefore does not have a specialized compartment intended for storing a laptop.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_442", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm not really into green and don't need any lockable closures. What's the cheapest camera case you have that matches my preferences?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND NOT closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'green' AND closure_type != 'locks' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_443", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I've got no interest in cases with locks and I'm particular about the color; either red or teal would do. What's the cheapest case you got that ticks all these boxes?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras` with asin: B001I3X3HU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND color IN (\"teal\", \"red\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND color IN (\"teal\", \"red\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND color IN (\"teal\", \"red\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'locks' AND (color = 'red' OR color = 'teal') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_561", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I've successfully used it with a Nikon D5000 with a battery grip, and their sizes are quite close.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "search_qa_444", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I don't like carrying around a bunch of stuff and I'm on a tight budget, so find me the cheapest camera case you have that doesn't have more than one pocket and costs no more than 30 bucks.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_445", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm looking for a red camera case, but I don't want any pockets. What's the cheapest you got in stock?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_446", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm looking for a Sony camera case but my budget is tight, not more than 50 dollars. Get me the least expensive option you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Sony\" AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Sony\" AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Sony' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_447", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I've got a ton of accessories and prefer Sony or Canon. Show me a camera case from these brands with the least amount of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Canon\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Canon\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Canon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand='Sony' OR brand='Canon') AND pockets=(SELECT pockets FROM camera_cases WHERE brand='Sony' OR brand='Canon' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "search_qa_448", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm looking for a green camera case that can resist a little rain. What's the cheapest one you have that checks those boxes?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_449", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Zippers and drawstrings are my style, so look up the cheapest camera case with either of those features, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'drawstring') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_562", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I require a case durable enough to endure the demands of fieldwork, one that can also accommodate my complete photography gear. Would this be an appropriate selection?", "long_answer": "This camera case may not be suitable for extensive fieldwork involving diverse equipment, as it omits the essential feature of a tripod attachment. Such functionality is crucial for the secure transport and rapid setup of standard professional photography gear, including tripods and external lights.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_637", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Fastpack 200 have a dedicated pocket for carrying a water bottle?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack is equipped with an outer accessory pocket, which can be utilized for carrying a water bottle. However, it should be noted that this pocket may be snug for certain sizes of bottles, potentially limiting the compatibility with some larger water bottles.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_638", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case compatible with the Canon Powershot A650IS camera?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case is specifically tailored to fit the Canon Powershot A650IS, ensuring a secure and form-fitting protection for the camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_450", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm picky about brands, so only show me stuff from USA Gear and Ape Case. Also, I need to keep it under 10 dollars. Now, give me the one with the least pockets.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Ape Case\") AND price <= 10 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Ape Case\") AND price <= 10 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Ape Case\") AND price <= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'Ape Case') AND price < 10 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_639", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this bag suitable for storing a Canon Powershot camera along with its charger and small accessories?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to fit several models of the Canon Powershot camera, providing enough space for not only the camera itself but also its charger and additional minor accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_563", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate my Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit just fine. I use it for my Nikon D3500 and they have similar dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_640", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can the bag be conveniently converted to 'flip mode' for easy access?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with the capability to be used in 'flip mode'; however, according to customer feedback, mastering this feature may require some practice, particularly when the bag is heavily loaded.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_564", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Could carrying this camera case for extended periods lead to discomfort in my hip?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case features an ergonomic design that includes a mechanism for evenly distributing weight when worn on the hip, reducing strain and enhancing comfort during prolonged use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop feature unique ergonomic benefits, contributing to an even weight distribution that minimizes strain when carried on the hip for extended periods.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_565", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "During my travels, I would like to reach for my camera at a moment's notice. Could this camera case pose any problems for that?", "long_answer": "If your travel purpose centers on swiftly capturing moments, a camera case with backpack straps may feel somewhat limiting, as it doesn't provide the rapid access to your camera that a sling bag does. For immediate availability, opting for a design that permits fast gear access without the need to take off the bag could be more fitting.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps do not have a function of instant accessibility compared to certain sling bags which can provide faster access to equipment for those who need to switch gear quickly and frequently.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_451", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I don't fancy anything with a zipper closure or a red color. What's the camera case with the fewest pockets you have that meets these conditions?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND NOT color = \"red\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND NOT color = \"red\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND NOT color = \"red\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'zipper' AND color != 'red' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_566", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I require a case durable enough to withstand the demands of fieldwork while also accommodating all my photography gear. Would this be a suitable option?", "long_answer": "The camera case might not be adequate for extensive fieldwork involving diverse equipment due to the absence of a critical tripod attachment. This feature is essential for the safe transport and rapid setup of commonly utilized professional photography gear, including tripods and external lighting.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_567", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "I'm not sure it will. I have a Canon 60D with a Sigma 17-55mm f2.8 and it fits, but I believe your Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens might be a bit too big to fit in this backpack.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8"}}
{"id": "search_qa_452", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm over the black camera case I currently have. Can you recommend an AmazonBasics non-black one instead? Just show me one, don't wanna waste time.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND brand = \"AmazonBasics\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND brand = \"AmazonBasics\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'AmazonBasics' AND color != 'black' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_568", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Should I happen to inadvertently spill a beverage on my camera bag, will the contents, specifically my camera, remain protected?", "long_answer": "The case material boasts water-resistant properties to shield your camera from minor splashes. However, it is not fully waterproof. Therefore, promptly cleaning up any spills is advisable to prevent possible damage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_641", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Fastpack 200 backpack come with a built-in tripod holder?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack does not include a dedicated holder specifically designed for carrying a tripod. Users seeking to transport a tripod with this backpack typically improvise by using the front flap to secure lightweight tripods.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_569", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does this bag fit the 50-500 Sigma lenses?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and your 50-500 Sigma lenses and mine are similar in size. So it will fit fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_570", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can this bag carry a 15 1/2 inches long lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, this bag is able to hold a 15 1/2 inches long lens. It fits my Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens perfectly, and the size of your lens is quite similar to that.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the 15 1/2 inches long lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the 15 1/2 inches long lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_571", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this case fit a Canon Rebel T3? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Nikon D3500 which is similar in size to the Canon Rebel T3 and it fits perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_572", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this bag fit my Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens, and it fits perfectly in this bag. Given that your camera and lens are a similar size, you should have no problem fitting them in.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_573", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can I rapidly retrieve my camera from this case when I need to take a spontaneous shot?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is crafted for enhanced accessibility, eschewing complex sealing methods such as watertight zippers or locks commonly seen in waterproof cases. This facilitates rapid access to your camera, perfect for capturing those spontaneous, fleeting moments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_453", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Look, I can't stand drawstring closures. Can you find me a camera case by OP/TECH USA without one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' AND closure_type != 'drawstring';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_574", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will the Canon EOS Rebel T5 fit in this Lowepro Fastpack 200?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit well. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits in this case. Your Canon EOS Rebel T5 is about the same size as my setup.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T5 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T5 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_575", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I frequently shoot in windy conditions; can this case still be used effectively?", "long_answer": "Under blustery conditions, maintaining camera stability is crucial, particularly for disciplines such as landscape photography where slight motion can result in blurred images. Regrettably, this particular case lacks a tripod attachment, rendering it less than ideal for stabilizing your camera in those scenarios.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_642", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is this backpack designed to accommodate a 17-inch laptop?", "long_answer": "The backpack is specifically tailored to hold laptops up to a maximum size of 15.6 inches, and customers have reported that a 17-inch laptop cannot be accommodated within it.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_576", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "When not in use, is the camera case designed for convenient storage without occupying too much space?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is crafted from a material that enables it to collapse when not in use, ensuring easy storage without taking up significant space.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_643", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the Case Logic sling bag have compartments for small personal items such as keys or a smartphone?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic sling bag includes extra zippered pockets that are specifically designed to hold and secure small personal items like keys or a smartphone.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_644", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is there a designated pocket in the case for storing small items such as memory sticks or an extra battery?", "long_answer": "The case includes a small pocket suitable for storing items like memory sticks, and it could potentially accommodate an extra battery, though it's important to note that the space available in this pocket is somewhat restricted.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_577", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can I use this case for my Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8?", "long_answer": "Yes, my Canon 70D with 70-250 lens fits well and your camera seems to have a similar size, so it should fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_645", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the Cubeze 37 case adequately protective of camera equipment, including cameras and lenses?", "long_answer": "The Cubeze 37 case is designed with padding to offer extra durability and protection, and users generally report that it effectively safeguards their cameras and lenses when they are securely placed within the case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_578", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this case fit the Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "No, it won't. I have a Nikon D3500 which fits but considering the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm lens is larger than the Nikon D3500, it won't fit in this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_646", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Does this camera case provide waterproof protection?", "long_answer": "The camera case does offer a degree of protection, but it is not marketed as waterproof or completely weather-resistant. The case is capable of shielding against minor splashes; however, it should not be relied upon in conditions of heavy rain or submersion in water.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_454", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm not flashing a lot of cash and barely need any pockets. Gimme the cheapest camera case you have within 30 dollars that comes with less than two pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND pockets < 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND pockets < 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_455", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I refuse to spend more than 50 dollars on a camera case that's not even water resistant. Give me the cheapest option you have that meets these standards.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_579", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag fit my Canon EOS Rebel T1i?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it with my Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the sizes are almost identical.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T1i has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T1i fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_647", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the camera bag designed to allow for quick retrieval of the camera?", "long_answer": "The bag is consistently reported by customers to provide quick access to the camera, thereby facilitating the ability to take impromptu photographs efficiently.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_580", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does this camera case serve as a fashionable accessory that complements one's attire?", "long_answer": "The camera case prioritizes functionality and carrying comfort, potentially falling short for those who value high-fashion aesthetics. Its design favors practicality, including a shoulder strap for ease of use, rather than luxury appeal.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap fail to meet the requirements for users seeking a fashionable accessory, as the strap's primary focus is on functionality and comfort over luxury aesthetics.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_648", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the retaining strap included with the case serve its intended purpose effectively?", "long_answer": "The retaining strap included with the case serves its intended purpose of keeping the case attached to the camera or lens; however, its utility depends on user preference, as some users may find it useful while others may choose to remove it.", "short_answer": "varies", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_456", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I'm in need of a camera case but it has to have either locks or velcro, and anything but mica color. Just make sure it's the one with the fewest pockets. Can you sort that out for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND NOT color = \"mica\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND NOT color = \"mica\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND NOT color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'velcro') AND color != 'mica' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_649", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is a shoulder strap included with the purchase of this bag?", "long_answer": "The bag includes a detachable padded shoulder strap designed to enhance carrying comfort for the user.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_581", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this bag hold the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to fit. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens and they have a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_582", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm concerned with how long it takes to stow my equipment; will this case expedite the packing?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is designed for efficiency. It facilitates faster storage of your camera as it eliminates the hassle of external attachments such as tripods. As a result, you can stow your equipment quickly and seamlessly, ensuring you don't miss any important moments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_650", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the ergonomic sling strap and padded waistbelt design of this backpack contribute to comfort over long durations?", "long_answer": "The design features, including the ergonomic sling strap and padded waistbelt, contribute to the backpack's comfort for extended wear, but the overall level of comfort experienced can be influenced by the weight of the contents carried within the backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_583", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is it possible to modify the camera case to accommodate my larger frame comfortably?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case features adaptable components to accommodate a wide range of body shapes, thus ensuring comfortable wearability no matter your size. The adjustable backpack straps, in particular, offer a customizable and supportive fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps feature adjustable elements that accommodate varying body types, which is a testament to their design versatility for personalized comfort and support.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_584", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I need my camera gear to remain unobtrusive in city environments; does this case help it blend in?", "long_answer": "In crowded urban settings where inconspicuity is essential, a camera case designed with a dedicated compartment for a tripod may not be the most suitable option. The design required to accommodate tripod storage could make the case stand out and inadvertently signal the presence of expensive camera gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket lack the capability to remain sleek and inconspicuous, as the protrusion or shape of the pocket may reveal the storage of valuable equipment, potentially drawing unwanted attention.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_651", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the camera case designed to fit the PowerShot A590IS model perfectly?", "long_answer": "The camera case in question is not designed with the specific intention of fitting the PowerShot A590IS model, but according to reports from several reviewers who own the A590IS, it appears to accommodate the camera quite well.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_652", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Are the padded dividers in the main compartment customizable for different camera and lens setups?", "long_answer": "The padded dividers in the main compartment of the product are fully adjustable, which gives you the flexibility to configure the space to accommodate various sizes and shapes of cameras and lenses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_585", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this case fit a Canon EOS Rebel SL1?", "long_answer": "Yes, the case will fit. I use this with a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens which is a similar size to the Canon EOS Rebel SL1.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_457", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I don't have time for flimsy zippers. Get me the cheapest camera case with either a drawstring or lock closure.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('drawstring', 'locks') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_458", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I need a camera case under 100 bucks, preferably with a drawstring or velcro closure. And don't bother showing me something with a bunch of pockets, just give me the one with the least.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 \nAND (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'velcro') \nORDER BY pockets ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_653", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the bag remain comfortable to wear throughout the entire day?", "long_answer": "While the bag is deemed comfortable by the majority of users because of its padded shoulder strap, it has the potential to feel heavy over a prolonged period, especially if it is fully loaded. However, the inclusion of an adjustable waist strap helps in evening out the weight distribution, enhancing the overall comfort.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_654", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the backpack have a designated storage system for carrying a tripod?", "long_answer": "The backpack has a dedicated storage system designed for tripods, which features a hidden foldout holder and a quick-release buckle with a strap to secure a compact tripod or monopod to the side. Nevertheless, it is worth noting that some users have reported that attaching a tripod can affect the balance of the backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_586", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does this case have fewer complex parts that might break or require maintenance?", "long_answer": "Indeed, as this camera case is not engineered for waterproofing, it typically lacks intricate seals or locking systems. Consequently, there are fewer components that may fail or necessitate regular maintenance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_655", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Does the case have dedicated storage for additional batteries and memory cards?", "long_answer": "The case is designed with specific storage compartments that can accommodate memory stick media and an extra battery, although the available space is intended to hold only these essential accessories and is somewhat restricted.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_587", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for situations where I need to travel light and keep my luggage to a minimum?", "long_answer": "Should your journey necessitate stringent baggage limits and require you to pack efficiently, this specific camera case might not be suitable. It features a dedicated tripod pocket that potentially enlarges the case's dimensions, diminishing its potential for compact storage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket fail to meet the requirements for a compact storage solution when space is a premium, such as for photographers needing to adhere to strict travel luggage constraints.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_656", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can the foam interior of the Pelican 1200 Case be customized to fit various items?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case utilizes Pick N'Pluck foam, which enables easy customization of the foam interior to securely accommodate a variety of items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_459", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm into this color red and I only prefer drawstring or velcro closure types for my camera case. Can you find me a product like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"velcro\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color='red' AND (closure_type='drawstring' OR closure_type='velcro');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_657", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the AmazonBasics camera case have a dedicated space for storing spare batteries and memory cards?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics camera case features a zippered pocket specifically designed to hold memory cards and small accessories, which includes being able to accommodate spare batteries, as evidenced by the successful experiences of numerous users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_588", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for extended underwater photography sessions?", "long_answer": "No, since the case is constructed from EVA, which isn't meant for prolonged submersion, it's unsuitable for lengthy underwater photography sessions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with material described as EVA cannot be used for extreme underwater photography, as their water resistance has limits and they are not designed to be fully submerged for prolonged periods.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "eva", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_658", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is there an external water bottle pocket on the bag for carrying beverages?", "long_answer": "The bag comes equipped with an external water bottle pocket, allowing for easy access to a bottle for hydration purposes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_659", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the appearance of the bag noticeably that of a camera bag when carried?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed in a way that its appearance does not conspicuously resemble a traditional camera bag, which is appreciated by many users for the added security it provides while traveling.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_660", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack come with a satisfaction guarantee from Digital Goja?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack is indeed accompanied by a satisfaction guarantee from Digital Goja, which is valid for a period of 90 days and promises complete satisfaction.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_589", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can I swiftly access my camera for impromptu photos with this case?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the absence of a tripod mount on this case enables quick access to your camera, making it perfectly suited for effortlessly capturing those unplanned, spontaneous moments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_460", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm not trying to drop a fortune, but I need a camera case that won't get destroyed if it gets wet. What's the most budget-friendly waterproof case you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_461", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I've had enough of these annoying velcro closures! What's the cheapest camera case you have that doesn't have one of those?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'velcro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_661", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Does the case provide adequate protection for my camera in the event of a drop?", "long_answer": "While the case provides some level of protection against drops due to its construction, it is not as protective as a hard case, which could offer more substantial protection against impacts.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_662", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack provide comfort when worn?", "long_answer": "The backpack's comfort is noted by customers and is attributed to features such as the adjustable sternum strap and removable waistbelt, which enable even weight distribution.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_462", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I don't really care about water protection, but I love Case Logic's quality. Give me the case with the fewest pockets from them.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand = \"Case Logic\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand = \"Case Logic\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand = \"Case Logic\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Case Logic' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_663", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this backpack comfortably accommodate multiple professional-grade lenses and heavy camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed to be compact and is ideally suited for smaller SLR camera bodies and a few lenses. However, for those with multiple professional-grade lenses and heavier camera equipment, a larger and more robust backpack is recommended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_664", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is the foam in the Pelican 1200 Case designed to be customizable for various types of equipment?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case includes Pick N' Pluck foam, which allows users to customize it by removing sections to create a snug fit for their specific equipment shapes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_590", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will the Canon 55-250 usm lens fit in this case?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I am currently using this case for my Nikon D3500 and they are of similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 55-250 usm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 55-250 usm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_665", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the adjustable shoulder strap on this bag contribute to its comfort during prolonged use?", "long_answer": "The bag features a removable, adjustable shoulder strap that has been found by most users to be sufficient for comfortable wear when carried over an extended period.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_666", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the backpack have enough room to accommodate clothing for overnight trips?", "long_answer": "Although the backpack is designed primarily for carrying equipment, its size is sufficient to allow customers to pack personal items such as clothing, making it suitable for short, overnight trips.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_463", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm only interested in AmazonBasics stuff, and it's got to be water resistant. Get me the info on that, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'AmazonBasics' AND water_resistance = 'yes';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_464", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I have a thing for red and black, and I dig USA Gear stuff. Find me a camera case from them in either of those colors, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR` with asin: B005J09OXU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"black\") AND brand = \"USA Gear\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"black\") AND brand = \"USA Gear\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND (color = 'red' OR color = 'black');"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_591", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can the Canon T31 with a 250mm lens fit on this bag?", "long_answer": "Yes. My Nikon D3500 fits very well and your Canon T31 with a 250mm lens is of similar size to the D3500, hence, it should fit in this bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon T31 with 250mm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon T31 with 250mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_667", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Would you suggest this bag to someone based on customer feedback regarding its size and functionality?", "long_answer": "The bag has received high recommendations from customers who are satisfied with its size and functionality, making it a suitable choice to suggest to a friend if it aligns with their needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_465", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I've had enough with Ape Case stuff. Get me the cheapest camera case from any other brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Ape Case' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_668", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "What is the color of the bag's interior lining?", "long_answer": "The bag's interior is lined with a bright yellow color, which is intended to enhance the visibility of the bag's contents, providing a contrast that makes it easier for users to locate items inside the bag.", "short_answer": "bright yellow", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_669", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "How does the body-side access design of this bag enhance the security of its contents?", "long_answer": "The bag's body-side access feature enhances security by ensuring that the main compartment can only be opened and accessed when the bag is not being worn, which deters potential theft by making it difficult for someone to access the contents of the bag without the wearer’s knowledge.", "short_answer": "back-side opening", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_670", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the bag include a strap system for attaching a tripod?", "long_answer": "The bag comes with a strap system on the front, equipped with industrial strength hook-and-loop fasteners, which is designed for securing a tripod or similar bulky items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_592", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does this case fit a Canon t5i with a 300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it does. I use it for my Nikon D5000 with a battery grip which is similar in size to your Canon t5i with a 300mm lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_671", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Lowepro Fastpack 200 resemble a regular backpack in appearance?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Fastpack 200 is designed to look like a regular backpack rather than a conventional camera bag, which appeals to many customers due to the added security and improved aesthetics it provides.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_672", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is there a variety of color choices available for the interior lining of the bag?", "long_answer": "The bag's interior is exclusively lined with a bright orange color, which serves the practical purpose of making it easier to find dark-colored items inside. Currently, no alternative color options are offered for the interior lining of the bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_593", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this camera case protect my camera during kayaking?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is crafted from water-repellent materials like PVC or silicone. This enables you to go kayaking with your camera assured it's protected from splashes and short dips underwater.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof capabilities typically mean they are constructed from materials such as PVC or silicone that inherently resist water penetration, thereby safeguarding the camera equipment in wet conditions.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_466", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I don't want any red nonsense and I don't need it to be too roomy, but see if you can find me the cheapest camera case with two pockets or less.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"red\" AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"red\" AND pockets <= 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"red\" AND pockets <= 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color <> 'red' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_594", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for individuals who suffer from back pain while transporting heavy equipment?", "long_answer": "Certainly, it's designed for those mindful of back pain. The camera case features adaptable backpack straps that aid in evenly spreading the camera's weight and associated equipment across your back, potentially lessening discomfort and facilitating extended carrying of your gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps feature adjustable elements that accommodate varying body types, which is a testament to their design versatility for personalized comfort and support.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_595", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this bag fit my Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "I'm sorry but it might not fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and this bag fits it perfectly, but your camera setup is bigger than mine so it would be a tight squeeze if it does fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_596", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is it likely that I will encounter any discomfort when using this case to transport my camera equipment during extended hikes?", "long_answer": "Yes, the potential for discomfort exists during extended hikes should you opt for a camera case with mainly a hand grip for carrying. This method of carrying might not evenly distribute the weight of particularly heavy cameras and gear, resulting in strain. Hence, for such endeavors, it would be advisable to seek a case with extra support features.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip are not recommended for long-duration use or for transporting very heavy cameras and equipment, as this may result in discomfort or strain due to insufficient weight distribution and support.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_467", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I don't need any fancy features, no water protection nonsense and two pockets will suffice. Give me a simple camera case that meets my needs.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND pockets = 2;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_468", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm sticking with OP/TECH USA brand but I tan’t tolerate a camera case without water resistance. Can you recommend one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' AND water_resistance = 'yes';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_469", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I've only got 10 dollars and I need a case for my camera that can resist water. Which of your products can I afford?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND water_resistance = 'yes';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_673", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can the bag's interior compartments be reconfigured to fit different equipment sizes?", "long_answer": "Yes, the bag contains adjustable partitions that enable users to reorganize the interior space, optimizing the fit for various sizes and shapes of equipment to ensure they are tightly held and protected.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_470", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm looking for a Case Logic or Lowepro camera case that's water resistant, but please don't get me one with a lot of pockets. Find me the one with the fewest pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack` with asin: B000YA33DC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Lowepro\") AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Lowepro\") AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Lowepro\") AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'Lowepro') \nAND water_resistance = 'yes' \nORDER BY pockets ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_471", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I ain't a fan of drawstrings and too many pockets confuse me. Find me a budget-friendly camera case that has only one pocket and doesn't use drawstring closure, alright?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'drawstring' AND pockets = 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_597", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can the grip on this camera case aid in preventing the camera from slipping out of my hand?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera cases equipped with a grip feature are crafted from materials like rubber and silicone to provide enhanced slip resistance, ensuring a more secure hold and diminishing the likelihood of unintended drops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip feature materials such as rubber, foam, silicone, or leather, with options like rubber and silicone offering high slip resistance and leather providing a premium aesthetic.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_598", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm really into macro photography; does this case support that type of detailed work?", "long_answer": "Macro photography typically demands a highly stable camera to capture intricate details without any blurring, yet this camera case lacks a tripod attachment feature, which is crucial for achieving such stability.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_599", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Will this bag fit my Canon EOS Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit your Rebel T3. I use this with my Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens, and they have really similar dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_674", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Fastpack 200 backpack have a dedicated compartment for laptops?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack is primarily designed to carry camera equipment and does not feature a dedicated compartment for laptops. While fitting small laptops or tablets like iPads may be possible, it is not designed to securely accommodate all sizes of laptops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_600", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Will this case fit my Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. It fits my Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses perfectly and I believe the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip is similar in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_601", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this camera case capable of enduring long-distance travel without being burdensome?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is crafted for easy portability and durability during extended journeys, remaining unburdensome due to its nylon construction that keeps the case lightweight.\n", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_675", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can the internal dividers within the bag be repositioned or detached according to need?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with internal dividers that can be repositioned or detached as they attach with Velcro, providing flexibility for different custom configurations to accommodate various equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_676", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the bag considered well-made and durable by most users?", "long_answer": "The consensus among users is that the bag is well-constructed and durable, implying it provides adequate protection for camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_602", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Was this camera case crafted for traveling photographers who require swift setup at multiple sites?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this case is ideally suited for travel photographers who require the ability to move quickly and seize opportunities without the extra setup time that tripods require. Without a tripod attachment, the case appeals to those who prioritize portability and quickness over the stabilizing benefits of tripods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_677", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the Velcro padding in the camera bag effective in securing equipment inside the compartments?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is equipped with adjustable padded dividers that possess robust Velcro, which ensures that equipment remains securely fastened within the compartmentalized areas of the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_603", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case ensure sufficient protection for my equipment when I'm shooting in snowy environments?", "long_answer": "Although the case is meant to function in dry settings, the presence of snow can lead to moisture intrusion, possibly jeopardizing your equipment. This camera case isn't tailored for waterproofing, an important point to ponder if there's a chance your camera will be exposed to thawing snow. Opting for a waterproof or weather-resistant case is recommended for snowy environments to ensure total confidence in your gear's protection.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_678", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the bag's polyester/nylon exterior waterproof enough to protect gear during light rain?", "long_answer": "The bag's exterior is made of durable polyester/nylon material, which can provide some level of protection against light rain, keeping your gear safe in mild weather conditions. However, it is not marketed as fully waterproof, implying that for heavy rain, you might need to take extra precautions to ensure complete protection of your gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_604", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is it possible for me to conveniently modify the case to accommodate the various camera models I possess?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is crafted from a highly flexible material, ensuring it can adapt to accommodate different camera sizes and keep your equipment firmly in place.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_679", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the bag capable of accommodating multiple camera bodies?", "long_answer": "The bag is primarily designed to carry a single DSLR along with lenses and accessories. However, it has the potential to fit an extra camera body, depending on how large and how the equipment is arranged within the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_680", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 equipped with a built-in raincoat or waterproof cover?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 is not equipped with a built-in raincoat or all-weather cover, but it is constructed with fabric that is water-resistant, providing protection against light rain or moisture.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_605", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I like creating time-lapse videos; could this case benefit my workflow?", "long_answer": "For time-lapse photography, maintaining absolute stillness of your camera for long durations is essential, usually requiring the use of a tripod. Since this camera case lacks a tripod attachment, it might not be the best option for your time-lapse endeavors where steady positioning is paramount.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_472", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I ain't looking to salvage a sunken treasure, but a bit of water resistance wouldn't hurt. And keep it under 10 dollars. Can you find me a camera case like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND price < 10;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_606", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is this camera case dependable for protecting my gear in crowded areas?", "long_answer": "The camera bags offer ease of portability with their shoulder straps, yet in densely populated areas where the potential for harm or theft is greater, opting for a sturdier, lockable hard case is recommended for enhanced security.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap lack the capability to offer the same level of security as a locked carry-on or hard case, so they might not be the primary choice for transporting extremely valuable or sensitive equipment.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_607", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can this backpack fit a Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, this backpack can fit a Canon 10-22mm lens, and your lens is approximately the same size as that one, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_608", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for my professional photography shoots where I use a variety of accessories?", "long_answer": "When utilizing tools like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods for professional photography, this specific camera case might fall short of expectations, as it does not include a tripod attachment feature crucial for affixing these accessories to achieve ideal lighting conditions and image steadiness.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_681", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can the larger styles of the Soft Pouch accommodate a lens hood mounted backwards for storage?", "long_answer": "The larger variants of the Soft Pouch have been specifically designed to provide sufficient space in the lens compartment to allow for the storage of a lens hood in the reversed position.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_609", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can a Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens fit into this camera bag?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon L-series 100-400 and it fits well. The dimensions of your camera seems similar to mine so it would fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_610", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the camera case equipped to handle outdoor photography under diverse weather conditions?", "long_answer": "The case is made from a material that is capable of withstanding various outdoor conditions and offers some level of water resistance. Nevertheless, under severe weather circumstances, particularly those with significant water exposure, the case may not provide full protection without extra waterproofing steps.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_473", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I've got this thing for drawstring closures. So, find me a camera case like that. Make it the one with the least pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_611", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will the camera case boast a luxurious appearance that sets it apart?", "long_answer": "Since the camera case is crafted from nylon, it might not exude the same luxurious aesthetic as other premium materials such as leather. Nylon typically offers a casual and functional look that may not satisfy those in search of a distinctive, upscale aesthetic.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_474", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm looking for a specific camera case that can handle some water and comes in \"mica\" color. Got any options?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag` with asin: B009GYIKHQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"mica\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND color = \"mica\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND color = 'mica';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_612", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fit in this case? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Nikon D90 that fits well and the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime is similar in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_682", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can the top compartment of the bag accommodate large personal items?", "long_answer": "The top compartment is designed for smaller personal items and daypack essentials. However, it may not be sufficient for larger, bulkier items based on feedback from several customers.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_683", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does this bag serve well as a permanent solution for professional photographers to house their growing equipment collection?", "long_answer": "Although the bag provides robust protection and has a durable build, according to feedback from users, it may prove insufficient over time as they accumulate more photography equipment, leading to a need for a larger or more accommodating storage option.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_613", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can I fit my Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens in this backpack?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, no. I have tried fitting my Canon 10-22mm lens and it is a snug fit for that. The Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens is significantly larger, so it will not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_614", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does this camera case come with a feature that enables me to secure it to my tripod?", "long_answer": "Regrettably, the camera case does not include an integrated option for direct tripod attachment. Should a tripod be critical for your photographic endeavors, you may have to explore alternative cases or employ an additional camera support system in conjunction with this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_475", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I don't care if the case isn't waterproof, but I do want it to lock. What's the cheapest camera case you have with locks but without water resistance?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'locks' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_684", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG adequately sized for professional photographers with extensive equipment?", "long_answer": "The Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG is designed with a smaller capacity, making it ideal for amateur or hobbyist photographers who have fewer lenses and accessories. It may not be sufficient for professional photographers that require carrying a lot of equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_685", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this case produced by the official Canon brand?", "long_answer": "This case is indeed an official product of the Canon brand, indicating that it is manufactured or endorsed by Canon itself.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_615", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens fit this?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case will fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits well. Your Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens should have around the same dimensions as my camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon rebel xsi with a 200mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_616", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is this camera case capable of enduring long-distance travel without being burdensome?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is crafted for easy portability and is built to endure long journeys without becoming burdensome, thanks to its nylon construction that keeps the case light in weight.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_617", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can this backpack fit a Nikon D3200 with a Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8?", "long_answer": "Yes, this bag should fit your Nikon D3200 with a Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8. It accommodates my Canon 70D with a 70-250 lens perfectly, and your equipment should be around the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_686", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does this bag come with dedicated water bottle holders?", "long_answer": "This bag lacks designated water bottle holders. However, it does have sufficient space to accommodate a water bottle either within the main compartment alongside other items or in one of its pockets.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_618", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can I use this case for my Canon 600D?", "long_answer": "Yes, you can. I use it for my Nikon D90 and it fits well. The Canon 600D has a similar size to the Nikon D90, so it should work for you too.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Canon 600D has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Canon 600D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_687", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is there a dedicated laptop compartment in the Flipside 300 backpack model?", "long_answer": "The Flipside 300 backpack model lacks a specific compartment designed to hold and protect a laptop.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_619", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Should I bring my camera to the shore, would its case shield it from the corrosive sea breeze and any incidental splashes?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is engineered to guard not only against splashes of water but also the corrosive effects of salty sea breezes. However, please be aware that due to its waterproof features, the case lacks breathability, which means you may have to address potential internal condensation that might accumulate over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof features do not have the function of gas exchange, meaning that while they keep water out, air circulation is generally limited, which could potentially cause issues with condensation.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_688", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the bag designed to fit various body sizes and types comfortably?", "long_answer": "The bag comes equipped with adjustable shoulder and waist straps, which allows it to adapt to and fit a broad spectrum of body sizes. Many customers have reported that the sling bag fits comfortably across diverse users. However, it is important to note that, like any wearable item, the fit may still vary from person to person based on individual body shapes and sizes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_620", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 70-200 F4 lens? ", "long_answer": "Unfortunately no, it can't. I have a Nikon D3500 which fits well, but the Canon 70-200 F4 lens is larger than that so it may not fit properly.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_689", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "How well does the padding and reinforcement of this bag protect camera equipment from environmental factors and handling wear?", "long_answer": "The bag is constructed with full padding and reinforced design, which provides a high level of protection for camera equipment. It is specifically designed to guard against moisture, dust, and damage from regular handling, ensuring the safety of the contents inside.", "short_answer": "highly protective", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_621", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I frequently take wildlife photographs and occasionally, my equipment gets dropped. Will this case provide protection in those instances?", "long_answer": "Although the case shields your camera from water damage, it is crucial to recognize that to defend against drops, a case with shock-resistant materials or designated impact-cushioning padding is necessary to mitigate damage from falls.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof characteristics lack the capability to protect against substantial impacts or drops unless they also incorporate specific padding or shock-resistant materials.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_622", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I frequently need to swiftly reach for my camera to capture unplanned moments. Does this case accommodate such rapid access?", "long_answer": "Should you need quick access to your camera, it might be advisable to opt for a non-waterproof case. Although waterproof cases provide superb defense against environmental conditions, they often have seals that can impede ease of opening—potentially hindering your ability to rapidly access your camera.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof property are not suitable for situations where quick access and multiple openings of the case are necessary, as their protective seals can make them less convenient to open frequently.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_623", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can this case accommodate my Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to fit. I have a Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses and it fits well. Your camera setup seems to have similar dimensions, so it should be okay.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_624", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Could this case assist me in preventing missed key shots during high-speed events?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is designed for photographers who need to react swiftly, such as those covering events, thanks to the addition of a specialized tripod pocket. This feature enables you to quickly access and deploy your tripod, which can be crucial in seizing a pivotal moment or lamenting a missed opportunity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket typically mean that the product is designed with the needs of photographers in mind who require quick and easy access to their tripods for capturing stable and precise shots across various photography genres.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_690", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 bag comfortable for long hikes and extended travel on foot?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 bag, with its size and protective padding, tends to be larger and heavier than more casual bags, potentially making it cumbersome to some users for extended periods of carrying, especially during long hikes or when traveling without a vehicle. It is designed more for transporting a large quantity of equipment to a destination where the bag can be set down, rather than for ease of carrying over long distances.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_625", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is this camera case comfortable to carry while traversing diverse terrains during my photo shoots?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is designed for comfortable transport due to its backpack straps that ensure effortless and ergonomic carrying. This feature is particularly beneficial for photographers who frequently navigate various terrains while transporting their gear as part of their regular shooting activities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are ideally used for applications that involve movement across varying terrain or travel, lending themselves to be particularly useful for adventure and travel photographers.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_626", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this camera case protect my equipment should I encounter rain while on my photography excursions?", "long_answer": "The camera case you are looking at is crafted with a focus on being both lightweight and compact, perfect for use in dry settings. Its design prioritizes functionality in environments that are not prone to moisture, so it may not offer complete protection in the rain. If you often find yourself in wet situations, it would be wise to consider a case with waterproof features.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_691", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack designed for both daily use and travel?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 is versatile and can serve as an everyday storage solution for photography equipment as well as a dependable bag for travel purposes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_692", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does this backpack offer quick access to a camera for photographers?", "long_answer": "This backpack features a sling design that allows photographers to rapidly access their camera gear, making it a practical option for those who need to switch or retrieve equipment quickly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_627", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "As a travel photographer frequently scaling heights and traversing rugged terrain, would this case withstand such challenging conditions?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case comes with backpack straps that render it a dependable ally for photographers frequently climbing or navigating rugged terrain. This mode of carrying boosts stability and comfort, crucial for photographers facing ever-shifting landscapes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are ideally used for applications that involve movement across varying terrain or travel, lending themselves to be particularly useful for adventure and travel photographers.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_628", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Will this bag fit a Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8?", "long_answer": "I have this bag and it fits my Canon 10-22mm lens. Considering your Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar dimensions to my camera and lens, it should fit in this bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D3200 with Polaroid Grip and Tamron Sp17-50mmf2.8 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_629", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens?", "long_answer": "This bag works well with my Canon 70D that has a 18-200mm lens attached. If your T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens is around the same size, it should fit without any issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_476", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I'm kind of a brand snob, so only show me camera cases from Sony or Canon. Just the first one that pops up is fine.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Canon\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Canon\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'Canon') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_693", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the bag feature a shoulder strap that provides comfort for prolonged use?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with a wide, padded shoulder strap that is also detachable, which ensures comfort for users carrying it over extended periods, particularly targeting photographers who require mobility.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_694", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the waist strap on this product removable?", "long_answer": "The waist strap is designed to remain attached to the product and cannot be removed. However, it allows for adjustments and can be conveniently tucked away when not in use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_477", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I ain't planning on spending more than 10 dollars, and I don't need any extra pockets. So, what's the cheapest camera case ya got that suits my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_630", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is it safe to bring this camera case to the beach without concern for water damage?", "long_answer": "The camera case material provides a degree of protection against moisture, yet it isn't fully waterproof unless further treatments are applied. It's advisable to implement extra measures if you intend to subject it to challenging conditions like sand and saltwater.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_695", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the case designed to be waterproof?", "long_answer": "The case is not marketed as waterproof, meaning that while it may offer some defense against minor moisture, it is not made to withstand substantial water exposure such as heavy rainfall or being submerged in water.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_631", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is this camera case durable enough for long-distance travel without being burdensome?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is crafted for effortless portability and to endure long-distance journeys without becoming a burden, thanks to its nylon construction, which guarantees that the case stays light in weight.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_632", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can I rely on this case to keep my camera dry in the event of getting caught in a downpour?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is constructed with sealed zippers or roll-top closures that are purposefully designed to block water entry, ensuring your camera stays dry even if subjected to rainfall.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a waterproof design are known for incorporating sealed zippers or roll-top closures that prevent water intrusion, ensuring that the camera remains dry in challenging weather or aquatic environments.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_478", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I hate dealing with buckles and snaps, they're a pain! Get me the camera case that's got either a zipper or velcro as the closure type and is the cheapest.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'velcro') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_633", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is this case appropriate for photography in scenarios where holding the camera is not feasible, such as when operating a remote shutter?", "long_answer": "In scenarios requiring hands-free camera operation, such as using a remote shutter, the absence of a tripod mount on this camera case precludes it from offering sufficient stability on its own. For such instances, opting for a case that accommodates a tripod would be recommended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_634", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is it okay to bring this case on my desert photography journey to shield my camera from the heat?", "long_answer": "Considering the case is made of nylon, it is unsuitable for exceedingly high-temperature environments. Nylon does not possess sufficient insulation properties to protect against intense heat, which should be taken into account for settings such as deserts. A case designed with thermal protection would likely be a better fit for your requirements.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_635", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I frequently shoot in windy conditions; can this case still be used effectively?", "long_answer": "In breezy conditions, maintaining camera stability is crucial, particularly for types of photography such as landscapes, where even the slightest motion can result in blurred photographs. Regrettably, this case lacks a tripod attachment, potentially rendering it less suitable for securing your camera in these scenarios.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_479", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm eyeing a mica-colored camera case, but I'm not really into lots of pockets. Can you find me the one with the least pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag` with asin: B009GYIKHQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'mica' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_480", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm only interested in either green or black camera cases. Can you pinpoint the first product that comes in either of these colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"black\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"black\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('green', 'black') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_696", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the Canon bag designed to be waterproof?", "long_answer": "The Canon bag is not advertised with waterproof capabilities. It offers some protection against moisture, but it is not intended for situations where it would be exposed to large volumes of water.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_481", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm not a fan of bulky cases and I don't care for water resistance. What's the cheapest camera case you have with no more than one pocket?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets <= 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets <= 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_636", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is it safe to attach extra gear to my camera bag without risking damage?", "long_answer": "You should be aware that attaching additional gear to your camera case using the d-ring or clip fixtures must not surpass the carrying capacity specified by the manufacturer. Exceeding this limit could compromise the safety and structural integrity of the camera case and any connected accessories, including a tripod.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with d-ring or clip attachments cannot be used for exceeding the carrying capacity specified by manufacturers, as doing so may compromise the safety and integrity of both the camera case and the tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "d-ring or clip attachments", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_482", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I'm not really into Altura Photo, can you find me a red camera case from any other brand?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND color = \"red\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND color = \"red\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND brand != 'Altura Photo';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_697", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "What is the durability level of the Canon PSC-85 camera case with regard to everyday usage?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 camera case is manufactured using high-quality materials, which are capable of withstanding the wear and tear of regular use, thereby ensuring a durable form of protection for the camera.", "short_answer": "very durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_698", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Does the case provide a dedicated space for storing extra batteries or memory cards?", "long_answer": "The case has a compact design, but it features a small pocket that can accommodate additional batteries or a memory card, providing storage for these accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_637", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Nikon D5000?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Nikon D3500 which fits perfectly in this case and the D5000 is similar in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Nikon D5000 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Nikon D5000 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_483", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Alright, I've got a thing against yellow, so I don't want any yellow camera cases. Also, let's keep it pretty minimal...maybe the one with the fewest pockets? Give me the next best option.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'yellow' \nORDER BY pockets ASC \nLIMIT 1 OFFSET 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_699", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is the Pelican 1120 Case equipped with wheels for transportation?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1120 Case is not equipped with wheels. However, it is designed to be easily portable and comes with a carrying handle to facilitate transportation.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_638", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the case sturdy enough to endure regular use outdoors?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is crafted from nylon fabric, renowned for its substantial tensile strength. Consequently, it exhibits resistance to tearing and stretching, guaranteeing long-lasting durability during frequent outdoor activities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_700", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Are the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack shoulder straps comfortable for wearing throughout the entire day?", "long_answer": "The majority of users report that the shoulder straps on the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack are comfortable for all-day wear. The straps are designed in such a way that they help to distribute the weight evenly across the shoulders, reducing the potential for discomfort.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_484", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I don't want an orange case. Give me the one with the smallest number of pockets that isn't orange.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'orange' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_639", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is there a feature on this camera case that permits convenient portability without sacrificing too much style?", "long_answer": "This camera case comes with a shoulder strap designed for convenience and ease of use in daily carrying. Yet, it is worth mentioning that its design prioritizes practicality over a sleek or luxurious appearance, which may not suit the taste of all users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap fail to meet the requirements for users seeking a fashionable accessory, as the strap's primary focus is on functionality and comfort over luxury aesthetics.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_701", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the camera compartment come with additional padding on the bottom?", "long_answer": "The camera compartment does not come equipped with extra padding on the bottom, suggesting that additional protective measures should be taken when storing fragile lenses or equipment in that part of the bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_702", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does the bag offer features to enhance carrying comfort?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with comfort in mind, featuring a well-made, padded shoulder strap and an optional hidden waist belt for added support when needed.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_640", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does this camera case have an integrated feature for attaching it to my tripod?", "long_answer": "Regrettably, this camera case does not include an integrated mechanism for direct tripod attachment. Should a tripod be crucial for your photography work, you may need to look at alternative cases or employ an additional camera support system in conjunction with this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_641", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can I instantly access my camera while covering fast-paced sports events?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case isn't suitable for scenarios requiring quick access to your camera, like capturing high-speed sports action. Its design, featuring backpack straps, necessitates removing the entire backpack to reach your equipment, potentially leading to missed opportunities in fast-moving shooting contexts.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps cannot be used for scenarios where a quick, one-handed operation or access is necessary such as in certain types of event photography, since taking off the backpack can be more time-consuming than simply swinging a shoulder bag around.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_485", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "No fluff or clutter for me, got it? I want a camera case with either a lock or a zipper but no pockets. Get me one now.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'zipper') AND pockets = 0;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_703", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Are the interior dividers of the backpack adjustable to accommodate different camera sizes?", "long_answer": "The backpack's interior dividers are fully customizable thanks to their Velcro design, which enables the user to rearrange and tailor the space to securely fit a variety of camera sizes and related accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_642", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will this bag fit my Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not, the bag fits my Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens perfectly, but it appears that your lens is larger than the 18-200mm lens, and hence may not fit in this bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_486", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm not a fan of too many pockets and I don't want to spend a fortune. Show me the cheapest camera case you got with one pocket or less and under a hundred dollars.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND price < 100 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_643", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Could this camera case assist in freeing up my hands for other equipment?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case with backpack straps provides the ease of transporting your equipment on your back, allowing your hands to be unencumbered to handle additional photographic gear or to maneuver within your shooting surroundings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are known for facilitating hands-free operation, thus enabling photographers to move more freely and focus on capturing images without the encumbrance of holding onto their case.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_704", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Does the bag have an adjustable shoulder strap with comfort features for prolonged use?", "long_answer": "The bag comes with an adjustable shoulder strap featuring a cam lock buckle. It also includes a padded shoulder pad, which is removable and has a non-slip patch, all of which contribute to comfort during extended periods of wearing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_487", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm outdoors a lot, and it can get wet. I want a green camera case, and it has to be water resistant. Oh, and I'm not too fussed about pockets - give me the one with the fewest.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_705", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is there a shoulder strap included with this case for carrying?", "long_answer": "The case is equipped with a shoulder strap, making it convenient to carry.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_644", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I like to snap pictures rapidly without fussing over equipment setup; would this camera case suit my needs?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is perfect for photographers such as yourself who prioritize speed and simplicity. Omitting a tripod attachment, it is crafted to be light and handy, catering to those rapid, spontaneous shots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_706", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the camera case available in multiple sizes?", "long_answer": "The camera case being discussed is available in a medium size. To determine if this case will fit your camera, you should compare the internal dimensions provided in the product listing with the dimensions of your camera.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_707", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is the Soft Pouch capable of accommodating a camera with a telephoto lens up to 10 inches in length?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch is designed to fit cameras with lenses up to 10 inches in length, thereby offering a suitable protective option for some camera setups equipped with a telephoto lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_645", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "As a professional photographer, ought I to consider this camera case for my field assignments?", "long_answer": "As a professional who often operates in diverse shooting settings and requires exact camera placement, this specific camera case may not be ideal due to its absence of a tripod attachment. Such a feature is commonly suggested for professionals to achieve the best outcomes in specialized photographic conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_708", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG camera bag less expensive than its market counterparts?", "long_answer": "Based on customer testimonials, the Canon 200DG camera bag is considered a great value and is noted to be less expensive in comparison to similar camera bags available at retail stores.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_709", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does this camera sling's design offer protection against theft in crowded environments?", "long_answer": "The camera sling features a design where the main compartment zipper is placed against the wearer's back, deterring potential thieves. Additional safety can be achieved by wearing the sling in front, as recommended by some users, when in unfamiliar or densely populated areas.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_710", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 camera bag large enough to accommodate the extensive equipment of a professional photographer?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 camera bag is designed primarily for amateur photographers or professionals seeking a more compact solution for light travel or casual use, which may not be sufficient for professional photographers with a significant amount of gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_488", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I just cannot stand mica-colored stuff and I prefer zipper closures. Which camera case fits that criteria and also has the fewest pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" AND closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" AND closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"mica\" AND closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'mica' AND closure_type = 'zipper' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_489", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm bored of all these black camera cases. Show me the first product you have that's something different!", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'black' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_646", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can I safely assume that my camera will remain undamaged after spending a day at the beach with this case?", "long_answer": "Certainly, your camera is expected to withstand water exposure, including ocean spray or unintended submersion, when equipped with this waterproof camera case. Nevertheless, it's important to emphasize that although the case provides protection against water and sand intrusion, it is not entirely crush-proof. Care should be taken to avoid scenarios where the case could be subjected to substantial force or pressure, as this could lead to damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof elements fail to meet the requirements for being entirely crush-proof; while they can protect against water, they may not withstand being subjected to heavy weights or forces without additional rigid structural features.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_647", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Will this bag accommodate a Canon Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use mine for a Nikon D3500, and the Canon Rebel T3 is similar in size, so it should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_648", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. My Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses fits into this case comfortably, and your camera model is roughly the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_711", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the bag have compartments specifically designed to hold extra lenses?", "long_answer": "The bag offers two large side compartments, each measuring 6 inches by 4 inches by 3.5 inches, which are made to accommodate additional lenses along with other accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_649", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this case appropriate for outdoor photography, where frequent adjustments to storage configurations are necessary?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the material is perfect for outdoor photography due to its flexibility, which enables you to effortlessly adjust the storage setups to meet your specific needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_712", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack designed to meet the needs of professional photo-hikers?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is noted for its durability and comfort, features that cater to the requirements of professional photo-hikers engaging in active outdoor photography.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_650", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for a photographer who needs to be prepared to quickly capture action shots?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is perfectly designed for photographers needing to be ready in an instant. It features a specialized tripod pocket that allows for swift and convenient retrieval of your tripod, ensuring you can set up quickly for action shots without any hassle with your equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket are known for their convenience in allowing for quick attachment and detachment of tripods, which is particularly beneficial in dynamic shooting situations where setting up the shot swiftly is crucial.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_713", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Can the Canon SLR Gadget Bag accommodate camera brands other than Canon EOS or Rebel?", "long_answer": "Although primarily designed for Canon EOS or Rebel cameras, the Canon SLR Gadget Bag features adjustable dividers, which provide the flexibility to potentially house other camera brands. However, it is essential to verify that the dimensions of the non-Canon camera are compatible with the bag's space.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_651", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will this backpack fit my Canon Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits perfectly. Your Canon Rebel T3 is similar in size so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_714", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the backpack designed for comfortable all-day use when fully loaded?", "long_answer": "The backpack is generally reported by users to be comfortable for all-day use, even when it is fully packed with items. The ease of rotation and quick access to gear due to its sling design contributes to the comfort level, reducing potential discomfort from prolonged use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_652", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will this backpack be suitable for my Canon EOS Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be. I have a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens and it fits well. Your Canon EOS Rebel T3 has similar size with my kit so it should also fit the backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_490", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm not looking for anything fancy, just a basic OP/TECH USA camera case with the least pockets and no water resistance. Can you get me that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_491", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Hey, I need a camera case that's either yellow or red, and either has locks or uses a drawstring. Can you show me what we got in that category?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"yellow\", \"red\") AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"yellow\", \"red\") AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (color = 'yellow' OR color = 'red') \nAND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'drawstring');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_715", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 backpack capable of holding a 15.6 inch laptop?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 backpack is specifically designed to hold laptops up to 16 inches, which means that it can accommodate a 15.6-inch laptop, albeit with a snug fit reported by some customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_653", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I frequently go on hikes and must minimize my camera equipment; would this camera case be appropriate for such use?", "long_answer": "While hiking, it's crucial to carry only the essentials. That said, this camera case includes a specific pocket for a tripod, which may conflict with your intent to maintain a simplified and light load. In this context, a smaller camera case could be more suitable for your needs.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket fail to meet the requirements for a compact storage solution when space is a premium, such as for photographers needing to adhere to strict travel luggage constraints.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_716", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Do the zippers or other components of the product have a high failure rate?", "long_answer": "A small number of users have reported problems with the zippers, but overall, most feedback indicates that under typical conditions, the bag's components, including zippers, are durable and less likely to break.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_654", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this case accommodate my Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case should fit your Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and they fit perfectly. Considering that your camera and lens sizes are similar to mine, it will likewise fit in the case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_492", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Look, I'm trying to find a camera case in either teal or purple but I don't want to overspend. Find me the cheapest one in these colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"purple\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"purple\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"purple\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('teal', 'purple') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_655", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm somewhat prone to clumsiness and am concerned about the possibility of the case tearing. Is it durable enough to mitigate that risk?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the nylon fabric used to create this camera case is highly prized for its tear-resistant properties. Such durability renders it an ideal selection for individuals wary of damage due to inadvertent mishandling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_656", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Though I'm merely a photography enthusiast, I'm wondering whether this case might restrict me somehow when shooting outdoors.", "long_answer": "Though the case might satisfy a hobbyist for everyday use, the lack of a tripod mount might pose constraints during outdoor photography sessions where a tripod is essential. This becomes particularly relevant as your interest in photography expands to situations where camera steadiness is vital for achieving the intended image.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_657", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I intend to photograph a waterfall; will this case protect my camera from moisture?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is constructed from waterproof materials like PVC or silicone, ensuring superb resistance to water and safeguarding your camera from moisture when in close proximity to waterfalls.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof capabilities typically mean they are constructed from materials such as PVC or silicone that inherently resist water penetration, thereby safeguarding the camera equipment in wet conditions.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_658", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I frequently embark on extended photography treks; is this camera case crafted for comfort during such activities?", "long_answer": "For extended treks, consider a camera case designed to distribute your equipment's weight evenly. A case equipped with a belt loop might not offer optimal comfort for bearing heavier loads, and therefore, it might not be the best option for your photography excursions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop are not suitable for individuals who prefer to carry multiple heavy lenses and accessories due to the limited load capacity that a single belt loop may offer.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_717", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "What is the size classification of the Canon SLR Gadget Bag for EOS or Rebel Cameras according to user feedback?", "long_answer": "The Canon SLR Gadget Bag for EOS or Rebel Cameras is generally regarded by users as fairly large, making it more appropriate for individuals who either possess a substantial amount of equipment or desire additional space to accommodate future acquisitions.", "short_answer": "Large", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_659", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is this camera case sufficient for safeguarding my equipment throughout strenuous outdoor activities?", "long_answer": "When engaging in intense outdoor activities, you may opt for a camera case that offers a solid structure for enhanced protection. Cases constructed from nylon tend to possess a degree of flexibility, which could fall short in delivering the structural rigidity you desire for these circumstances.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_660", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can it fit Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens? ", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, it doesn't. I have a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens which fits inside it but I think the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens is bigger than my camera hence it won't fit into it.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_718", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Does the camera's case provide a secure and tight fit for the camera?", "long_answer": "The case is designed to fit the camera securely, providing a snug fit that ensures good protection with minimal excess space, as commonly described by users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_719", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "What is the maximum number of camera bodies that the bag can accommodate?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to hold one camera body with multiple lenses; however, some customers have successfully fit two camera bodies into the bag with a few lenses, subject to the sizes of the camera bodies and lenses.", "short_answer": "two", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_493", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I don't need anything fancy like water resistance, just a plain camera case will do. Also, I prefer \"Canon\" or \"AmazonBasics\". What's the cheapest you can offer?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"AmazonBasics\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"AmazonBasics\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Canon', 'AmazonBasics') AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_720", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the backpack have a dedicated holder suitable for carrying a tripod?", "long_answer": "The backpack comes equipped with an exterior holder that is specifically designed to carry tripods or monopods. It is particularly adept at holding smaller tripods, although it might not be large enough to accommodate bigger tripods with ease.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_661", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Would you recommend this camera case for traveling with my complete photography equipment?", "long_answer": "Although this camera case could serve well for travel, should your photography gear feature a weighty or sizeable tripod, the d-ring or clip attachments might not support the extra load. It is recommended to opt for a case equipped with sturdier tripod attachment facilities for such apparatus.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with d-ring or clip attachments lack the capability to adjust to exceptionally heavy or bulky tripods that surpass the designed weight limit, and therefore are not intended for use with specialized, heavyweight photographic equipment.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "d-ring or clip attachments", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_721", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the Fastpack 200 be conveniently used for air travel?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 is designed with features conducive to air travel, such as its durable build and compact size that fits either under the seat or in the overhead compartment. Additionally, it is equipped with padded shoulder straps to enhance comfort while navigating through airports.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_494", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I can't stand all these bulky camera cases. I just need something simple, maybe just one pocket, and I don't want to fork out more than 100 dollars. Show me the cheapest option you got that meets these specs.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND price < 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND price < 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 1 AND price <= 100 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_662", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Will this camera case be convenient to carry on extended hikes?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is designed to be both lightweight and compact, making it a superb option for lengthy treks where carrying extra weight or bulk is undesirable. It is engineered to provide convenience and practicality without significantly increasing your burden, aligning perfectly with the requirements of active and mobile photography.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_495", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I can't stand orange, and I need a case that either locks or has a drawstring. Also, too many pockets just get confusing. What's the simplest one you got that fits those requirements?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color <> 'orange' AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM camera_cases WHERE color <> 'orange' AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'drawstring'));"}}
{"id": "search_qa_496", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I ain't got cash to blow, and honestly, I only trust cases with locks or drawstrings. Help me find the cheapest one available that doesn't go over 10 bucks.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_663", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this case accommodate 50-500 Sigma lenses?", "long_answer": "Yes, it would. I've used this case with my Canon 10-22mm lens and it fits perfectly. Considering that the Canon and the 50-500 Sigma are of similar size, it should work just fine for you.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_722", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "How convenient is the access to equipment in the ACPRO2000 camera bag when moving around?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 camera bag is primarily designed for protecting and transporting equipment rather than quick access. To reach your gear, you will need to unbuckle and unzip several compartments, which can be somewhat time-consuming.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_497", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I hate to fumble around for things. Give me a camera case with no pockets and a locking feature. What's the product ID for that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type = \"locks\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND closure_type = \"locks\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND closure_type = 'locks';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_664", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "If I frequently use the camera case near bodies of water, will the protective quality diminish more rapidly?", "long_answer": "Regular exposure to aquatic environments may accelerate the deterioration of water resistance, thus necessitating more frequent application of waterproofing treatments to maintain the camera case's water-resistant properties.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof attributes feature maintenance requirements such as periodic treatments with water repellent sprays to maintain their high protection level against water.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_665", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Does the camera case utilize space efficiently for use as carry-on luggage on airplanes?", "long_answer": "Considering the size limitations frequently imposed on carry-on baggage for flights, this camera case may not be the optimal choice for space efficiency given its specialized tripod pocket, which occupies additional space and could pose difficulties when attempting to fit into compact overhead bins or under-seat storage areas.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket fail to meet the requirements for a compact storage solution when space is a premium, such as for photographers needing to adhere to strict travel luggage constraints.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_498", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Look, I am only interested in camera cases from either Pelican or OP/TECH USA and I don't need a whole lot of pockets. Tell me which one has the least.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"OP/TECH USA\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"OP/TECH USA\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Pelican', 'OP/TECH USA') \nORDER BY pockets ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_723", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can a DSLR with an attached lens fit inside the backpack given its internal dimensions?", "long_answer": "The backpack with internal dimensions measuring 7.5 inches in length, 5 inches in width, and 12 inches in height, offers ample space to accommodate a DSLR camera with an attached lens, and potentially extra lenses, subject to the dimensions of the specific equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_666", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is this case appropriate for photography scenarios in which I am unable to hold the camera, such as when using a remote shutter?", "long_answer": "In circumstances that require hands-free camera operation, such as using a remote shutter, the absence of a tripod mount on this camera case prevents it from offering adequate stability on its own. It is recommended to use a case that accommodates a tripod for such situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_667", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I am looking for a camera case that has a premium touch feel; would you suggest this one?", "long_answer": "The texture of this camera case might not align with your expectations of a 'premium touch' since it's constructed from nylon. While nylon offers durability and function, it lacks the sumptuous sensation associated with high-end materials like leather.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_668", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can I fit a Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom in this bag?", "long_answer": "Yes, a Canon 70D with 135mm zoom should fit. I have a Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses which is of similar size, and those fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "search_qa_499", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Look, I need a black camera case with either locks or a drawstring. What's the cheapest option you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)` with asin: B0002INQT2", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"black\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"black\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"black\" AND closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'black' \nAND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_669", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not. I own a Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses which fits, and my setup is smaller than a Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens. So your camera would not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_670", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Will this bag accommodate my Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it just fits. Your xsi with 55-250mm lens is a bit longer, so it wouldn't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_500", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I've got a thing for USA Gear. Give me the cheapest camera case they've got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR` with asin: B005J09OXU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_671", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can the camera case provide complete protection for my equipment during heavy rainfall?", "long_answer": "Although the camera case is crafted from robust material, it should be underscored that cases made from this material typically offer only elementary water resistance. To achieve full waterproofing, supplementary measures must be undertaken to guarantee that your gear remains dry during intense rainfall.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_501", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Look, I've only got 30 dollars to spare and I'm after a camera case with a zipper. Find me the cheapest one you've got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND closure_type = \"zipper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND closure_type = \"zipper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND closure_type = 'zipper' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_502", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Stop trying to push Altura Photo on me. I need a camera case with no more than two pockets from any other brand. What’s my best option here?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND pockets <= 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND pockets <= 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Altura Photo' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_724", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "In the event of a drop, does the case offer sufficient protection for the camera?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback suggests that the case's padding and construction afford a reasonable level of protection for the camera when it is accidentally dropped.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_725", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the bag's design provide comfort for prolonged wearing?", "long_answer": "The bag features adjustable shoulder and waist straps, which are designed to offer comfort when worn for an extended time. It is designed similar to a backpack, allowing it to be swung around for easy access, and includes a padded strap to ease shoulder pressure.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_726", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Does the camera case provide easy access to the camera and lenses?", "long_answer": "The camera case is designed for convenient accessibility, featuring a drawstring closure which can be easily opened for quick access. Additionally, the excess drawstring fabric can be folded down to keep the top of the case open between shots, thus facilitating rapid access to equipment when necessary.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_503", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I've got a thing for Pelican brand, but don't need the water resistance stuff. What's the cheapest case you've got from them?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Pelican' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_672", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Could this camera case aid in alleviating fatigue during prolonged outdoor photography sessions?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case featuring backpack straps is designed to evenly distribute weight across your shoulders, significantly lessening fatigue during extended outdoor photo sessions. Its ergonomic design is intended to provide support for adventure photographers navigating various terrains.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are ideally used for applications that involve movement across varying terrain or travel, lending themselves to be particularly useful for adventure and travel photographers.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_727", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can the Ape Case ACPRO2000 withstand frequent travel and rough handling?", "long_answer": "User feedback suggests that the Ape Case ACPRO2000 is considered durable and well-made, which makes it suitable for enduring the tough conditions associated with frequent travel and rough handling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_673", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the Canon Rebel with a 55-200 lens fit in this bag?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, no. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens and it fits perfectly but your lens is larger, so it won't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_728", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can the Canon logo on the bag be removed for increased security?", "long_answer": "The Canon logo on the bag is securely attached and cannot be removed without personal modification, as it is not designed to be detachable by default.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_674", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can a Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens fit into this case?", "long_answer": "No, I doubt if it will. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens, and it fits well with the case. Your lens is longer, so it may not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_729", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the camera bag come with a specialized compartment for carrying a tripod or monopod?", "long_answer": "The camera bag features an exterior holder that is specifically designed for the purpose of securing a tripod or monopod, providing a convenient solution for photographers who need to carry their support equipment alongside their camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_730", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is a rain cover included with the purchase of this camera backpack?", "long_answer": "The camera backpack does not include a rain cover as part of its standard accessories. Customers who require protection against the elements typically have to buy a separate weather cover.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_504", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm a big fan of Ape Case and love their velcro closure type. What's the cheapest model you got that matches what I'm looking for?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" AND closure_type = \"velcro\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" AND closure_type = \"velcro\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" AND closure_type = \"velcro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Ape Case' AND closure_type = 'velcro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_731", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Does the carrying case for this product have a compact design?", "long_answer": "The carrying case is considered to be bulkier than some customers anticipated, offering robust protection at the expense of fitting comfortably into smaller bags, owing to its considerable width. ", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_675", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I occasionally feel discomfort while toting bags; is this camera case designed for comfort during prolonged periods of carrying?", "long_answer": "Should you suffer from a medical condition or pain that exacerbates when bearing weight on one side, a camera case with a shoulder strap might prove to be uncomfortable over extended periods. It's wise to explore alternative carrying solutions that more equally distribute the weight throughout your body.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not suitable for users who may have medical conditions or pain that is exacerbated by carrying weight on one side of the body; other carrying options may be better in these cases.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_732", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the bag suitable for outdoor photography and resistant to various weather conditions?", "long_answer": "The bag is particularly constructed to endure the challenges of outdoor adventures, with a rugged design complemented by a waterproof base that offers protection against the elements, making it suitable for outdoor photography.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_733", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can I quickly access my camera without removing the bag?", "long_answer": "The sling design of the bag is specifically made to rotate to the front of your body, enabling you to have immediate access to your camera, negating the need to take off the bag to reach your camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_676", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this case fit my a77 with a vertical grip and heavy zoom lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, I believe it should. It perfectly accommodates my Nikon D90 and your a77 with vertical grip and heavy zoom has a similar size to that.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the a77 with vertical grip and heavy zoom has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the a77 with vertical grip and heavy zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_677", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this fit my Canon 1100D?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. My Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens fits perfectly. Given that the Canon 1100D has similar dimensions, it should fit as well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon 1100D has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon 1100D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_505", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm all about easy access and extra storage. What's the zipper camera case you have with the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'zipper' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_678", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Can I carry the camera case with me while shooting on the go?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is equipped with backpack straps for comfortable wear on your back, which facilitates hands-free use. This feature enables you to move with greater freedom and concentrate on capturing images without manually holding your case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are known for facilitating hands-free operation, thus enabling photographers to move more freely and focus on capturing images without the encumbrance of holding onto their case.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_679", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag carry Canon Powershot SX50 HS?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it for my Canon 70D with a 18-55mm lens and it fits great. The Canon Powershot SX50 HS is about the same size, so it should also fit in this bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon Powershot SX50 HS has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon Powershot SX50 HS fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_680", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, I have a Canon 10-22mm lens that fits well in this case, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom is around the same size, so it should fit fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_506", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I hate fumbling with extra pockets. Find me an \"Altura Photo\" camera case that doesn't have any.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND pockets = 0;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_681", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can the case protect my camera from snow and thawing ice during winter photography?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the case is designed to protect your camera from snow and ice, ensuring that any melting snow won't seep in and lead to water damage. However, due to the waterproof feature's limitation on air circulation, be mindful of potential condensation inside the case caused by temperature fluctuations during your winter photo shoots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof features do not have the function of gas exchange, meaning that while they keep water out, air circulation is generally limited, which could potentially cause issues with condensation.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_507", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I don't care about the water stuff. Just get me a camera case that closes with a drawstring.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_682", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Does this case contain fewer complex parts that might break or require maintenance?", "long_answer": "Indeed, as this camera case is not intended to be waterproof, it typically lacks intricate seals or locking mechanisms. Consequently, there are fewer components that may malfunction or necessitate maintenance as time progresses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_508", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm only interested in Lowepro and AmazonBasics brands, don't show me anything orange though! What's the first product you got that meets these criteria?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack` with asin: B000YA33DC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND NOT color = \"orange\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND NOT color = \"orange\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Lowepro', 'AmazonBasics') AND color != 'orange' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_509", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm looking for a bit of a statement piece. Got any camera cases in purple or orange? Show me the first one you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"orange\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"orange\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('purple', 'orange') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_683", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is this case compatible with my Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, your Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip should fit perfectly in this case as it has a similar size to the Nikon D5000 with battery grip, which I have confirmed fits well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_684", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is there a risk of the camera case being stolen while I am traveling?", "long_answer": "Although no camera case can ensure absolute protection from theft, exercise caution with cases featuring a dedicated tripod compartment. Their unique shape can inadvertently signal you're transporting high-value equipment, potentially elevating the risk of theft.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket lack the capability to remain sleek and inconspicuous, as the protrusion or shape of the pocket may reveal the storage of valuable equipment, potentially drawing unwanted attention.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_734", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Lowepro Flipside 300 capable of accommodating a pro DSLR with an attached large lens?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is specifically designed to hold a professional DSLR camera with a large lens, for example, an 80-200mm f/2.8, and provides additional space for other camera accessories such as extra lenses or flash units.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_735", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "What is the weight of the camera sling?", "long_answer": "The weight of the camera sling is roughly 1.2 pounds, which is considered to be relatively light, ensuring ease of carrying for camera equipment.", "short_answer": "1.2 pounds", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_685", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is this case suitable for my camera if my primary focus is long-exposure photography necessitating the use of a tripod?", "long_answer": "In long-exposure photography where stable camera support is essential, this case may not be the ideal choice due to the lack of an integrated tripod mounting feature. To use a tripod, you'd need to remove your camera from the case and mount it separately.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_686", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Will this case fit my 6D w/24-105mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The bag fits my Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens perfectly and your 6D w/24-105mm lens has a similar size, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the 6D w/24-105mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the 6D w/24-105mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_736", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the bag constructed from durable material and also weatherproof?", "long_answer": "The bag is crafted using sturdy materials, featuring robust stitching and durable straps, contributing to its durability. However, its weatherproof capabilities may be limited, as it does not come equipped with a rain cover, which might be a concern for users requiring protection from the elements.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_737", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "How secure is the Ape Case backpack against theft due to its design features?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case backpack includes design features such as multiple buckles and zippers that enhance its security, creating a more theft-resistant backpack, particularly in areas where there is a high population density.", "short_answer": "especially secure", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_510", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm not one for extra pockets and I need my cases to be water-resistant. Get me your cheapest option for a camera case that fits these needs.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets <= 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets <= 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 1 AND water_resistance = 'yes' \nORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_687", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is the material of the camera case susceptible to damage?", "long_answer": "The camera case is resistant to damage, thanks to its neoprene construction. Renowned for its durability, neoprene excels in withstanding different types of wear and tear, guaranteeing that your case remains in good condition over numerous uses.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with neoprene material are known for their durability, offering long-term resistance to wear and tear, which is a valuable trait for photographers who frequently travel and use their camera gear in various rough conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "neoprene", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_511", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case that's either red or green and doesn't cost more than a hundred. Can you get me the product id for the first one that meets these conditions?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"green\") AND price <= 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"green\") AND price <= 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('red', 'green') AND price <= 100\nORDER BY product_id \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_738", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is the Ape Case Cubeze 37 insert compatible with non-specialized bags, such as standard backpacks or messenger bags?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze 37 insert is designed with versatility in mind and can be utilized within various common bags including standard backpacks, messenger bags, and other luggage types. Its padded design and drawstring closure feature provide protection and a secure fit for camera gear, effectively transforming these everyday bags into camera-safe storage options.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_688", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this camera case a suitable option for those who prioritize convenience above robust protection against harsh environmental conditions?", "long_answer": "Certainly, if you prioritize convenience and ease of access above shielding from water and harsh environmental factors, this camera case is an appropriate option. It forgoes waterproofing to allow for easier, more intuitive access to your camera gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_689", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can this pouch accommodate a Canon EOS Rebel T3i? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Nikon D90 which is nearly the same size as the Canon EOS Rebel T3i and it fits perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_739", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is this bag capable of fitting a camera with a battery grip attached?", "long_answer": "The bag has been used by numerous customers to carry cameras equipped with a battery grip, suggesting that there is typically enough space to accommodate the additional size. Nonetheless, the compatibility can vary based on the particular camera model and the dimensions of the battery grip.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_512", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I don't need any fancy water-resistant stuff, just something reasonably priced. What's your most affordable non-water-resistant camera case that's priced around or below your average?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no'\nORDER BY price\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_740", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the backpack provide protection against water without additional coverage?", "long_answer": "The backpack is constructed with a durable, water-resistant outer material that offers resistance to moisture and protection from wear. Nonetheless, in conditions with heavy rain, the backpack's protection may be insufficient, and it is recommended to use extra rain protection.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_741", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the internal compartments of the camera bag be adjusted to accommodate different pieces of camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is equipped with adjustable padded dividers, which means that you can easily customize the interior compartments to fit various sizes and shapes of camera equipment securely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_742", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "What type of closure mechanism does the case's flap cover use?", "long_answer": "The case's flap cover utilizes non-marring snaps, which ensure a secure closure at the bottom of the pouch.", "short_answer": "non-marring snaps", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_743", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Does the backpack provide comfort for extended wearing due to its design?", "long_answer": "The backpack features padded shoulder straps and a padded back, which are designed to offer comfort during extended periods of wear. However, it's important to note that the perception of comfort is subjective and can differ among individuals depending on their preferences and physical build.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_744", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is the case's weight comfortable for daily use?", "long_answer": "The case is specifically designed for extreme protection, resulting in a sturdier and consequently heavier build. This indicates that while it provides high-level protection, it may not be ideal for those who prioritize lightweight portability.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_513", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm only interested in Pelican or Canon. Can you pull up the first camera case you find from either of these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Canon\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Canon\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Pelican', 'Canon') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_745", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Does the Canon PSC-85 case design ensure a secure grip while removing the camera?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 case is designed with a soft lining that enables the camera to be inserted and removed with ease, thus ensuring that users can maintain a good grip on the camera during this process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_746", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is the Pelican 1200 Case suitable for secure firearm storage?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Pelican 1200 Case is specifically designed for such purposes, as customers often use it to securely store and transport firearms. The internal foam can be customized to fit the contours of a firearm, ensuring a tight fit, and the case has provisions to add a lock for additional security measures.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_514", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I've got a ton of stuff to cart around, but I don't need loads of pockets and I need something water-resistant. Find me your cheapest camera case that fits these requirements.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_747", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is this camera case compatible with all Sony digital camera models?", "long_answer": "The case is specifically designed for slim Cyber-shot models, and a proper fit can only be ensured by comparing the camera's dimensions with the case's interior measurements, which are 4.38 inches in length, 3 inches in width, and 3 inches in height.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_690", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I require a case that can withstand the demands of fieldwork and accommodate all my photography gear. Is this the suitable option?", "long_answer": "This camera case might not be adequate for demanding fieldwork involving diverse equipment due to the absence of a vital tripod attachment feature. Such a feature is essential for the safe transport and expedient setup of widely used professional photography gear, including tripods and additional lighting.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_691", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can I easily detach the camera case in crowded areas such as concerts or festivals?", "long_answer": "No, a camera case equipped with a belt loop as a carrying feature may not be the ideal selection for crowded venues. Rapid detachment of the camera case from a belt can prove impractical in densely filled events, rendering it a less advisable choice for professional purposes in these circumstances.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop are not recommended for professional use in environments where quick removal of the camera case from the belt is not practical, such as densely packed crowd events where reaching down consistently might not be feasible.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_748", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the interior dividers of the Fastpack 200 be repositioned for different gear setups?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 features interior dividers within the main compartment that are indeed adjustable, providing the flexibility to customize the organization to accommodate various types and sizes of gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_515", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I refuse to fiddle around with zippers anymore, and I really like Case Logic brand. Could you show me their first non-zipper camera case?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND brand = \"Case Logic\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND brand = \"Case Logic\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Case Logic' AND closure_type != 'zipper' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_516", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I don't want any of those Ape Case products. Can you find me a water resistant camera case with the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand <> 'Ape Case' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_517", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I like the Ape Case brand and I'm a big fan of velcro closures. Do you have any camera cases like that in your line-up?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND brand = \"Ape Case\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND brand = \"Ape Case\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Ape Case' AND closure_type = 'velcro';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_749", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case compatible with the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-W80 camera?", "long_answer": "The Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case is specifically designed to accommodate slim Cyber-shot digital cameras, and according to customer reports, it fits the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-W80 model excellently.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_518", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I want a bit of color on my gear, but orange only. And don't show me anything over 50 dollars. What's the cheapest orange camera case you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" AND price < 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" AND price < 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'orange' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_692", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this case accommodate a T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. I use this for my Nikon D3500 and they're almost identical in size, so your T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_693", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can this camera case protect my equipment in the event that I get caught in a downpour during a hike?", "long_answer": "As the camera case is not waterproof, there is a risk of water seeping in and potentially damaging your camera if exposed to rain. It is constructed to provide some degree of protection against dampness, but for trips in adverse weather conditions, it may be prudent to opt for a waterproof option.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_694", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Can I swiftly retrieve my camera from this case to take candid shots?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the absence of a tripod mount on this case enables swift access to your camera, which is perfect for effortlessly taking those surprising, candid moments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_695", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this case work with my Canon Powershot SX50 HS?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it with my Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and that fits perfectly. I believe the dimensions of your camera are similar to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon Powershot SX50 HS has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon Powershot SX50 HS fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_750", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the Hi-Vis yellow interior of the ACPRO2000 make it easier to find small items in low light conditions?", "long_answer": "The Hi-Vis yellow interior of the ACPRO2000 is appreciated by customers for its ability to improve the visibility of small accessories and items within the bag, especially in situations where lighting is poor.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_519", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm all about this Canon and Sony gear, so I'm hunting for a camera case from one of those brands. Could you help me out and show me one with the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Sony\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Sony\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Sony\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Canon','Sony') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_751", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Are the velcro dividers in the bag effective at holding gear in place when the bag is not fully packed?", "long_answer": "The velcro dividers within the bag have received mixed feedback, where some reviewers suggest they could be more robust. They aim to organize and secure items, but their performance may not be optimal when the bag isn't fully loaded, as their effectiveness can be influenced by the packing style and the amount of content inside the bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_696", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Has the camera case been designed for photographers requiring swift relocation?", "long_answer": "Certainly, our camera cases are designed for active photographers who frequently transition between sites and need to do so swiftly. The lack of a tripod attachment feature ensures a smooth experience, enabling rapid packing and unpacking of your camera equipment without additional hassle.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_520", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Look, I only got 10 dollars to spend and I hate zippers. What's the cheapest camera case you have without a zipper?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND closure_type != 'zipper' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_752", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Does the Ape Case Cubeze provide sufficient padding to protect camera equipment adequately?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze comes with padding that majority of customers find adequate for daily use and offers reasonable protection especially when placed within another bag. Nevertheless, a minority of customers have indicated a desire for thicker padding to safeguard more expensive equipment, resulting in some users supplementing it with additional padding of their own.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_753", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the main compartment of the bag detachable?", "long_answer": "The main camera gear compartment of the bag is designed to be detachable based on customer feedback, providing flexibility in the usage of the backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_521", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I can't be dealing with too many pockets, it gets confusing. Just show me a zipper case with less pockets than average.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'zipper' AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases)"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_754", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the Case Logic bag suitable for outdoor activities such as hiking and photography sessions?", "long_answer": "The design and construction of the Case Logic bag include features like a waterproof base and a padded handle, specifically catering to the demands of outdoor activities and adventures, thus making it appropriate for use during hiking or outdoor photography sessions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_522", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I've got a thing for purple and either zippers or drawstrings are my go-to. Hook me up with the first product that matches these preferences.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_697", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can this camera case remain upright independently when placed down?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case is designed with an emphasis on portability and the ability to be worn as a backpack. Consequently, it features backpack straps and lacks the rigid structure that would allow it to stand upright independently, unlike hard cases that are capable of being free-standing.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps lack the capability to stay upright on their own when set down due to their design focused on back wear-ability, unlike hard cases which can be free-standing.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_755", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the camera case come with a feature that allows it to be attached to a camera strap?", "long_answer": "The camera case includes a Holster Tether that permits attachment to your camera's strap, providing you with the convenience of quick access to your camera without having to put the case down while taking photographs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_698", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can I use this case for my Canon EOS Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, you can. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits great. The Canon EOS Rebel T3 is about the same size and should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_699", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can I use this bag for my Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it for my Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens which is a similar size to your camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_756", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can the Ape Case Cubeze be used as a standalone bag?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze is designed primarily to protect gear inside another bag; however, it can serve as a standalone container for brief transport although it lacks dedicated carrying features such as a handle or strap.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_700", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a Canon EOS Rebel SL1?", "long_answer": "Yes it should, I use it with my Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens which is similar in size to the Canon EOS Rebel SL1.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel SL1 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_523", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case but I'm picky about colors, alright? So, find me a green or purple one that won't cost me more than 10 dollars.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"purple\") AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"purple\") AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('green', 'purple') AND price <= 10;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_701", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Do I need to perform regular maintenance to maintain the case in optimal condition?", "long_answer": "Certainly, choosing a waterproof camera case requires regular application of water repellent sprays to uphold optimal water resistance over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof attributes feature maintenance requirements such as periodic treatments with water repellent sprays to maintain their high protection level against water.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_702", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can I use this bag with my Canon Powershot SX50 HS?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it for my Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and they have similar dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon Powershot SX50 HS has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon Powershot SX50 HS fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_757", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can the camera be accidentally activated while inside its case?", "long_answer": "There is a potential for the camera's buttons to be pressed accidentally due to the case's snug fit, indicating that care should be taken when inserting the camera to prevent unintentional activation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_524", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I don't need all those extra pockets and I'm not a fan of green. Find me the cheapest camera case with no more than two pockets and not in green, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND color != 'green' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_703", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Should my drink inadvertently spill on the camera case, will it safeguard the camera from harm?", "long_answer": "Since this case is not waterproof, it fails to offer complete protection from spills. A minor amount of liquid may not inflict damage, yet larger spills pose a considerable threat of seeping through and harming your camera. Opting for a waterproof camera case would offer superior safeguarding against these mishaps.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_525", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm a fan of AmazonBasics and USA Gear. What's the cheapest camera case from these guys?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"USA Gear\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"USA Gear\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"USA Gear\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('AmazonBasics', 'USA Gear') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_526", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I've got a thing for \"USA Gear\" and \"Case Logic\". What's the cheapest camera case you have from either of those brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Case Logic\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Case Logic\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Case Logic\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'Case Logic') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_758", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the bag design allow for rapid access to the camera without being removed?", "long_answer": "The sling bag is specifically designed to enable quick access to the camera by rotating the bag from the back to the front, thus eliminating the need to take the bag off to reach the camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_759", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Do the bag's side and front pockets have padding to protect delicate accessories?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with padded side pockets for safely storing delicate accessories such as memory cards. The front pocket also features padding to offer extra protection for stored items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_704", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Should I inadvertently spill a beverage onto my camera's case, would the camera remain protected?", "long_answer": "The case material possesses a degree of water resistance that can safeguard your camera from small splashes. Nonetheless, it is not fully waterproof, hence it is advisable to swiftly attend to any spills to prevent possible damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_705", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Will my Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom lens fit in this backpack?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit just fine. I have a Canon 70D with a 70-250 lens and it fits perfectly. The sizes of the two lenses are similar.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_760", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is there a dedicated compartment in the camera sling for storing additional lenses?", "long_answer": "The camera sling is equipped with a large zippered compartment specifically designed to accommodate an extra lens or flash, providing convenience for photographers who need to carry additional equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_761", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this backpack suitable for travel photographers seeking a discreet option?", "long_answer": "The backpack's larger size makes it more noticeable and consequently may not be the ideal choice for travel photographers who aim to maintain a low profile and avoid drawing attention.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_762", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Does the Pelican 1200 Case meet the TSA requirements for checked firearm travel?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 Case is designed with two holes for locks that accommodate TSA requirements for firearm travel. Customers who have used this case report successful travel experiences. Travellers are advised to confirm that their personal locks are compatible with the case's lock holes prior to flying.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_763", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is a built-in weather cover included with the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is not equipped with a built-in weather cover. Customers seeking to protect the backpack from the elements commonly utilize compatible rain covers from third-party manufacturers.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_764", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Do the zipper pullers come with a built-in locking mechanism for security?", "long_answer": "The zipper pullers on the item in question lack a dedicated built-in locking mechanism. Therefore, while it is not provided by the design, customers have improvised their own solutions by using small padlocks or zip ties to enhance the security of their zippers.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_527", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm ain't interested in anything else but Canon, alright? Ditch the rest, find me the most affordable Canon camera case you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Canon' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_706", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is this camera case a suitable choice if I need it to serve as both a case and a standalone tripod holder?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case lacks the free-standing functionality required for a tripod holder. Designed primarily for back wearing, the backpack straps mean it does not possess the necessary rigid external framework to independently support a tripod.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps lack the capability to stay upright on their own when set down due to their design focused on back wear-ability, unlike hard cases which can be free-standing.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_765", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the backpack designed to be suitable for both hiking and outdoor photography activities?", "long_answer": "The backpack is specifically designed with features that cater to outdoor photography and hiking needs, providing both comfort and functionality for these activities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_528", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm specifically after a camera case from either AmazonBasics or Lowepro, and I prefer ones with zippers or locks. Sort through your stuff and give me the cheapest option, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Lowepro\") AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Lowepro\") AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Lowepro\") AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('AmazonBasics', 'Lowepro') AND closure_type IN ('zipper', 'locks') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_766", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "What is the durability level of the case's material?", "long_answer": "The case is constructed from a strong, black, ballistic-type fabric which is reinforced with sufficient padding and lining on the inside to provide durability for daily usage.", "short_answer": "high durability level", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_529", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm looking for a Sony camera case with either locks or drawstrings, but it should not have too many pockets. Which model would you recommend?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND brand = \"Sony\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND brand = \"Sony\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"drawstring\") AND brand = \"Sony\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Sony' AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') AND pockets < 3;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_707", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Does this case pose a risk of my camera falling if I am not holding it continuously?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the risk of accidental drops is heightened due to the case's design, which features solely a hand grip. This necessitates that users keep a continuous hold on the case, as it lacks any securing features, such as a neck or cross-body strap.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip do not have a function of securing the camera to the body like a neck strap or cross-body strap, potentially increasing the risk of accidental drops if the user does not maintain a constant grip.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_708", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this case accommodate a Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately no, I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens which fits perfectly inside, but the Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens is a little larger than that, so it would not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_767", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the material of the bag durable enough for years of wear and tear?", "long_answer": "The bag's material is designed to withstand years of use, with its quality affirmed by both metadata and feedback from customers testifying to its long-term durability. ", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_768", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack remain upright when placed on a flat surface?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack is designed to maintain its shape and remain upright when placed on a flat surface if the items inside are distributed in a balanced manner.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_530", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm only interested in Canon and Ape Case brands for my camera case. Tell me, what's the cheapest product you've got from them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Ape Case\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Ape Case\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Ape Case\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Canon', 'Ape Case') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_769", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the Day Holster available in various sizes to accommodate larger camera bodies?", "long_answer": "Based on the product metadata, the Day Holster does not come in multiple sizes, suggesting that it is designed with medium-sized DSLR camera bodies in mind, as opposed to accommodating very large camera bodies.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_709", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is it possible for me to rapidly deploy my tripod for swift capture of unexpected movements or occurrences with this camera case?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case features a specific pocket for a tripod, enabling swift attachment and detachment. This proves particularly useful in scenarios where quick shot setup is crucial, like when photographing fast-paced events or activities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket are known for their convenience in allowing for quick attachment and detachment of tripods, which is particularly beneficial in dynamic shooting situations where setting up the shot swiftly is crucial.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_770", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the case made of durable nylon advertised as being waterproof?", "long_answer": "The case is constructed from durable nylon, offering a certain degree of protection. However, it is not marketed as being waterproof, and it is advisable to keep it away from water to prevent damage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_531", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I've had a bad experience with USA Gear. Show me a different brand for camera cases. Just one will do for now.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'USA Gear' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_710", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm merely an amateur photographer; however, I wonder if this case could restrict me in any manner while shooting outdoors?", "long_answer": "Although the case may be adequate for a hobbyist's everyday needs, its lack of a tripod attachment might pose restrictions for outdoor photography sessions where a tripod is essential. This becomes particularly relevant as your interest in photography expands to situations where camera stability is vital for getting that perfect shot.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not recommended for photography enthusiasts and professionals who engage in specialized shooting scenarios that necessitate the steadiness and precise positioning afforded by a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_771", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can the Case Logic SHC-101 holster fit a Nikon D5100 camera with a standard zoom lens attached?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SHC-101 holster is designed to fit a Nikon D5100 camera when it is equipped with a standard zoom lens. However, it should be noted that the snugness of the fit may vary based on the dimensions of the particular lens being used.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_532", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I've got a thing for green and prefer to stick to average price range. Besides, I need to keep my stuff organized. So can you find me a green camera case with the least number of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' AND pockets = (SELECT pockets FROM camera_cases WHERE color = 'green' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1) ORDER BY price ASC;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_533", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I don't wanna spend any more than 30 dollars on this. What's the cheapest camera case you've got within my budget?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_711", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Nikon D7100 with a 55-300mm VR lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should work. My Canon 70D with an 18-200mm fits perfectly and given that your Nikon D7100 with a 55-300mm VR lens has similar dimensions, it should also fit in the case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Nikon D7100 + 55-300mm VR lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Nikon D7100 + 55-300mm VR lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_712", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Will this bag fit a small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. The product fits with Nikon D3500, and your small prime has a similar size to the Nikon D3500. So, it should definitely fit!", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_534", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm not really a fan of velcro and I'm looking for a red case. Can you find a suitable product for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND color = \"red\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND color = \"red\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'velcro' AND color = 'red';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_772", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the Canon PSC-85 case weatherproof or waterproof?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 case is neither advertised as weatherproof nor waterproof. Its primary function is to offer basic protection to the camera from scratches and minor impacts rather than providing resistance against weather elements like rain or splashes.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_773", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the Canon SLR Gadget Bag provide adequate protection for camera gear?", "long_answer": "The Canon SLR Gadget Bag comes fully padded, offering robust protection for camera equipment against minor impacts according to user feedback.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_535", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm not looking to spend over a 100 dollars, and I only trust OP/TECH USA and Lowepro. Give me the most affordable option from these brands, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Lowepro\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Lowepro\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('OP/TECH USA', 'Lowepro') AND price <= 100 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_774", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag capable of accommodating a large DSLR and an attached zoom lens?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag is explicitly designed to hold a large DSLR camera with a zoom lens attached, and even has room for an additional lens or flash, plus other accessories. It also features an expandable compartment to provide extra space for slightly larger camera setups, although they might fit snugly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_775", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can a professional photographer with a large gear set use this bag effectively?", "long_answer": "The backpack is considered suitable for casual photography use and lighter professional applications. However, it may not be ideal for professional photographers with extensive gear sets, as they might require a larger capacity bag to accommodate their needs.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_536", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm trying to save some cash. What's the cheapest camera case you've got under 10 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_537", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I dislike USA Gear and I've had enough of the color red. Hook me up with a different brand camera case and color, just make sure it's the one with the least pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT color = \"red\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT color = \"red\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND NOT color = \"red\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'USA Gear' AND color != 'red' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_776", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is this camera sling designed to be worn in ways other than cross-body?", "long_answer": "The camera sling is specifically intended for cross-body wear to enhance security and provide easy access to the equipment. It is not designed to be worn over a single shoulder as doing so might affect both comfort and accessibility to the camera gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_538", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I’m not a fan of drawstring closure types and I've got a thing for purple. Can you show me a purple camera case that doesn't use a drawstring?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND color = \"purple\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND color = \"purple\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'drawstring' AND color = 'purple';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_713", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Will this case accommodate my 50-500 Sigma lenses?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it with my Nikon D5200 and two lenses which are similar in size to your Sigma lens. It fits perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_777", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the camera bag designed to be comfortable when fully loaded with equipment?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is equipped with a detachable padded shoulder strap that enhances comfort for the users while carrying the bag fully loaded with photography equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_714", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Would it be feasible to carry this case on public transportation without it being too conspicuous?", "long_answer": "The camera case isn't crafted for subtlety on public transit, as the backpack straps add to its bulkier profile. Unlike slimmer cases, this makes it more difficult to tuck away or hold close to your body in cramped areas.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps fail to meet the requirements for a low-profile carry option in crowd-intensive settings due to their bulkier design when compared to more streamlined cases or bags.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_539", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm only interested in Lowepro and Sony cases, and I don't want any of that extra pocket nonsense. What's the first option you can show me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"Sony\") AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"Sony\") AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Lowepro', 'Sony') AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_540", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I don't need any fancy water-resistant case or ones with loads of pockets. What's the cheapest bare-bones camera case you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets <= 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets <= 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND pockets <= 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_715", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Will this case fit a Canon G15?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. This case is designed for a Canon L-series 100-400, which is similar in size to the Canon G15.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon G15 has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon G15 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_778", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the Case Logic SLRC-202 camera bag come with a warranty?", "long_answer": "The Case Logic SLRC-202 camera bag includes a 25-year warranty that covers defects in materials and workmanship, indicating a high level of durability and a strong assurance from the manufacturer regarding the quality of the product.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_541", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I'm in the mood for something colorful and cheap. What's the least expensive camera case you have in either orange or green?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"green\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"green\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('orange', 'green') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_779", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "How effective is the Canon PSC-85 case in protecting a camera from everyday bumps and scratches?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 case is designed to offer effective protection against bumps and scratches, as evidenced by numerous user reports highlighting its padded interior and soft lining contributing to the case's protective capability.", "short_answer": "strong protection", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_716", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does this case offer sufficient security to safeguard my delicate photography equipment against possible theft?", "long_answer": "Camera cases that come with shoulder straps offer protection and convenience for daily use; nonetheless, they don't offer the same security against theft as locked carry-ons or hard cases, which could be preferable when prioritizing theft prevention.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap lack the capability to offer the same level of security as a locked carry-on or hard case, so they might not be the primary choice for transporting extremely valuable or sensitive equipment.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_717", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this case accommodate a small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon L-series 100-400, and it fits fine. Your small prime should be a similar size, so I believe it will fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_780", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the camera case have features that allow it to be easily attached to a belt or backpack?", "long_answer": "The camera case is equipped with a belt loop and a clip specifically designed for easy attachment to a belt or a backpack, enhancing its convenience for the user.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_781", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "What is an alternative way to carry the backpack without using the shoulder sling?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with a padded top handle that provides a comfortable alternative for hand-carrying when you choose not to use the shoulder sling.", "short_answer": "padded top handle", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_718", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Should a drink inadvertently be spilled on my camera case, will my camera remain protected?", "long_answer": "The case material features a degree of water resistance designed to shield your camera from small spills. Nonetheless, it is not fully waterproof; therefore, promptly cleaning up any spills is advisable to prevent possible damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_719", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is this case a suitable option for professional photographers seeking robust support for their equipment?", "long_answer": "Professional photographers typically need robust support for their gear to avoid damage. Given nylon's inherent pliability, this camera case might not provide the desired level of rigidity that is essential for protecting professional photography equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_782", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the Canon SLR Gadget Bag have water-repellent properties?", "long_answer": "The Canon SLR Gadget Bag is made from durable nylon which is water-repellent, providing protection for your camera and accessories against water exposure.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_720", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this bag fit my Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The size of your device is similar to my Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, which fits perfectly in this bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_783", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the backpack comfortably accommodate multiple lenses and a flash unit for professional photographers?", "long_answer": "The backpack is focused on mobility and may not have ample space for professional photographers carrying larger lenses and flash units, potentially making it less ideal for those with extensive equipment needs.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_721", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will the material of this camera case degrade rapidly with daily use?", "long_answer": "Rubber, foam, silicone, and leather are all robust materials frequently utilized for camera case grips, each providing durability that withstands regular usage. Specifically, silicone and rubber are renowned for their sturdiness and capacity to preserve their quality over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip feature materials such as rubber, foam, silicone, or leather, with options like rubber and silicone offering high slip resistance and leather providing a premium aesthetic.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_542", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm really not looking to spend a lot nor do I need all those extra pockets. Just show me the simplest and cheapest camera case you got that's less than 10 dollars.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 AND pockets = 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_784", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the camera gear well-protected from damage in the main compartment of this bag?", "long_answer": "The main compartment of the bag features ample padding, and according to reports from users, this padding has successfully protected their camera equipment against damage from incidents such as drops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_543", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I've had it up to here with Canon! Get me the first non-Canon camera case you can find with either a zipper or lock closure.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)` with asin: B00WUIIH8W", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Canon\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Canon' AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'locks') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_722", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should work. I have a Nikon D90 which is similar in size to your Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or a fast prime lens and it fits well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_723", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this case accommodate a T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it for my Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens, and the size of your T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens is similar to my camera. Therefore, your T5i should fit in this case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the T5i with a sigma 18-35mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_724", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can I use this case for my Canon 5DII? ", "long_answer": "Yes, you should be able to. I have a Nikon D3500 and it fits perfectly. I believe your Canon 5DII has similar dimensions as my Nikon.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5DII has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5DII fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_785", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "What is the total number of zippers on the camera case?", "long_answer": "The camera case is equipped with a single zipper, although there's feedback from customers indicating a preference for two zippers to facilitate more versatile closing options.", "short_answer": "one", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_786", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack suitable for carrying a 17-inch laptop?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case ACPRO2000 backpack is specifically designed to accommodate laptops and tablets that measure up to 16 inches in size. As a result, a 17-inch laptop would likely not fit within the designated compartment of this backpack.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_787", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is this bag designed to securely transport a full-sized tripod?", "long_answer": "This bag is designed with straps specifically meant to secure a full-sized tripod, enabling users to carry the tripod conveniently. Customer feedback confirms that these straps hold the tripod effectively during transport, preventing slippage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_544", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Listen, I ain't keen on anything from Pelican and I've only got 30 bucks to spare. What's the cheapest camera case you've got that fits my criteria?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Pelican\" AND price <= 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Pelican\" AND price <= 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand <> 'Pelican' AND price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_545", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm looking for a budget-friendly camera case, but still want some functionality though. What's the cheapest one you've got under 10 dollars with the least number of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 10 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_725", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit just fine. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens that fits perfectly and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens is roughly the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_726", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can this case accommodate an A-99 with a vertical grip? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit just fine. I use it for my Nikon D3500 and they're roughly the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the A-99 with vertical grip has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the A-99 with vertical grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_788", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the camera backpack include a compartment for personal items apart from camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The backpack is primarily designed for camera gear, featuring specific compartments and dividers for that purpose. Nonetheless, it also offers zippered mesh pockets for small items and a top compartment that can serve to store personal belongings or extra camera accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_546", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I ain't loaded, but I need a case that isn't going to open on me. Whether it's a drawstring or a zipper, don't care. Keep it under 100 and show me the one with the fewest pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") AND price <= 100 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") AND price <= 100 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") AND price <= 100 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'zipper') AND price < 100 ORDER BY pockets LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_727", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can I use this case with a Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use this case for my Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and your camera seems to be of similar dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Pentax K-2 with Sigma 18-125 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_789", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this bag designed to comfortably accommodate two SLR camera bodies?", "long_answer": "This bag is specifically designed to comfortably hold one or two SLR camera bodies, in addition to lenses and other photography accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_790", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is there a belt loop on the pouch for attachment to a belt?", "long_answer": "The pouch itself does not have a belt loop; however, it is equipped with a retaining strap that allows it to be fastened to a belt or bag strap, providing a means to secure it conveniently.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_547", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm only interested in Canon and OP/TECH USA cases right now. Give me a camera case from either of these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"OP/TECH USA\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"OP/TECH USA\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Canon', 'OP/TECH USA') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_728", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this camera bag appropriate for a photographer who frequently travels with a full-sized professional tripod?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case is not suitable for photographers who travel with a full-sized professional tripod, as the compartment for the tripod is not designed to accommodate larger models, which could result in the inconvenience of needing an additional bag for the tripod.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod compartment cannot be used for conveniently storing larger professional tripods that exceed the size limitations of the pocket, which could lead to inconvenience or the need for additional carrying solutions for such equipment.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_791", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the Ape Case backpack comfortable to carry, according to customer feedback?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback indicates that the backpack's design allows for easy carrying, providing a balanced and comfortable experience even with its considerable size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_548", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm only interested in \"USA Gear\" or \"Lowepro\". Find me the cheapest case from either of these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Lowepro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Lowepro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Lowepro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'Lowepro') \nORDER BY price \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_549", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Look, I don't care about water resistance and I only have 10 bucks. What's the cheapest camera case you got that isn't water-resistant?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_550", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm a fan of Case Logic but I don't want to bleed my wallet dry. What's the cheapest camera case from them that's under a hundred?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)` with asin: B00WUIIH8W", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND price < 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND price < 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Case Logic' AND price < 100 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_729", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Will this camera case exhibit a luxurious appearance that distinguishes itself?", "long_answer": "Since this camera case is made of nylon, it might not exude the same luxurious appearance as cases crafted from high-end materials such as leather. Nylon usually presents a more informal and practical look, potentially falling short for those in search of an exceptional, opulent aesthetic.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_730", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is it reasonable to anticipate that this camera case will retain its shape after years of use?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is constructed from nylon, renowned for its resistance to stretching. Consequently, the case maintains its original form more effectively over time, even through frequent usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_792", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can the camera bag accommodate a camera body, multiple lenses, and additional accessories such as flash, batteries, memory cards, and cables?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is reported by customers to have sufficient space to hold a camera body, several lenses, a flash unit, as well as smaller accessories including batteries, memory cards, and cables.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_731", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm really passionate about macro photography; does this case facilitate that type of precise work?", "long_answer": "Macro photography typically necessitates a highly stable camera to seize intricate details sharply, yet this camera case lacks a tripod attachment feature, which is crucial for achieving such stability.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_793", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the Lowepro Passport Sling designed to look like a typical camera bag?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Passport Sling is crafted with a discreet design that makes it unlike a typical camera bag, aiming to lessen the chance of drawing attention and signaling that it contains expensive camera equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_732", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Will this bag fit a T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The Nikon D3500 fits this bag and your T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens has a similar size with the Nikon D3500.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_733", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Will this case maintain its durability with everyday use in a professional photography environment?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is designed to endure the rigors of everyday use, particularly in professional environments. The nylon material provides superior abrasion resistance, ensuring that it retains its structural integrity and safeguards your camera through regular use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_734", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this Pelican 1120 case also fit my Canon 5DII?", "long_answer": "Yes, the case is suitable for Nikon D3500 and the Canon 5DII has similar dimensions to the Nikon D3500, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5DII has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5DII fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_794", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack designed to provide protection against pickpockets in high-risk areas?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 backpack is designed with backside entry, which offers additional security against pickpockets, hence making it a suitable option for carrying gear in areas where pickpocketing is prevalent.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_735", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm concerned about my tripod being jostled during travel. Is this camera case designed for secure transportation?", "long_answer": "The camera case features external straps designed to hold a tripod securely, offering a convenient method to carry it along with your other gear. However, note that the tripod will be subject to environmental elements and possible impacts. Should this exposure be a concern, you might want to search for a bag that permits internal storage of the tripod, ensuring enhanced protection while on the move.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with external straps for tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who prefer or need to carry their tripod inside their bag for extra protection or for those who do not use tripods in their photography work.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "external straps", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_736", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can this case fit a Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom?", "long_answer": "Yes, the case should fit. I have a Nikon D5200 with two lenses, and the size is pretty similar to the Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "search_qa_551", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I don't want any fancy stuff, just a simple camera case with maxim one pocket and either a velcro or drawstring closure. What's the cheapest one you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 \nAND (closure_type = 'velcro' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_795", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the camera case accommodate an external flash?", "long_answer": "The case is designed as a fitted day holster, focused on housing the camera with an attached lens only, and does not have extra space to accommodate larger accessories like an external flash.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_737", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can I use this case for my Nikon D5000?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should work. I use it for my Nikon D3500 which is similar in size to the D5000, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Nikon D5000 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Nikon D5000 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_738", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can I safely assume that my camera will remain undamaged after spending a day at the beach with this case?", "long_answer": "Certainly, your camera is designed to withstand water exposure such as ocean spray or unintentional submersions when equipped with this waterproof camera case. Yet, it is important to acknowledge that although the case offers protection against water and sand, it is not entirely crush-resistant. Care should be taken to avoid circumstances where the case could be subjected to significant force or pressure, as this could lead to damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof elements fail to meet the requirements for being entirely crush-proof; while they can protect against water, they may not withstand being subjected to heavy weights or forces without additional rigid structural features.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_739", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Will this case accommodate my Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The case is designed to fit the Canon L-series 100-400, and your Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens is similar in size. It should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon T2i with the 18-55 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_796", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does this camera bag provide comfort for extended carrying periods?", "long_answer": "Yes, the camera bag is designed for comfort during extended carrying with features like a padded handle and an adjustable, padded shoulder strap equipped with swivel hardware to prevent strap twisting.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_740", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this case suitable for a wedding photographer to carry around?", "long_answer": "A camera case with backpack straps might not conform to the formal dress code typically expected at weddings, where a professional appearance is often required, as it may appear overly casual for such occasions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are not recommended for situations that demand rapid gear changes or a professional appearance that aligns with formal event dress codes, as a backpack might be viewed as too casual or cumbersome in such environments.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_797", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the backpack's actual size match its appearance in photos?", "long_answer": "The backpack may seem larger in photos according to some customers, and it's recommended to confirm the actual dimensions provided in the product description to ensure the size aligns with personal expectations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_741", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for air travel transportation of my expensive camera equipment?", "long_answer": "Our camera cases, crafted for convenience and quick access, may not offer the utmost security for highly valuable gear when flying. We suggest considering a lockable carry-on or a hard-shell case for increased protection during air travel.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap lack the capability to offer the same level of security as a locked carry-on or hard case, so they might not be the primary choice for transporting extremely valuable or sensitive equipment.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_552", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm looking for something flashy. Find me the least expensive camera case in either red or orange.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"orange\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"orange\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"orange\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('red','orange') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_553", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I've heard good things about Lowepro. Can you pull up the first product you have from them in camera cases?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack` with asin: B000YA33DC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Lowepro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Lowepro' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_742", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is this camera case designed to be less bulky than others?", "long_answer": "Indeed, since this camera case isn't waterproof, it usually lacks the additional heft associated with protective seals. Consequently, it offers a sleeker and less burdensome option for daily usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_798", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the backpack's interior adjustable to fit larger telephoto lenses?", "long_answer": "The backpack's interior features adjustable compartments that enable it to house larger lenses, encompassing a range of telephoto lenses. Nevertheless, the space may be limited for particularly sizable lenses, and will vary according to the total space needed for all gear intended to be carried within the backpack.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_554", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I can't deal with all these extra pockets, two is more than enough. Also, I'm a stickler for brands, so can you find me a case from either OP/TECH USA or USA Gear?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"USA Gear\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"USA Gear\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('OP/TECH USA', 'USA Gear') AND pockets <= 2;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_799", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is the Pelican case appropriate for secure storage of sensitive medical equipment?", "long_answer": "The Pelican case is designed to be airtight and crushproof, which makes it an excellent option for securely storing and protecting sensitive medical supplies, ensuring they are safe from harm and environmental factors.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_743", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Will this case work for a Canon t5i with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, this backpack should accommodate your camera. I use it for my Canon 70D with a 70-250mm lens, and the dimensions are close.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_555", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case but I can't stand those with multiple pockets. And I'd only want purple or orange ones. Now, what's the cheapest you can offer that meets these odd requirements?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"orange\") AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"orange\") AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"purple\", \"orange\") AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets=0 \nAND (color='purple' OR color='orange') \nORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_556", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I don't want to drop more than 30 dollars and I'm loyal to Case Logic. What's the cheapest camera case you have from them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"Case Logic\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"Case Logic\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Case Logic' AND price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_800", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the shoulder strap provide comfort during prolonged periods of use?", "long_answer": "The shoulder strap of this product is padded and intentionally designed to enhance comfort during extended use. The inclusion of a wide mesh center piece contributes significantly to the comfort it offers, particularly when the user is carrying heavier items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_744", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can this camera case protect my gear when I encounter rain on my photographic excursions?", "long_answer": "The camera case in question is crafted to prioritize portability and compactness, thus rendering it perfect for use in arid environments. Its functionality is optimized for dry settings, which means it might not offer complete rain protection. Should you often face damp conditions, seeking a waterproof case is recommended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_745", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can this bag fit a Canon EOS 7D?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Nikon D3500, which is very similar in size to the Canon EOS 7D, and it fits in this bag perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS 7D has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS 7D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_801", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the backpack suitable for carrying various cameras and accessories simultaneously?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed to accommodate a variety of photography equipment, including multiple types of cameras ranging from DSLR to point & shoot, as well as lenses and other accessories, as reported by users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_746", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this backpack hold a Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "I'm sorry, but I don't believe this backpack can accommodate the Canon 70-200 F4 lens. I have a Nikon D3500 which fits comfortably, and your lens is larger than my camera. So, it may not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_802", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the AmazonBasics Sling Backpack come with a warranty?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Sling Backpack comes with a one-year AmazonBasics warranty, which is provided to give customers added security and peace of mind regarding their purchase.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_747", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is there a compartment within the camera case specifically designed for tripod storage that ensures it doesn't damage my lenses?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the case features a dedicated pocket designed specifically for storing a tripod. This provision ensures that the tripod remains separate from your lenses and other sensitive gear, thus protecting them from potential harm.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket feature designs that aim to protect camera equipment from scratches or damage potentially caused by tripod legs or knobs, contributing to the overall safety of the stored gear.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_557", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Zippers on my camera case are a no-go for me but I can't shell out more than a 100 dollars. What's the cheapest non-zipper case you have within my budget?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND price <= 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND price <= 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type <> 'zipper' AND price <= 100 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_748", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm organizing a photography trip to the desert. Is this case suitable for safeguarding my camera against sand and dust?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is ideal for a desert photography expedition. It is crafted to emphasize both compactness and functionality in arid conditions, providing safeguarding against sand and dust. However, it's important to note that it is intended for dry settings and is not designed to protect your equipment in scenarios involving submersion or exposure to significant moisture.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_803", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can the bag be safely washed in a washing machine?", "long_answer": "The construction and materials of the bag indicate that it is not meant for machine washing. Instead, the recommended methods for cleaning are spot cleaning or hand washing according to the care instructions provided by the manufacturer.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_804", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can the AmazonBasics Sling Backpack's main compartment be adjusted to fit a Canon T2i with an attached Sigma 18-250 lens?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Sling Backpack features adjustable dividers in the main compartment that can be customized to accommodate a DSLR camera such as the Canon T2i with a Sigma 18-250 lens attached, ensuring a snug and secure fit for your equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_749", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this backpack fit a Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. The backpack can accommodate my Canon 10-22mm lens which is similar in size to your Canon 70D with 135mm zoom.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_558", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I don't need any fancy water resistance feature, just a simple Sony case. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Sony\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Sony\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Sony\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Sony' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_805", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Given the internal dimensions of 7.5\" x 5\" x 12\" (LxWxH), can this container accommodate a smaller SLR camera body, 1-2 lenses, and some small accessories?", "long_answer": "The container's internal dimensions are typically adequate for housing a smaller SLR camera body along with 1-2 lenses and a selection of small accessories; however, it's recommended to measure your particular camera gear to confirm compatibility.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_806", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Has the strap hook on the product been reported to break by any customers?", "long_answer": "Yes, several customers have reported incidents of the strap hook breaking, indicating it is a known issue, though not all customers have encountered this problem.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_750", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Does this camera case enable me to swiftly retrieve my camera should a sudden photo opportunity present itself?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera cases equipped with a hand grip are intentionally crafted to provide quick and easy access to your camera. This characteristic is especially advantageous for seizing those impromptu moments frequently encountered in street photography or while transitioning between shots at events.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip are known for providing quick and easy access to the camera, which is advantageous in scenarios where time is critical, such as capturing spontaneous moments in street photography or transitioning between shots at an event.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_807", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does the bag have compartments for storing small accessories like batteries and memory cards?", "long_answer": "The bag includes multiple compartments specifically designed to accommodate small accessories, including batteries and memory cards, providing an organized way to carry these items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_559", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm looking for some pop in my gear. Give me the cheapest orange camera case you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'orange' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_751", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this case accommodate my Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens?", "long_answer": "No, it may not. The case is designed to fit a Nikon D3500 which is smaller than your Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_560", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I can't stand the color teal, it's just a no-go for me. Can you find a camera case that isn't teal and has the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"teal\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"teal\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"teal\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color <> 'teal' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_808", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the camera case have a warranty or return policy?", "long_answer": "The camera case comes with a standard return policy. For returns or exchanges, issues must be reported within a specified timeframe, which is detailed in Amazon's return policy.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_809", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the backpack fabric water-resistant?", "long_answer": "The backpack is constructed using robust fabric that is water-resistant, affording the bag a level of protection against moisture.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_810", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the neoprene camera case significantly increase the size of the camera setup?", "long_answer": "The camera case is made of neoprene material, which provides protection without adding significant bulk to the camera setup. It remains convenient for carrying your camera either within another bag or on its own with a sling.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_811", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the Canon 200DG bag suitable for maintaining a professional appearance?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG bag is designed with attractive styling that is well-received for professional contexts, making it a good choice for both photography enthusiasts and professionals seeking to maintain a professional look.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_812", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Does this bag have an alternative carrying option other than the shoulder strap?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with a top handle, which offers an alternative means of carrying it besides the shoulder strap.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_752", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this case fit a small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit perfectly. I have a Nikon D3500 which is a similar size to your lens and it fits in this case comfortably.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_753", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Will this fit my Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it for my Canon 70D with a 70-250 lens, and the size of your Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip is almost identical to the Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, so it should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_754", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can this case fit my Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR?", "long_answer": "I believe it should. I have a Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens and it fits perfectly. Your Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR should also fit since they have similar dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_755", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera case designed to securely transport a tripod through densely populated spaces?", "long_answer": "The camera bag offers a convenient hook and loop fastener mechanism for attaching your tripod, facilitating easy access. However, in densely populated areas, this may not be the most secure method of transport, given the ease with which the fastener can be released. In situations where security is paramount, implementing extra anti-theft precautions may be advisable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with tripod attachment using hook and loop fastener do not have a function of providing an extremely secure, theft-deterrent method of attaching tripods since the fasteners can be easily opened, potentially allowing for quick unauthorized removal.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "hook and loop fastener", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_561", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I don't need any fancy water resistance feature and I'm not ready to drop more than 50 dollars. Give me the cheapest dry camera case you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price < 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price < 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_756", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fit in this bag?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon 70D with a 70-250mm lens and it fits well. The Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens is comparable in size, so it should fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_813", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is the exterior of the Pelican 1120 Case resistant to scratches and marks?", "long_answer": "While the Pelican 1120 Case is designed for durability and protection of contents, its exterior can acquire minor scratches under harsh conditions, though these do not affect the case's protective capabilities.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_814", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the camera gear backpack feature a specific compartment for personal items?", "long_answer": "The camera gear backpack is designed with a top compartment and mesh pockets that can be utilized for storing personal items, in conjunction to compartments for camera gear and accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_562", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Listen, I'm a die-hard fan of OP/TECH USA. Show me the cheapest camera case they have, pronto.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand='OP/TECH USA' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_815", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the Soft Pouch - Digital D-Series case considerably increase the camera's weight or bulk?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch - Digital D-Series case, crafted from neoprene, adds minimal volume and weight to the camera, maintaining its compactness and lightness while offering protection.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_816", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Does the Ape Case Cubeze provide a cost-effective alternative to buying a dedicated camera bag?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze is considered a valuable investment by customers, as it allows them to transform any preferred bag into a secure space for their camera equipment at a lower price compared to purchasing most dedicated camera bags.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_757", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Will this backpack fit my Canon EOS 7D? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The Nikon D3500 fits and the Canon EOS 7D is a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS 7D has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS 7D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_758", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I frequently trek to my photography sites. Is this camera case built for convenient transport during extended hikes?", "long_answer": "For those who favor a lean and simplistic setup for their treks, this camera case might not be ideal since the built-in tripod pocket can introduce extra weight and heft. Opting for a case lacking this particular component could better align with your preference for lightweight travel.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket are not suitable for photographers who prioritize the most lightweight and minimalist gear setup, as this feature may add to the bulk and weight of the case.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_817", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the bag's design include a method for securing a tripod?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with a strap system on the front, designed for securing a tripod or other large items. The fastening mechanism uses industrial strength hook-and-loop to ensure the tripod or bulky gear is held firmly in place.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_818", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Does the case come with a metal ring that would allow it to be attached directly to a belt loop?", "long_answer": "The case includes a sturdy metal ring suitable for easy attachment to a belt loop using accessories like a spring snap fastener.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_563", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I've got a thing for red stuff. Pull up the cheapest red camera case you have in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_819", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "How durable is the material of the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack when used for travel and extended periods?", "long_answer": "The material of the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack is reported by customers to be durable and reliable, even with frequent travel and long-term utilization, making it well-regarded in terms of maintaining its condition and protecting camera equipment.", "short_answer": "durable and reliable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_820", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can the bag fit a DSLR camera with an attached battery grip as well as additional lenses and accessories?", "long_answer": "The bag's interior design may prove to be insufficient for housing larger DSLR cameras that have battery grips attached, particularly when also trying to include extra lenses or other accessories in the space.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_564", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Alright, I'm looking for a camera case that's either mica or teal, but it's got to be water resistant. Find me the least expensive one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras` with asin: B001I3X3HU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"teal\") AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"teal\") AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"teal\") AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('mica', 'teal') AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_759", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this case fit a d3300? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens which fits nicely and the d3300 is of similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the d3300 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the d3300 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_760", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens?", "long_answer": "Probably not, I use mine for my Nikon D5000 with a battery grip and it just fits. Considering that your setup is larger, I don't think it would fit comfortably.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_761", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can I use this bag for my Canon T3? ", "long_answer": "Yes, I have the Canon L-series 100-400 and it fits perfectly. The dimensions of your camera are similar to mine, so it will fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon T3 has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "search_qa_565", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm interested in a dash of color for my camera case - either green or purple will do. And I trust only \"Altura Photo\" or \"Lowepro\" for quality. Find me the best-priced camera case meeting these criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"purple\") AND brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Lowepro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"purple\") AND brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Lowepro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"purple\") AND brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Lowepro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (color = 'green' OR color = 'purple') AND (brand = 'Altura Photo' OR brand = 'Lowepro') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_821", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can the Canon 200DG camera bag accommodate multiple SLR camera bodies, lenses, and accessories simultaneously?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag is designed with enough space to carry up to two SLR camera bodies, three lenses, and additional accessories, featuring padded side pockets to extend its storage capacity for your photographic equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_762", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I enjoy landscape photography; is this case suitable for accommodating my additional equipment needs?", "long_answer": "Certainly, given that landscape photography typically requires a tripod for optimal outcomes, this camera bag is designed with a dedicated compartment for a tripod. It allows you to conveniently transport all the vital equipment, making sure your tripod is easily available whenever you need to prepare for a photograph.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket typically mean that the product is designed with the needs of photographers in mind who require quick and easy access to their tripods for capturing stable and precise shots across various photography genres.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_763", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is this case designed for comfortable carrying over extended periods during a city tour?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is designed for comfort during prolonged city tours, thanks to its backpack straps that evenly distribute weight across your shoulders. However, it may not be the most discreet choice in densely populated urban settings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps fail to meet the requirements for a low-profile carry option in crowd-intensive settings due to their bulkier design when compared to more streamlined cases or bags.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_822", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does this backpack include a system for carrying a tripod?", "long_answer": "This backpack incorporates a Hideaway Tripod Mount system designed to secure a tripod to the pack, allowing for convenient transportation of the tripod.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_823", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can the main compartment of this bag accommodate a Canon EOS 60D camera with an 18-200mm lens?", "long_answer": "Based on customer feedback, the main compartment of the bag is adequately sized to fit a Canon EOS 60D camera equipped with an 18-200mm lens, and the bag's protective hammock system offers further security for the camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_824", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can the camera be accessed rapidly when using this case?", "long_answer": "The design of the case facilitates rapid access to the camera, enabling swift unclipping and removal so that moments can be captured with minimal delay.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_825", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the camera fall out of the bag when accessing the main compartment?", "long_answer": "When opening the main compartment of the bag, there is a risk that the camera may shift and possibly fall out if it is not secured correctly. It is advised to hold the camera while opening the compartment or to use an additional method to ensure the camera remains in place.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_566", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm not looking for something fancy. Just a camera case with one pocket or maybe none at all and either a drawstring or zipper will do. Find me the cheapest one available, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (pockets = 0 OR pockets = 1) \nAND (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'zipper') \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_567", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm keen on Altura Photo products. What's the cheapest camera case you have from them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_568", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm only interested in Case Logic and Lowepro. What's the cheapest camera case you have from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Lowepro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Lowepro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Lowepro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'Lowepro') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_569", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Look, I need a camera case with either a lock or a zipper, just make sure it's not water resistant. What's the cheapest option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras` with asin: B005VTIMEQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'zipper') AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_570", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case but I only buy Sony or Altura Photo products. Out of these two brands, show me the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Altura Photo\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Altura Photo\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Altura Photo\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'Altura Photo') \nORDER BY price \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_764", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Will this bag fit my Canon 70-200 F4 lens?", "long_answer": "It does not appear so. According to the case compatibility, I've tested this with a Canon L-series 100-400 which perfectly fits, but that's smaller than your Canon 70-200 F4 lens. Thus, I believe your lens would not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon 70-200 F4 lens has larger size than Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon 70-200 F4 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_765", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does this medium case fit a Nikon D7100 with 18-300mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon L-series 100-400 and it fits perfectly. Your Nikon D7100 with 18-300mm lens has similar dimensions, so it should also fit nicely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Nikon D7100 with 18-300mm lens has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Nikon D7100 with 18-300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "search_qa_571", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I don't need any of that waterproof nonsense and I'm not a fan of Ape Case. Show me the cheapest camera case you've got that fits the criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Ape Case' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_766", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does this camera case suit formal occasions or professional environments?", "long_answer": "This camera case is well-made and durable, thanks to its nylon construction, but its aesthetic is better suited for casual or utilitarian purposes rather than formal or professional environments, which might call for a more refined appearance, such as that offered by leather.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_767", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is this camera case designed for easy retrieval of my folding travel tripod while hiking?", "long_answer": "Certainly, if your collapsible travel tripod conforms to a standard shape and size, it should comfortably slip into the dedicated tripod compartment of the camera case, ensuring swift access throughout your outdoor excursions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket do not have a function of accommodating very large or unusually shaped tripods that require more space or alternative attachment mechanisms than the pocket provides.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_826", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the camera accessible from the side of the Fastpack 200 without removing the backpack?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 is designed with side entry compartments that enable photographers to quickly access their camera and accessories without the need to remove the backpack, facilitating ease of use while on the move.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_572", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm looking to add a bit of color to my gear. Find me the cheapest camera case you have in either mica or purple.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"purple\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"purple\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"purple\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('mica', 'purple') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_768", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can I swiftly retrieve my camera for impromptu photography with this case?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the absence of a tripod mount on this case allows for quick access to your camera, making it perfect for effortlessly snapping those unanticipated, candid moments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_769", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is this case appropriate for outdoor photography where frequent adjustments to storage setups are needed?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the material is perfect for outdoor photography, offering the essential flexibility to effortlessly adjust the storage configurations to meet your specific needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_573", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I go all sorts of places with my Sony gear, even under wet conditions. I need a waterproof camera case for it. What's your recommendation for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Sony\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Sony\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Sony' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_770", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this case suitable for my camera when I predominantly engage in long-exposure photography and need to use a tripod?", "long_answer": "For long-exposure photography, which often necessitates stable camera support, this case may not be the most practical choice because it lacks an integrated tripod mounting system. To use a tripod, you would need to remove your camera from the case and mount it separately.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_574", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm specifically looking for Sony or Lowepro camera cases. Show me the cheapest one available.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Lowepro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Lowepro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Lowepro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'Lowepro') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_827", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera sling made from durable nylon both waterproof and weatherproof?", "long_answer": "The camera sling is not explicitly described as being waterproof or weatherproof by the product materials. Even though it is constructed from durable nylon, which might provide some protection against light rain, ensuring the camera's safety in heavy rain would likely require extra waterproofing precautions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_771", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate my 50-500 Sigma lenses?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to fit your 50-500 Sigma lenses. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens, which is similar in size, and it fits just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_575", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I don't care about water resistance and I am a fan of Pelican brand. Give me any Pelican camera case that doesn't have this feature.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Pelican\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Pelican\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Pelican' AND water_resistance = 'no';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_576", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I don't want anything fancy, just a camera case with no more than 2 pockets and a lock closure. What's my best option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND closure_type = \"locks\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND closure_type = \"locks\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'locks' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_828", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Does the case offer a built-in shoulder strap for over-the-shoulder or cross-body carrying?", "long_answer": "The case lacks a built-in shoulder strap; however, it is equipped with a belt loop and possibly a steel ring that could allow for the attachment of a personal strap for over-the-shoulder or cross-body carrying.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_772", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is the camera case intended for photographers who require rapid relocation between sites?", "long_answer": "Certainly, our camera cases are designed with active photographers in mind who require the ability to swiftly transition from one location to another. The omission of a tripod attachment feature facilitates a smooth experience, enabling rapid packing and unpacking of your camera equipment without additional procedures.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_577", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Look, I'm not going to be around water and I've only got 30 bucks to spare. What's the cheapest non-water-resistant camera case you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_773", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Will this case fit a Nikon D80 with a MB80 Grip?", "long_answer": "Absolutely, I use this with my Canon 70D with 70-250 lens and they are similar in size, so it should fit your Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_829", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case compatible with the Canon PowerShot SX230HS?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case is designed to be a perfect fit specifically for the Canon PowerShot SX230HS, ensuring compatibility between the case and the camera model.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_774", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can a Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens fit into this bag?", "long_answer": "No, I have tried this camera bag for my Nikon D3500 and it fits exactly, so I can't see a Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens being able to fit in here due to the larger size.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_775", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this camera case be convenient to carry on extended hikes?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is designed to be both lightweight and compact, making it an ideal option for lengthy treks when you wish to avoid carrying any extra weight or bulk. It is engineered to provide convenience and functionality, while scarcely increasing your load, perfectly suiting the needs of active and on-the-go photographers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_830", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the backpack large enough to accommodate a camera with an attached battery grip?", "long_answer": "Some camera models equipped with a battery grip can be accommodated by the backpack. To fit specific sizes of cameras and grips, however, it might necessitate adjustments or a bit of effort.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_578", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I hate mess and don't need pockets. Just get me a camera case with a lock and no extra pockets. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'locks' AND pockets = 0;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_579", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I hate pockets and velcro. Give me the first camera case you find without either of those.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND closure_type != 'velcro' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_580", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Black is a no-go for me and I don't need a ton of pockets. What's the most affordable camera case you have that isn't black and has less than or average number of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'black' AND pockets <= (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_581", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm only interested in either AmazonBasics or Canon for my camera case. What's the cheapest option you got from these two brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Canon\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Canon\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Canon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('AmazonBasics', 'Canon') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_582", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm picking between Pelican and AmazonBasics for the brand, and it's gotta have either a velcro or drawstring closure. Which camera case would you recommend?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'Pelican' OR brand = 'AmazonBasics') AND (closure_type = 'velcro' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_776", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does this case simplify the task of transporting my photography gear in busy areas?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case features straps specifically designed to attach a tripod to the outside. This frees your hands from having to carry the tripod, significantly easing transit through crowded spaces while ensuring your gear remains within easy reach.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with external straps for tripod attachment are ideally used for travel and outdoor photography where hands-free transit is essential, enhancing the photographer's ability to navigate difficult terrains or crowded locales without the burden of holding the tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "external straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_777", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "At times, I feel discomfort when carrying bags; is this camera case comfortable enough for me to carry over extended periods?", "long_answer": "Should you suffer from a medical condition or experience pain that could be exacerbated by bearing weight on one side, using a camera case with a shoulder strap may prove uncomfortable over extended periods. It is advisable to explore alternative carrying solutions that more evenly balance the weight throughout your body.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not suitable for users who may have medical conditions or pain that is exacerbated by carrying weight on one side of the body; other carrying options may be better in these cases.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_583", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm kinda into \"Ape Case\" and \"OP/TECH USA\". Pull up the first camera case you find from either brand for me.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"OP/TECH USA\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"OP/TECH USA\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Ape Case', 'OP/TECH USA') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_584", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm all about bold colors. Find me the cheapest camera case you've got in either orange or red.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"red\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"red\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"red\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('orange', 'red') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_831", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does this sling bag incorporate anti-theft features?", "long_answer": "This sling bag lacks specific anti-theft features but offers a discreet design allowing users to swing it forward, thereby increasing its security against potential theft.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_585", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm a fan of Velcro, buddy. Find me the cheapest camera case with Velcro closure you got in store.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"velcro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'velcro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_832", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the backpack fully waterproof?", "long_answer": "The backpack offers some water resistance due to the design of the zipper, which is placed on the back and is protected by a flap; however, the backpack is not marketed or designed to be completely waterproof.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_778", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can a Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens fit in this sling? ", "long_answer": "No, it won't fit. I have a Nikon D5000 with a battery grip and it just fits. Your Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens is larger than my device, so it wouldn't fit into this sling.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5000 with battery grip, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Nikon D5000 with battery grip, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5000 with battery grip"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_779", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this case appropriate for outdoor photography when frequent adjustments to storage configurations are necessary?", "long_answer": "Certainly, it is perfect for outdoor photography; the material offers the required flexibility, enabling you to easily adjust the storage setups to meet your needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_780", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for individuals with back issues?", "long_answer": "Considering that uneven weight distribution can negatively impact those with back problems, a camera case equipped with a shoulder strap might not be the best option. Such a case could worsen pain or discomfort. Therefore, it is advisable to seek out cases that provide alternative carrying methods to reduce back strain.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not suitable for users who may have medical conditions or pain that is exacerbated by carrying weight on one side of the body; other carrying options may be better in these cases.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_833", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the bag made from waterproof material?", "long_answer": "The material used to make the bag is not described as waterproof, implying that the bag may not provide protection against water without additional precautions. It is advisable to take protective measures when using the bag in adverse weather conditions to prevent any potential damage from moisture.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_834", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 camera bag too large to be convenient for day trips or hikes?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 camera bag is considered quite large, which might not be the most practical choice for day trips or hikes that require only minimal equipment. This suggests that some individuals might find the bag cumbersome for light-travel situations and would opt for a smaller alternative.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_586", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Got a thing for purple. Give me the product id of your first purple camera case you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"purple\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_587", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I like the color green and need a camera case that can handle a little rain. What's the cheapest one you have that checks both those boxes?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_781", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm quite interested in macro photography; does this case provide any support for that type of detailed work?", "long_answer": "Macro photography typically necessitates a stable camera to record fine details without any blur; however, this camera case lacks a tripod attachment feature, which is crucial for achieving such stability.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment do not have a function of providing a stable base for photography styles that demand a stationary camera, such as macro photography or astrophotography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_835", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Does the holster come with its own carrying handle or strap for independent use?", "long_answer": "The holster must be attached to your camera's strap using the provided tether, as it is not equipped with its own carrying handle or strap for independent carrying.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_836", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is this case suitable for carrying GoPro cameras and their accessories?", "long_answer": "This case is specifically designed to accommodate GoPro cameras and their accessories, offering sufficient space and ensuring their protection, making it a popular choice among GoPro users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_588", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I've got a thing against Pelican. Find me a purple camera case from any other brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Pelican\" AND color = \"purple\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Pelican\" AND color = \"purple\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'purple' AND brand != 'Pelican';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_837", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this camera backpack designed to accommodate a laptop?", "long_answer": "The backpack is primarily designed for carrying camera equipment and accessories. While some customers have successfully placed smaller laptops or tablets inside, the backpack is typically not sized to comfortably fit larger laptop devices.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_838", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera sling designed to be worn on both the left and right shoulder?", "long_answer": "The camera sling is designed predominantly to be worn across the body, with optimal rotation favoring the left shoulder for right-handed users, suggesting a design intended for right-handed access as reported by users.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_782", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the camera case make efficient use of space for carry-on luggage when flying?", "long_answer": "Considering the size limitations for carry-on baggage on flights, this camera case may not be the best choice for space economy because of its dedicated tripod pocket. The pocket could occupy extra space, making it more challenging to fit the case into smaller overhead bins or under-seat storage areas.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket fail to meet the requirements for a compact storage solution when space is a premium, such as for photographers needing to adhere to strict travel luggage constraints.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_839", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the main compartment of this backpack have protective features for safely carrying spare lenses?", "long_answer": "The primary compartment of the backpack is constructed with padded and adjustable dividers, specifically made to ensure the secure carrying and protection of additional lenses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_589", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case that's either orange or yellow, but anything with a drawstring is out of the question. Now which is your cheapest option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"yellow\") AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"yellow\") AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"yellow\") AND NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('orange', 'yellow') AND closure_type != 'drawstring' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_783", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I frequently take on photography assignments that necessitate carrying my equipment throughout the entire day. Would this case be appropriate for such use?", "long_answer": "When using a camera case for prolonged periods, such as toting your gear all day, choosing one with only a hand grip is typically not recommended. This carrying method may cause unease or tension because it fails to offer sufficient weight distribution and support for extremely heavy cameras and accessories.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip are not recommended for long-duration use or for transporting very heavy cameras and equipment, as this may result in discomfort or strain due to insufficient weight distribution and support.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_840", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Does the Ape Case Cubeze provide a discreet way to carry a camera in a regular bag during travel?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze is specifically designed as an insert that fits within any standard bag, thus providing a way to transport your camera discreetly without the exterior appearance of a typical camera bag. This feature makes it an excellent choice for travelers who wish to keep their camera inconspicuous.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_841", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the bag's padded shoulder strap provide comfort for prolonged carrying?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with a padded shoulder strap specifically designed to offer comfort during extended use. However, individual experiences with the bag's comfort level can differ, and some users may perceive the bag as too bulky, which affects the overall comfort when carried for long periods.", "short_answer": "It varies", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_590", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Drawstrings are my thing, but I'm not into that water-resistant stuff. Find me a camera case that's got a drawstring but isn't water-resistant.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring' AND water_resistance = 'no';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_784", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fit into this case? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it for a Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and your D80 with MB80 Grip is similar in size, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the Nikon D80 with MB80 Grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_785", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I require a case durable enough to withstand fieldwork demands and capable of accommodating all my photography gear. Would this be an appropriate selection?", "long_answer": "While this camera case may fall short for rigorous fieldwork involving a range of equipment, its absence of a tripod attachment is a significant drawback. Such a feature is essential for the safe transport and swift setup of standard professional photography gear, including tripods and external lights.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_591", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case, but I'm picky about color. It's gotta be either red or mica. Oh, and find me the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"mica\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"mica\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"red\", \"mica\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('red', 'mica') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_786", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is it reasonable to anticipate that this camera case will retain its shape throughout years of usage?", "long_answer": "Certainly, you can. The camera case is crafted from nylon, renowned for its stretch resistance. Consequently, the case maintains its form better over time, despite frequent use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_842", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the backpack have designated compartments for camera accessories such as lenses and flash units?", "long_answer": "The backpack includes a dedicated top compartment designed specifically for carrying extra lenses or flash units. It also features zippered mesh pockets in both the main and top compartments for the storage of smaller camera accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_843", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Fastpack 200 bag meet the size requirements for carry-on luggage on airlines?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 has dimensions that fall within the common size limits for carry-on luggage as set by many airlines, but travelers should verify with individual airlines since size allowances can vary.", "short_answer": "Check with airline", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_787", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can a Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens fit into this case?", "long_answer": "No, it will not. I have a Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and it barely fits into the case. The Rebel T3i with a long lens is larger, so I believe it won't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_592", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm not worried about it getting wet and I'm not a fan of Case Logic. Find me the cheapest camera case you have that's not water resistant and isn't from Case Logic.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND brand != 'Case Logic' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_788", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I worry about the durability of my camera case because I'm usually quite hard on my equipment. Would this be a wise purchase?", "long_answer": "Given your concerns, investing in this camera case would be prudent. The nylon fabric utilized for this case is known for its durability and abrasion resistance, indicating it is capable of withstanding rough handling and should provide extended protection for your equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_844", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Fastpack 200 backpack have a built-in tripod attachment system?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 backpack lacks an integrated system specifically designed for attaching tripods. However, users have improvised by utilizing other means, such as additional straps, to secure their tripods to the backpack.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_789", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Will this case accommodate my Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, it may not fit. The case has been designed to fit a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens, which is likely smaller than your Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_593", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case with either a drawstring or lock closure. And it should be either USA Gear or AmazonBasics brand. Can you find me one?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"AmazonBasics\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"locks\") AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"AmazonBasics\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'locks') AND (brand = 'USA Gear' OR brand = 'AmazonBasics');"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_790", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is it practical to transport a tripod along with this camera case when trekking to various photography locations?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the integrated dedicated tripod pocket simplifies the task of transporting your tripod. It offers a designated spot for your tripod that allows for swift access for setting up or removing as you traverse different photography spots, guaranteeing ease and effectiveness.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket are known for their convenience in allowing for quick attachment and detachment of tripods, which is particularly beneficial in dynamic shooting situations where setting up the shot swiftly is crucial.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_791", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, no. I have a Canon L-series 100-400 and it fills up the bag. Your Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens is larger, so it won't fit in this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "search_qa_594", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm sticking to my budget of 10 dollars, and I only trust Canon. What's the cheapest Canon case you have that I can afford?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand = \"Canon\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand = \"Canon\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Canon' AND price <= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_845", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the camera case designed to accommodate a charger in addition to the camera and small accessories?", "long_answer": "The camera case is designed to be compact, focusing on holding the camera and small accessories such as batteries and memory cards; therefore, it typically does not have enough space to store a charger.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_846", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack able to fit a professional DSLR camera with a 200mm lens attached?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack is specifically designed to accommodate a professional DSLR camera with a 200mm lens attached. Its construction takes into account the dimensions and requirements for safely housing a camera with such a lens, ensuring even a sizable 80-200mm f/2.8 lens fits along with additional camera accessories like extra lenses or flashes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_595", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I'm not interested in those flashy AmazonBasics camera cases with too many pockets. Just find me the simplest one they got, okay?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'AmazonBasics' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_596", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case with water resistance from the brand Altura Photo. What's your least expensive one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_792", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Could this case alleviate the pressure on my wrist while transporting my professional photography gear?", "long_answer": "A camera case equipped with a hand grip could potentially elevate the strain on your wrist when lugging around professional, heftier camera gear. This is because it focuses the weight on the hand, potentially amplifying strain and discomfort rather than alleviating it. With hefty equipment, a case that more evenly disperses weight would be advantageous.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a hand grip fail to meet the requirements for heavy-duty use where substantial weight distribution across the torso is necessary, as they concentrate the camera's weight onto one point of the hand.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "hand grip", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_597", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I hate the sound of velcro, so give me the Altura Photo camera case with the least amount of pockets that doesn't have a velcro closure.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND closure_type != 'velcro' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_598", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm only interested in stuff from Sony and Ape Case. Can you pick out a camera case from one of them for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Ape Case\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Sony\", \"Ape Case\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Sony', 'Ape Case') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_847", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack accommodate a DSLR camera along with several lenses?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack is specifically designed with enough room to comfortably store a DSLR camera equipped with a standard zoom lens. It also features a top compartment that can hold additional lenses or flash units, making it spacious enough for multiple photography accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_793", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I relish capturing images in dynamic settings. Is this case designed to accommodate such activities?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case thrives in swift-moving settings. Its design, omitting a tripod attachment, lessens impediments and facilitates rapid and effortless access to your camera, ensuring you can snap those ephemeral moments with the slightest of pauses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_599", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I've heard good things about AmazonBasics and Ape Case. Show me the first camera case you have from either of these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Ape Case\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Ape Case\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('AmazonBasics', 'Ape Case') ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_600", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Hey, my maximum spending's 50 dollars and I'm sort of obsessed with this teal color. Could you find me a camera case fitting those specifics?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras` with asin: B001I3X3HU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND color = \"teal\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND color = \"teal\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND color = 'teal';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_601", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm totally hooked on Pelican brand. Could you figure out the cheapest Pelican camera case for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases WHERE brand = 'Pelican' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_848", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is this case compatible with a Canon PowerShot camera based on its dimensions?", "long_answer": "If the dimensions of the Canon PowerShot camera are within 4.3 inches by 2.5 inches by 0.9 inches, the camera should fit comfortably in the case as customers have confirmed a snug fit for similar-sized cameras.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_602", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm willing to drop 50 bucks max, but I'm not a fan of Ape Case. Can you show me the least expensive camera case that isn't from them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 AND NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Ape Case' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_794", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is the case shock-absorbent for when I travel?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the neoprene material of the case is engineered to absorb impacts, rendering it a perfect selection for protecting your camera while on the move.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with neoprene material feature good cushioning and impact absorption, which is critical for protecting sensitive camera equipment against the risks of accidental drops and mishandling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "neoprene", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_849", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the padding in the backpack sufficient to protect delicate camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The backpack comes with adjustable padded dividers and overall cushioning that aim to offer protection for camera and associated delicate equipment. Nonetheless, there are user concerns indicating that the padding, especially around the zippers, might benefit from being more robust to enhance equipment safety.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_603", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I've had it with USA Gear, don't want to see anything from them. Direct me to the cheapest camera case from any other brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'USA Gear' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_850", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the main compartment zipper operate smoothly?", "long_answer": "The zipper on the main compartment is designed to function smoothly, yet there are occasional reports of it requiring extra effort. To enhance its operation, regular maintenance such as lubricating the zipper with wax is recommended.", "short_answer": "occasionally", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_795", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is this case appropriate for outdoor photography when frequent adjustments to storage configurations are necessary?", "long_answer": "Indeed, it is perfect for outdoor photography since the material offers the required versatility, enabling you to effortlessly adjust the storage setups according to your needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are ideally used for situations that require flexibility in storage and transportation, such as folding the case when empty or adjusting to accommodate various camera sizes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_604", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Orange just doesn't go with anything I own. Dig out the cheapest camera case you have that's NOT orange.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"orange\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'orange' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_796", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this camera case keep a discreet appearance while accommodating all my equipment?", "long_answer": "When transporting a tripod, be aware that camera bags featuring a specific section for tripod storage may not be discrete. The protruding shape of such a compartment could inadvertently indicate the presence of expensive gear, thus possibly attracting undesired notice.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket lack the capability to remain sleek and inconspicuous, as the protrusion or shape of the pocket may reveal the storage of valuable equipment, potentially drawing unwanted attention.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_605", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I don't want a case with a bunch of extra pockets and I don't want to spend more than a hundred dollars. Tell me what's the best option for me.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND pockets <= 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND pockets <= 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND price <= 100 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_797", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can this pouch hold a Canon 600D?", "long_answer": "Yes. The pouch is compatible with the Nikon D90 which is a similar size to the Canon 600D, so it should fit your 600D model just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Canon 600D has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Canon 600D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_798", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this camera case accommodate my gear for professional shoots where I may need multiple equipment options?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case features a specialized pocket for a tripod, enabling you to transport a tripod with your other professional gear. However, consider that this can increase the case's weight and size, which could affect your transportation and storage choices.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket are not suitable for photographers who prioritize the most lightweight and minimalist gear setup, as this feature may add to the bulk and weight of the case.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_606", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I can't stand drawstring closures and I don't want anything with more than 2 pockets. Show me the cheapest camera case you got that fits these criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND pockets <= 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND pockets <= 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'drawstring' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_799", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Should my drink inadvertently be spilled on the camera case, will the camera inside remain safeguarded from harm?", "long_answer": "Since this case isn't waterproof, it won't offer complete protection from spills. Minor splashes may not be harmful, yet there is a considerable risk that a substantial spill may penetrate and harm your camera. Opting for a waterproof camera case would provide superior defense against such incidents.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_800", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon EOS 5Ds?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits perfectly. The dimensions of the Canon EOS 5Ds are similar so it should work.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS 5Ds has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS 5Ds fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_851", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the internal dividers of the main compartment be adjusted to accommodate various equipment sizes?", "long_answer": "The internal dividers in the main compartment are designed to be customizable and can be adjusted to better fit and secure items of different sizes according to the user's equipment needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_607", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Velcro closure is a no-go for me, and don't worry about water resistance feature. Sift out the cheapest camera case in your product list that meets these criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras` with asin: B005VTIMEQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"velcro\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'velcro' AND water_resistance != 'yes' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_852", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Does the bag have designated compartments for storing small items?", "long_answer": "The bag contains two interior pockets featuring hook/loop closures specifically designed for holding small items such as personal electronics or various accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_608", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm an outdoor kinda guy, so I need a water resistant camera case. I particularly like USA Gear and Ape Case. Can you pull up the cheapest one you got from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR` with asin: B005J09OXU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Ape Case\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Ape Case\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Ape Case\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'USA Gear' OR brand = 'Ape Case') AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_801", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for an individual who frequently travels with their gear?", "long_answer": "Certainly. For someone who travels often, the nylon fabric of this camera case is beneficial because of its considerable tensile strength. This ensures it will withstand tearing and handle the demands of frequent traveling well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_853", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "What is the level of durability of the material used in constructing the backpack?", "long_answer": "The backpack is constructed using robust, water-resistant nylon, designed to endure frequent usage and provide lasting protection for the user's equipment, particularly aimed at professional individuals who may utilize the backpack on a regular basis.", "short_answer": "high durability", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_609", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm only interested in Canon brand stuff and I'm feeling either black or red. What's the first camera case you have that fits those specifics?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"red\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"red\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Canon' AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'red') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_854", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the Caselogic SLRC-202 camera bag capable of holding a Nikon D7100, a flash, and multiple lenses?", "long_answer": "The Caselogic SLRC-202 camera bag is specifically designed to accommodate a camera body, like the Nikon D7100, with an attached lens. Additionally, it has side compartments that provide space for a flash and at least one extra lens, with capacity varying based on the dimensions of the additional lenses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_610", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I'm only interested in camera cases made by AmazonBasics or Pelican. Which one is the least expensive?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Pelican\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Pelican\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"AmazonBasics\", \"Pelican\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('AmazonBasics', 'Pelican') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_611", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I hate cases with too many compartments. Find me a yellow or purple camera case that has one or no pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"purple\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"purple\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (color = 'yellow' OR color = 'purple') AND pockets <= 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_612", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I ain't planning to take photos under the rain, so no need for pricy water resistance stuff. Can you dig up the cheapest non-waterproof camera case that's 30 dollars or less?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price <= 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND price <= 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_802", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this camera case appropriate for a photographer who carries a full-sized professional tripod during travels?", "long_answer": "No, this camera case is not suitable for a photographer traveling with a full-sized professional tripod as the compartment isn't large enough for bigger tripods, possibly resulting in the need to carry an additional bag for the tripod.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod compartment cannot be used for conveniently storing larger professional tripods that exceed the size limitations of the pocket, which could lead to inconvenience or the need for additional carrying solutions for such equipment.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_613", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "No way I'm buying any AmazonBasic stuff. Get me the cheapest camera case under 50 bucks that doesn't come with plenty of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND price < 50 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND price < 50 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND price < 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 50 AND brand != 'AmazonBasics' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_855", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the main compartment of the bag capable of accommodating an SLR camera body with a zoom lens attached?", "long_answer": "The bag features a main compartment meant to store an SLR camera body with a kit lens attached. For larger zoom lenses, it's essential to check the combined dimensions of the camera body and lens to ensure they will fit properly in the bag.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_856", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera sling compact enough to meet carry-on requirements for flights?", "long_answer": "The camera sling's compact design enables it to fit under airline seats and in overhead compartments, making it suitable as a carry-on item for air travel according to customer reports.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_857", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is the camera box inside the bag removable for alternative uses of the bag?", "long_answer": "The camera bag is designed with versatility in mind, featuring a fully padded camera box that can be removed. Once taken out, the space can be repurposed for personal items, thus allowing the bag to be used in various situations aside from just carrying camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_858", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the camera case have sufficient space and features for convenient travel use?", "long_answer": "The camera case is equipped with a well-made sling that accommodates a camera, a couple of lenses, and has additional pockets, which many customers find perfect for travel purposes due to the convenience and space provided.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_803", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Should I inadvertently spill a beverage on my camera case, will the camera remain protected?", "long_answer": "The case material possesses a degree of water resistance capable of shielding your camera from minor spills. Nevertheless, it is not completely waterproof, so promptly cleaning up spills is advisable to prevent possible damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_859", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Lowepro Fastpack 200 backpack considered bulky by users for daily usage?", "long_answer": "While the Lowepro Fastpack 200 backpack is designed to protect and store camera equipment compactly, its ideal use case aligns with users needing to carry considerable camera gear. Due to its focus on protective storage for such equipment, some users do find the backpack to be slightly bulky for everyday, non-photography-related use.", "short_answer": "some users yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_860", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack have a dedicated system for attaching a tripod securely?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack is equipped with a dedicated and reliable system specifically designed for secure tripod attachment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_804", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Would my Canon EOS Rebel T3i fit in this case?", "long_answer": "Yes, it would. I have a Nikon D90 which is about the same size as your Canon EOS Rebel T3i and it fits perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_861", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the padding of this bag sufficient to protect its contents from serious drops or impacts?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with padding designed to shield against everyday use and minor impacts. However, it does not have enough cushioning to fully safeguard the contents from damage caused by substantial drops or severe impacts.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_805", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "During my photographic journeys, I often transition between various sites; will my case remain compact and manageable?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case remains compact and easy to maneuver while on the go. The nylon construction ensures it is light and provides a tight fit for your camera gear, perfect for travel photography that requires constant movement.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_614", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm not a fan of green and I'm loyal to Case Logic. What's the first Case Logic camera case you have that isn't green?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)` with asin: B00WUIIH8W", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND brand = \"Case Logic\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND brand = \"Case Logic\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Case Logic' AND color != 'green' ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_862", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "How comfortable is the bag when worn for extended periods of time?", "long_answer": "The bag is generally considered comfortable by most users because it has padded straps and distributes weight evenly. However, some users suggest that a wider waistbelt might enhance comfort further, especially when carrying heavier items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_615", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I don't need any fancy pockets, just a basic camera case. I prefer OP/TECH USA or USA Gear brands, however don't show me something expensive. What's the cheapest option?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"USA Gear\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"USA Gear\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"USA Gear\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('OP/TECH USA', 'USA Gear') AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_806", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate a small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E?", "long_answer": "Yes, it fits perfectly with Canon L-series 100-400, and your camera size is similar to that, so it should fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the small prime like a 50/1.4 or 90 TS-E fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "search_qa_616", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm working with a strict budget of 30 dollars and I can't stand the color teal. What's the first camera case you can show me that meets these conditions?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND NOT color = \"teal\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND NOT color = \"teal\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND color != 'teal' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_617", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm looking for a red camera case without the bells and whistles, just basic. What's your cheapest option?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND water_resistance = \"no\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND pockets = 0 AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_618", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I don't want some purple case that can't take a splash. Give me your cheapest camera case that's any color but purple and doesn't claim to be water-resistant.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color <> 'purple' AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_863", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the shoulder strap of the bag designed to provide comfort through padding?", "long_answer": "The shoulder strap of the bag is designed with padding to distribute weight evenly and enhance comfort during use. The strap is also removable, allowing for flexibility in how the bag is carried.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_864", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the AmazonBasics camera case include a limited warranty?", "long_answer": "AmazonBasics offers a limited warranty for their camera case, but the exact terms and duration of the warranty should be checked in the warranty documentation or product details.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_865", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this camera case compatible with newer Canon Powershot models?", "long_answer": "The case is made to fit certain models, such as the A650IS and A720IS, explicitly. While it is not guaranteed for newer models, some customers have reported that they were able to fit other newer Powershot models into the case comfortably. It is advisable to verify the case dimensions and ensure compatibility with any new model before making a purchase.", "short_answer": "Check compatibility", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_866", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is the backpack suitable for carrying both a camera and a large laptop?", "long_answer": "The backpack's primary purpose is to store cameras and related accessories. It may accommodate a small tablet or slim laptop, but it is not designed to fit larger laptops effectively.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_867", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the bag have a dedicated pocket for carrying a water bottle?", "long_answer": "The bag lacks a dedicated pocket specifically designed for carrying a water bottle, a feature that some users have expressed a desire to have.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_868", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is there a warranty or satisfaction guarantee offered with the backpack?", "long_answer": "The backpack comes with a Digital Goja 90-Day 100% Satisfaction Guarantee, ensuring that customers can purchase with confidence knowing they have this period to assess their satisfaction with the product.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_619", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "I don't like anything from Altura Photo, but I do need a camera case in black or yellow. Find me one with the least amount of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"black\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"black\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" AND color IN (\"yellow\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Altura Photo' AND color IN ('black', 'yellow') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_807", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Can this case fit a 50-500 Sigma lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it can. I use it with my Nikon D5200 and two lenses. If the size of your lens is similar to mine, it should fit perfectly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D5200 with 2 lenses"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_869", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the tripod attachment intended to be placed on the side of the backpack?", "long_answer": "The tripod attachment is specifically designed to fit on the bottom of the backpack, and attaching a tripod to the side would require user customization with additional hardware and is done at the user's own risk.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_620", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I can't stand cases with too many pockets, they're just a mess. Get me the cheapest case from Ape Case or Lowepro with less than two pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Lowepro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Lowepro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 2 AND brand IN (\"Ape Case\", \"Lowepro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Ape Case', 'Lowepro') AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_870", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the bag come with padded compartments for safely storing camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with padded side storage pockets and interior compartments, providing protection for your camera and accessories.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_808", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag fit a Canon T3i with a 300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and it fits perfectly. The size of your Canon T3i with a 300mm lens should be similar to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Canon T3i with 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Canon T3i with 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_809", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a Canon 70D with 135mm zoom?", "long_answer": "Yes, it can. This bag fits my Canon 10-22mm lens just fine and your Canon 70D with 135mm zoom seems to have similar dimensions, so it should fit well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_810", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is this camera case capable of protecting my equipment when I encounter rain on my photography excursions?", "long_answer": "The camera case under consideration is engineered to be light and compact, perfect for use in dry settings. Its functionality is optimized for non-wet environments, so it might not offer complete protection in the rain. If you often find yourself in damp conditions, it would be wise to opt for a case with waterproof features.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof feature design elements focused more on lightweight, compactness, and functionality in dry conditions rather than full protection against all elements.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_871", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for cameras come with a dedicated rain cover for weather protection?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Sling Backpack is not equipped with a dedicated rain cover to protect a camera in adverse weather conditions. However, for those seeking to safeguard their camera gear against the rain, it is suggested by users to treat the backpack with a water-repellent spray for additional protection.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_811", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is this camera case designed to protect my equipment in extremely cold conditions?", "long_answer": "Though the camera case is crafted from robust material, it should be noted that its nylon composition does not provide the best insulation in severely cold conditions. For extreme temperatures, a case designed with specialized thermal materials would be more suitable to safeguard your camera gear.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_812", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Do these camera cases accommodate photographers who favor minimalist gear configurations?", "long_answer": "Indeed, they do. Our camera cases are designed for photographers who favor a minimalistic style. By excluding a tripod attachment feature, our cases provide a simple, swift means for stowing and retrieving your camera, thus ideally enhancing a streamlined gear configuration.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_872", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "What is the material composition of the camera case?", "long_answer": "The camera case is made from durable tough nylon material, which not only adds to its durability but also offers a degree of protection for the camera equipment inside.", "short_answer": "tough nylon", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_813", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for formal occasions or professional environments?", "long_answer": "This camera case is expertly made and durable, thanks to its nylon fabrication. However, its aesthetic is better suited for casual or utilitarian purposes rather than formal or professional environments, where the refined appearance of leather might be more desirable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_814", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can I use this backpack for my Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with a 70-250 lens and it fits perfectly. Your Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens should have a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Nikon D90 with a 55-300 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_815", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I frequently hike with my camera in tow; is this case durable enough to resist constant abrasion from rough surfaces such as rocks or branches?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is crafted from nylon, specifically selected for its durability against wear from continuous contact with abrasive surfaces. Its robust resistance to abrasion ensures it can withstand the demands of hiking and interactions with elements like rocks or branches.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_816", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Do I have to bring an additional bag for my heavy-duty tripod if I'm using this camera case?", "long_answer": "Certainly, should your heavy-duty tripod exceed the size constraints of the dedicated tripod compartment in your camera case, an alternate carrying solution will be necessary since the compartment isn't intended for oversized professional tripods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod compartment cannot be used for conveniently storing larger professional tripods that exceed the size limitations of the pocket, which could lead to inconvenience or the need for additional carrying solutions for such equipment.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_873", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this backpack suitable as a gift for a photography enthusiast, considering its features and user feedback?", "long_answer": "The backpack's design, which accommodates the needs of photography enthusiasts and has received positive feedback, suggests that it would be a practical and appreciated gift for someone with an interest in photography.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_874", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the entire camera bag waterproof?", "long_answer": "The camera bag incorporates a semi-rigid, molded, water-resistant EVA base, which provides a certain level of protection against elements such as water. However, it's important to acknowledge that only the base has this water-resistant feature, and the rest of the bag does not have a waterproof classification. Therefore, while the base can guard against moisture, the bag as a whole is not fully waterproof.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_817", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I frequently shoot in windy conditions; can this case still be used effectively?", "long_answer": "Under blustery conditions, maintaining camera stability is crucial, particularly in disciplines such as landscape photography, where even slight movements can result in blurred photographs. Regrettably, this particular case lacks a tripod attachment, potentially rendering it less efficient at securing your camera's steadiness in these scenarios.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_875", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "How does the memory foam padding in this camera bag compare to the padding in other camera bags?", "long_answer": "The memory foam padding in this particular camera bag is specifically designed to offer enhanced protection for your LCD screen, ensuring it remains safe during transportation or storage. Additionally, the high-quality materials used in the bag's construction contribute to superior overall padding, safeguarding the rest of your photography equipment.", "short_answer": "superior", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_818", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is this case suitable for a wedding photographer to carry around?", "long_answer": "Given that a professional appearance is typically expected at weddings, a camera case sporting backpack straps could clash with the formal dress code, appearing overly casual for such occasions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are not recommended for situations that demand rapid gear changes or a professional appearance that aligns with formal event dress codes, as a backpack might be viewed as too casual or cumbersome in such environments.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_819", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the tripod attachment on the camera case sufficiently secure for travel photography, where I am frequently on the go?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case features a dependable tripod attachment system that utilizes hook and loop fasteners, perfect for travel photography where quick setup is crucial as you move from one location to the next. The design guarantees that your tripod stays firmly connected to your case and can be removed swiftly when required.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with tripod attachment using hook and loop fastener are ideally used for lightweight to moderate-weight tripods in conditions where convenience and speed are prioritized, such as in event photography or quick-paced travel scenarios.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "hook and loop fastener", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_876", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Does the backpack provide sufficient pockets and compartments for organizing accessories?", "long_answer": "The backpack includes several pockets and compartments designed to help organize various accessories and gear, which customers have frequently acknowledged and appreciated.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_621", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm not a fan of red, and I'm only interested in Pelican or OP/TECH USA brands. Can you find me the camera case from these brands with the least number of pockets, please?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND NOT color = \"red\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND NOT color = \"red\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND NOT color = \"red\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Pelican', 'OP/TECH USA') AND color != 'red' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_622", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I've had enough of OP/TECH USA stuff. Give me the cheapest camera case that's not from them.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand <> 'OP/TECH USA' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_820", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is this camera case adequate for safeguarding my gear during rigorous outdoor pursuits?", "long_answer": "When participating in rigorous outdoor activities, you might favor a camera case that offers a more solid structure for enhanced protection. Cases crafted from nylon materials generally exhibit a degree of flexibility, which suggests they might not provide the level of structural integrity you desire under those conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_821", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a Canon 1100D?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to accommodate a Canon 1100D. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and the bag fits it well. So, given its similar size, the Canon 1100D should also fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon 1100D has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon 1100D fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_623", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Look, I've had it with Case Logic. Gimme the cheapest camera case from another brand and it shouldn't cost me more than 50 bucks.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" AND price < 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Case Logic\" AND price < 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Case Logic' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_822", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Could you recommend this case for safeguarding professional photography gear during high-risk fieldwork?", "long_answer": "In high-risk field assignments where the safety of professional photography equipment is paramount, I would advise against a camera case with a shoulder strap. Such cases, due to their allowance for movement, might not offer the necessary protection against impacts or drops. A durable, rigid case specifically engineered to fully immobilize the equipment is preferable in these scenarios.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap cannot be used for circumstances where a rigid case is necessary due to extreme conditions or when full immobility of the equipment is required, as the mobility afforded by straps may not provide sufficient protection in these scenarios.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_877", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the main compartment of this camera bag spacious compared to those of other camera bags?", "long_answer": "The main compartment of this camera bag is reported by users as adequately spacious to accommodate a significant amount of gear, striking a balance by not being excessively large or too small, which suggests it is relatively comparable in size to other camera bags.", "short_answer": "just right", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_878", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "When the bag is filled to its maximum capacity, do its padded shoulder straps and additional support mechanisms ensure comfort for the wearer?", "long_answer": "The backpack is equipped with padded shoulder straps and back support, along with chest and waist straps, all of which contribute to wearer comfort. Nevertheless, there is the possibility that the bag could still feel heavy to some users when it is packed to its full capacity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_879", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can the ACPRO2000 camera bag fit a large DSLR with an attached telephoto lens?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 camera bag is capable of fitting a large DSLR with an attached telephoto lens, thanks to its spacious interior and customizable dividers that cater to bulky camera setups.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_823", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I like creating time-lapse videos; would this case benefit my workflow?", "long_answer": "In time-lapse photography, it's essential to keep your camera completely motionless for prolonged durations, usually requiring the use of a tripod. Since this camera case lacks a tripod mount, it might not be the best option for your time-lapse endeavors that demand stable support.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_880", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Will the Ape Case Cubeze remain stable inside most backpacks without an anchor system?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze is designed to fit inside most backpacks, but it lacks an integrated anchor system. To ensure stability and prevent it from tipping over or moving around excessively, it should fit snugly or be secured with other items in the backpack.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_824", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does this camera bag offer convenient quick-access for my collapsible travel tripod while hiking?", "long_answer": "Certainly, if your collapsible travel tripod conforms to a standard shape and size, it ought to fit snugly into the dedicated tripod pocket of the camera case, ensuring swift access throughout your outdoor expeditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket do not have a function of accommodating very large or unusually shaped tripods that require more space or alternative attachment mechanisms than the pocket provides.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_825", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Will this bag accommodate my Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens? ", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, this bag might not be able to accommodate your Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens. I use it for my Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and your camera seems to be larger than my setup.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_881", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does the retaining strap on the camera case interfere with taking photos?", "long_answer": "The camera case's retaining strap is specifically designed not to interfere with the process of taking photographs, and most users report it being useful for keeping the case attached and out of the way. However, for those who find it unnecessary or cumbersome, the strap is detachable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_826", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a 70-200/2.8 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it can fit a 70-200/2.8 lens. I have a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens and it fits just fine, and your lens is similar in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the 70-200/2.8 lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the 70-200/2.8 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_827", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Should my drink inadvertently get spilled on the camera case, would the camera inside remain safeguarded from harm?", "long_answer": "Since this case is not waterproof, it does not offer complete protection from spills. A minimal amount of liquid may not result in damage, yet there remains a considerable chance that a substantial spill might penetrate and harm your camera. Opting for a waterproof camera case would enhance security against such mishaps.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof do not have a function of providing a hermetic seal, and thus offer limited protection in wet environments, increasing the risk to the camera from water ingress.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_624", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I don't need any extra pockets but it has to be water resistant, alright? So tell me, which is the cheapest camera case you have that matches my needs?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_828", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can I rely on this case to maintain my camera's form while it's inside my bag?", "long_answer": "If keeping your camera's shape intact within your bag matters to you, note that this camera case is made of nylon, a naturally flexible material, and may not hold a stiff shape when pressed, potentially permitting slight alterations to the camera's form.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_882", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this bag durable and suitable for outdoor activities such as hiking or urban exploration?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to be durable and suitable for outdoor activities. According to customer feedback, the bag withstands the rigors of outdoor use, such as hiking and urban exploration, while also offering accessible storage for camera gear and other essentials.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_625", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I got a thing for teal. Tell me, what's the least expensive teal-colored camera case you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras` with asin: B001I3X3HU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'teal' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_883", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Does the bag become more flexible with use over time?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed in such a way that it may feel stiff at first, but with regular handling and use, it tends to become more flexible and pliable.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_829", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I require a case durable enough to withstand the demands of fieldwork and capable of accommodating all my photography gear. Is this an appropriate selection?", "long_answer": "The camera case might fall short for rigorous fieldwork involving diverse gear, given it's missing the essential tripod attachment feature needed for the secure transport and rapid setup of commonly used professional photography equipment such as tripods and external lights.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_626", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I don't need a bunch of pockets and I can't spend over $50. Show me the least pocketed, reasonably priced camera case you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND price < 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) AND price < 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 50 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_830", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can I use this bag for my Nikon D7100 with a Sigma 18-250 attached? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it for my Canon L-series 100-400 which is a similar size to your Nikon D7100 with Sigma 18-250 attached.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Nikon D7100 with Sigma 18-250 attached has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Nikon D7100 with Sigma 18-250 attached fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_884", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the camera in the sling bag protected from impacts effectively?", "long_answer": "The sling bag is equipped with a specialized hammock system that suspends the camera body within the case, which is designed to prevent the camera from hitting the bottom and absorb impact forces, thereby offering effective protection for the camera.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_831", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Will my tripod remain secure from inadvertent bumps if it's transported in this camera case while trekking?", "long_answer": "No, attaching your tripod to this camera case using the external straps provided can raise the chance of accidental bumps since the tripod would remain exposed, rather than nestled securely within the case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with external straps for tripod attachment lack the capability to provide as much protection for the tripod compared to internal storage, as it is exposed to the elements and potential impacts.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "external straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_885", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case compatible with a Canon Powershot camera?", "long_answer": "The AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case is indeed designed to accommodate most point and shoot cameras, Canon Powershots included. To ensure compatibility, it is essential to compare the case's internal dimensions of 4.3\" x 2.5\" x 0.9\" with the camera's dimensions to ensure it will fit properly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_832", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I take pleasure in photographing in dynamic settings. Is this case designed to accommodate such activities?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case thrives in dynamic settings. Its design, which lacks a tripod connection, minimizes hindrances and facilitates rapid access to your camera, so you can snap those ephemeral scenes with slight delay.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are ideally used for dynamic shooting environments, such as street photography, where mobility and the ability to shoot quickly from hand are advantageous.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_833", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is it possible to transport the camera case without utilizing a shoulder strap, allowing for hands-free carrying?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case has a feature that allows for secure attachment to your waist, offering a hands-free carrying alternative and eliminating the necessity of a shoulder strap.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop feature unique ergonomic benefits, contributing to an even weight distribution that minimizes strain when carried on the hip for extended periods.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_834", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can I use this with my Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not. I have a Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens and it fits just right. Your camera is larger with the 55-250mm lens so it likely will not fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_835", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Will this case fit my 6D w/24-105mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, this case will fit your 6D w/24-105mm lens. I use it for my Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and the dimensions are similar.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the 6D w/24-105mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the 6D w/24-105mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_886", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is the size of the bag too bulky for convenient travel?", "long_answer": "The perception of the bag's size varies among customers; however, a significant number consider it suitably sized for travel as it provides sufficient space without being overly cumbersome, allowing travelers the convenience of storing all their necessary equipment in one place.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_627", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Zippers always snag for me and I hate that, and too many pockets confuse me. Find me your cheapest camera case without a zipper and with two pockets or less.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets <= 2 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets <= 2 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'zipper' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_836", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "If I frequently use the camera case near bodies of water, will the protection diminish more rapidly?", "long_answer": "Indeed, regular contact with water can accelerate the deterioration of water resistance, thus it is crucial to apply waterproofing treatments more regularly to maintain the waterproof capability of the camera case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof attributes feature maintenance requirements such as periodic treatments with water repellent sprays to maintain their high protection level against water.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_887", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the backpack compact enough to fit under an airplane seat or overhead bin?", "long_answer": "Although the product information does not specifically mention compatibility with airplane storage, customer feedback indicates that the backpack's size is sufficiently compact to fit under an airplane seat or in an overhead bin.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_888", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the bag have a dedicated external pocket suitable for storing items such as manuals, maps, or notebooks?", "long_answer": "The bag features a large zippered slip pocket located on the back panel, specifically designed for storing items like manuals, maps, or notebooks, allowing for easy access and organization.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_837", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Can I fit my Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens into this case? ", "long_answer": "Unfortunately no, the case fits a Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens and your Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens is bigger than that.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_628", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Fancy colors like orange or purple really suit my style. Could you find me the cheapest camera case in either of those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"purple\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"purple\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"purple\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('orange', 'purple') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_838", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Can a 15 1/2 inches long lens fit in this pouch?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it for my Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and they fit perfectly. If your lens is around the same size as mine, it will fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the 15 1/2 inches long lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the 15 1/2 inches long lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_889", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is there a built-in tripod mount on this backpack?", "long_answer": "This backpack does not come with a built-in tripod mount; however, users have improvised by using the side mesh pocket along with a velcro strap to carry a tripod securely.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_629", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case that can handle the rain and has a drawstring closure. Can you find me something like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND closure_type = 'drawstring';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_630", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm only interested in either Lowepro or Ape Case brands, and I don't care if the darn thing can swim or not. Can you locate the least expensive camera case from these two brands that isn't water resistant?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"Ape Case\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"Ape Case\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"Ape Case\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN('Lowepro', 'Ape Case') AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_631", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I need a camera case that isn't too flashy, preferably mica or black. Can you find me one that has the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"black\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"black\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"mica\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('mica', 'black') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_632", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I like to keep things organized and I'm quite fond of the color yellow. Can you find me a yellow camera case with the least number of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'yellow' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_839", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the case sturdy enough to endure regular use outdoors?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is made from nylon, a material valued for its exceptional tensile strength, imparting resistance to tearing and stretching, hence guaranteeing longevity even with heavy use outdoors.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_840", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I frequently go hiking with my camera equipment. Is this case built to reduce the burden on extended treks?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this case has been thoughtfully designed to meet your requirements. Crafted from EVA, a material renowned for its lightweight properties, it is perfect for minimizing fatigue and guaranteeing that your camera equipment remains unburdening throughout extended treks.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with material described as EVA are known for their lightweight nature, providing ease of transport and reducing fatigue for photographers who carry their equipment for extended durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "eva", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_633", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I don't fancy zippers, so can you pull up an OP/TECH USA camera case that doesn't have one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' AND closure_type != 'zipper';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_841", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can a d3300 fit into this backpack?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and it fits perfectly, which is pretty similar in size to a d3300.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the d3300 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the d3300 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_634", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I'm not a fan of Sony and I prefer drawstring cases. What's the cheapest non-Sony drawstring camera case you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT brand = \"Sony\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT brand = \"Sony\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT brand = \"Sony\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Sony' AND closure_type = 'drawstring' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_635", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I have a Canon, but I don't care about the water resistance. Just give me the first Canon case you find that doesn't have that feature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Canon\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Canon' AND water_resistance = 'no' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_842", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I like capturing time-lapse footage; could this case benefit my workflow?", "long_answer": "In time-lapse photography, it is essential to keep your camera completely stationary for prolonged intervals, often requiring the use of a tripod. Since this camera case lacks a tripod mount, it may not be the best option for your time-lapse endeavors where consistent stability is vital.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment are not suitable for photographers who frequently undertake genres of photography that involve slow shutter speeds, where even the slightest movement can result in blur.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_636", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I can't stand Pelican brand, anything but them! Show me the cheapest camera case you have that isn't a Pelican.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Pelican\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Pelican\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Pelican\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Pelican' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_890", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is the backpack designed for compactness suitable for city street photography?", "long_answer": "The backpack's design aims to provide a balance between compactness and gear protection, which is deemed suitable for city use and street photography. The suitability for street photography, though, can be subjective and varies according to individual preferences regarding bag size.", "short_answer": "suitable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_891", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Can the interior dividers of the bag be reconfigured according to the user's needs?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed with padded dividers that are adjustable, providing the flexibility to customize the interior space in order to accommodate different sizes and shapes of camera equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_892", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the bag's base allow it to remain upright unassisted?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with a waterproof EVA base designed to provide the stability needed for the bag to stand up on its own without any support.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_637", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I need a camera case and I've only got 30 dollars to spare. Also, it needs to be green or teal. Oh, and it must have the fewest pockets. Can you find me one like this?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND color IN (\"green\", \"teal\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND color IN (\"green\", \"teal\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND color IN (\"green\", \"teal\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'teal') \nORDER BY pockets ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_893", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the Canon 200DG camera bag provide full waterproof protection for camera equipment?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG camera bag is crafted from water-repellent nylon and includes a weather-flap lid that offers protection against light rain and similar elements. However, it does not provide complete waterproofing that would safeguard equipment in more severe wet conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_638", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I don't need any of that fancy water-resistant nonsense. What's the first non-water-resistant camera case you have listed?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_639", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm not a fan of purple at all. So can you find me a camera case that has the fewest pockets and isn't purple?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color <> 'purple' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_640", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm only after 'Lowepro' or 'Ape Case' brands. Fetch me the first product you got from either brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"Ape Case\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"Ape Case\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Lowepro', 'Ape Case') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_843", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Could you recommend this case for professional photographic gear on hazardous field operations?", "long_answer": "For high-risk field assignments where the safety of professional photography equipment is paramount, I would advise against a camera case with a shoulder strap. Due to their potential for movement, these cases might not offer the necessary protection against the jolts or impacts that could happen. A hard case specifically designed for total immobilization would be better suited for such situations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap cannot be used for circumstances where a rigid case is necessary due to extreme conditions or when full immobility of the equipment is required, as the mobility afforded by straps may not provide sufficient protection in these scenarios.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_844", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the case sufficiently sturdy to endure regular use outdoors?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is crafted from nylon fabric, renowned for its superior tensile strength. As such, it boasts resistance to tearing and stretching, offering sustained durability for prolonged outdoor activities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_894", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Lowepro Fastpack 200 designed to carry a Canon EF 70-200mm sized telephoto lens?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Fastpack 200 has a main compartment with customizable dividers, enabling the potential accommodation of larger lenses such as the Canon EF 70-200mm. These larger lenses can often be carried horizontally in the upper section if the dividers are adjusted accordingly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_895", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does the internal fabric of the bag have a bright color to assist in seeing the contents more clearly?", "long_answer": "The bag's interior is lined with a bright yellow material, which is designed to enhance visibility, making it easier to see and locate items inside.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_641", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I can't stand the quality of Ape Case. Give me the camera case with the least amount of pockets that isn't from that brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ape Case\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Ape Case' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_845", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a 50-500 Sigma lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should be able to fit. I previously stored a Canon 10-22mm lens, and the 50-500 Sigma lens has similar dimensions. Therefore, it should fit quite comfortably.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the 50-500 Sigma lenses has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the 50-500 Sigma lenses fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_896", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the main compartment of the bag large enough to accommodate a camera with an attached longer telephoto lens without modifications?", "long_answer": "Fitting a camera with a longer telephoto lens into the main compartment of the bag might not be straightforward. Adjustments such as rearranging or removing the dividers might be needed to make space for the equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_642", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I got a thing for mica colored stuff. So find me the cheapest mica camera case you've got, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag` with asin: B009GYIKHQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'mica' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_846", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for extended photo shoots where I'll spend most of the time on my feet?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case is ideal for all-day photography sessions, thanks to its lightweight nylon design, which alleviates shoulder and back strain over prolonged usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material feature a lightweight construction which greatly enhances portability, especially beneficial for photographers who travel or carry their equipment for long durations.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_643", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm a fan of Case Logic. Give me the cheapest camera case from them, what's the damage?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster` with asin: B0078IL6K0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Case Logic' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_644", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I don't want a fancy case or anything, just something simple with only one pocket. Oh, and it needs to be green or teal. What's my best option here?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND color IN (\"green\", \"teal\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND color IN (\"green\", \"teal\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 1 AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'teal') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_645", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I have my likes when it comes to brands and colors. So, do you have any orange or red camera cases from Lowepro or OP/TECH USA? Preferably, the first one you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND color IN (\"orange\", \"red\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Lowepro\", \"OP/TECH USA\") AND color IN (\"orange\", \"red\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'Lowepro' OR brand = 'OP/TECH USA') AND (color = 'orange' OR color = 'red') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_847", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I've been using it with a Canon 10-22mm lens which is a similar size so there shouldn't be an issue.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G has similar size with Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikkor70-300mm f4.5-5.6G fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_646", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I don't want any of those AmazonBasics stuff, but I'm interested in a water-resistant camera case. Fetch me one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'AmazonBasics' AND water_resistance = 'yes' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_848", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Can this backpack accommodate a Canon t5i with a 300mm lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I have a Canon 70D with a 70-250 lens and it fits well. Your camera should be a similar size, so it should fit just fine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Canon t5i with a 300mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_849", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for extreme outdoor activities such as rock climbing?", "long_answer": "It is not advisable to use a camera case with a belt loop for high-impact activities like rock climbing. Instead, opting for a more durable case tailored for enhanced protection in such conditions is necessary.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop cannot be used for securely storing the camera while engaging in activities with a high likelihood of impact, such as rock climbing or mountain biking, where a tougher case may be necessary.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_897", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Does the camera bag have additional space for personal items besides camera equipment?", "long_answer": "This camera bag does include extra space for personal items in addition to space for camera equipment, although the amount of personal items it can hold may be limited by the total amount of camera gear being carried.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_850", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Does this case offer adequate protection for my camera against sand and dust while I'm at the beach?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the case's waterproof design provides an effective barrier against fine particles such as sand and dust. However, it's important to note that to prevent scratches or damage from inadvertent falls onto hard surfaces like rocks, the case must be equipped with internal padding.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof characteristics lack the capability to protect against substantial impacts or drops unless they also incorporate specific padding or shock-resistant materials.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_851", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "May I bring this case on my desert photo excursion to shield my camera from the intense heat?", "long_answer": "Considering the case is constructed from nylon, it isn't suitable for extremely high temperatures. The nylon fabric does not possess adequate insulation against intense heat, an important factor to consider in settings such as deserts. A case designed with thermal protection might better serve your requirements.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_647", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I need a camera case in teal with locks. Could you tell me your specific product for that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"teal\" AND closure_type = \"locks\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'teal' AND closure_type = 'locks';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_852", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Does this case fit the Canon Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it for my Nikon D3500 which is approximately the same size as your Canon Rebel T3.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon Rebel T3 has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_853", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is this camera case crafted for travel photographers who require swift setup across diverse locations?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this case is exceptionally convenient for travel photographers who require the ability to move quickly and snap shots without the extra setup involved with tripods. Without a tripod attachment, the case appeals to those who prioritize portability and quickness above the stabilizing benefits that tripods offer.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment typically mean they are intended for quick, on-the-go users who do not require the stabilization that tripods offer for long exposure or time-lapse photography.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_898", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is this backpack designed to be suitable for hikers and outdoor photographers?", "long_answer": "The backpack's design and features specifically cater to the needs of hikers and outdoor photographers, offering durability and comfort for carrying gear in outdoor environments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_854", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can I use this case with my Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have used it with my Canon 70D with an 18-55mm lens and the dimensions are very similar to your camera, so it will definitely fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the Nikon D750 with AF-S NIKKOR 28-300mm f/3.5-5.6G ED VR fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_648", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I can't stand red cases or any that close with buttons or zippers. Among those with velcro or drawstring closures, toss me the one with the least pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND NOT color = \"red\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND NOT color = \"red\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") AND NOT color = \"red\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'red' AND closure_type IN ('drawstring', 'velcro') ORDER BY pockets LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_899", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is this case suitable for storing electronic devices and their batteries?", "long_answer": "The case is indeed suitable to store electronic devices along with their batteries, providing a convenient storage solution.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_900", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the case provide a designated compartment for small accessories?", "long_answer": "The case comes equipped with a zippered pocket specifically designed for storing small accessories such as memory cards. However, due to limited space, it is most suited for holding just the essential items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_649", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I want a camera case in either teal or green, but it must have the least number of pockets. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"green\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"green\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('teal', 'green') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_650", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I ain't dropping more than a Benjamin on this. Show me the first camera case you have that's $100 or less.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_651", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I got this thing for red, but not a fan of Pelican stuff. Can you find me a red camera case from any other brand?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black` with asin: B000YIWOSY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND NOT brand = \"Pelican\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"red\" AND NOT brand = \"Pelican\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'red' AND brand != 'Pelican';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_901", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Is the backpack durable enough for rough outdoor activities?", "long_answer": "The backpack is constructed to be durable, featuring reinforced straps and metal zippers. However, customer experiences indicate that the backpack may show signs of wear and tear under extensive use, suggesting it might not withstand extremely rugged outdoor adventures if used for extended durations.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_902", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the velcro closure on the case durable enough to withstand frequent use?", "long_answer": "The velcro closure is constructed from high-quality materials, and as such, it is designed to be sturdy and retain its effectiveness even with regular use, according to the prevailing opinions among users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_855", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens?", "long_answer": "I'm afraid not. I have a Canon 10-22mm lens and it fits just right, and your Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens is larger than my lens, so it probably won't fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 10-22mm lens, and the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens has larger size than Canon 10-22mm lens, thus the Nikon D800 with a 300mm lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 10-22mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_652", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I don't plan on taking the camera case into any wet environments, so I don't need it to be water resistant. Also, don't give me any of that mica color nonsense. Find me the cheapest option you got that fits these criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND NOT color = \"mica\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'no' AND color != 'mica' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_653", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm tired of the usual black stuff. Do you have a drawstring camera case that's in any color but black?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND NOT color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring' AND color != 'black';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_856", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is this camera case designed to safeguard my equipment throughout a beach photoshoot?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the camera case is crafted with waterproof features, utilizing materials such as PVC or silicone to inhibit water from entering. This ensures that your camera remains protected, even amidst moist conditions like those encountered at the beach.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with waterproof capabilities typically mean they are constructed from materials such as PVC or silicone that inherently resist water penetration, thereby safeguarding the camera equipment in wet conditions.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_857", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I'm concerned about the time required to stow my equipment; does this case expedite the packing process?", "long_answer": "Undoubtedly, this camera case prioritizes efficiency. Designed for increased speed in storing your camera, it eliminates the hassle of external attachments such as tripods. As a result, you can stow your equipment quickly and stay in the moment without interruption.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_903", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Is the Fastpack 200 equipped with a waist strap or chest strap for support?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 is not designed with a waist strap or a chest strap; instead, it incorporates a compact design with padded shoulder straps to provide stability and comfort.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_858", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "I require a case durable enough to withstand the demands of fieldwork while accommodating all of my photography gear. Would this be a suitable option?", "long_answer": "The camera case might not be adequate for rigorous fieldwork that involves using an array of equipment, as it's missing the essential tripod attachment feature. This feature is crucial for the safe transport and swift set-up of commonly utilized professional photography gear such as tripods and additional lights.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_904", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is the case designed to accommodate multiple GoPro cameras and their mounts?", "long_answer": "The case is capable of storing multiple GoPro cameras along with several of their accessories, provided that they are organized effectively within the space. However, if the number of cameras and accessories increases significantly, opting for a larger case would be advisable to ensure everything fits nicely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_905", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can a large folding-prong charger fit comfortably in the zippered pocket of this case?", "long_answer": "The zippered pocket in the case is capable of holding small accessories such as USB cords and standard chargers; however, a particularly large folding-prong charger may only fit if forced due to limited space, which suggests a snug fit rather than a comfortable one.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_906", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack offer comfort during prolonged usage?", "long_answer": "The Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack is crafted with a padded sling strap that is able to rotate to the front of the body, providing comfort for its users, especially during extended periods of wear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_654", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Alright, I need one of your orange camera cases, but it's gotta be either Canon or Altura Photo - no other brands. Whip up the first one that matches my specifications.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Altura Photo\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"orange\" AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Altura Photo\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'orange' AND (brand = 'Canon' OR brand = 'Altura Photo') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_655", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I can't stand dull colors. Find me a teal or purple camera case. And, uh, I could use one with the least number of pockets.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras` with asin: B001I3X3HU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"purple\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"purple\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"teal\", \"purple\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('teal', 'purple') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_656", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I ain't shelling out more than 100 bucks and I need it to resist water. Find me the cheapest camera case that meets those conditions.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 100 AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 100 AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_657", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I don't need all the extra storage, just give me a simple drawstring camera case with no more than two pockets. What options do you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'drawstring' AND pockets <= 2;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_907", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "What type of closure does the case use, zipper or Velcro?", "long_answer": "The case utilizes a zipper closure for securing its contents. While some customers may have a preference for Velcro, the manufacturer has opted to design this case with a zipper mechanism.", "short_answer": "zipper", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_908", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Do customers commonly report concerns regarding the case's size and the amount of extra space available?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback reveals that a notable number of users have expressed concerns about the case's compact dimensions, specifically mentioning the lack of additional space inside the case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_909", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Are the internal dividers of this item adjustable or removable?", "long_answer": "The item's internal dividers are indeed designed to be flexible and user-configurable; they are padded and can be added, removed, or rearranged according to the specific dimensions and requirements of the user's equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_910", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "What are the specific storage capabilities of the device?", "long_answer": "The device offers a storage capacity of 1 terabyte, providing ample space for storing a significant amount of data, including files, applications, and multimedia content.", "short_answer": "1tb, files, apps, multimedia", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_859", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can this camera case remain upright by itself when set down?", "long_answer": "The design of this camera case emphasizes portability and being worn as a backpack, therefore it includes backpack straps. Consequently, it does not have the rigid structure that would allow it to stand upright independently, unlike hard cases that are self-supporting.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps lack the capability to stay upright on their own when set down due to their design focused on back wear-ability, unlike hard cases which can be free-standing.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_911", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Can the Canon 200DG bag fit DSLR cameras from Nikon as well as those from Canon?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG bag, although a Canon-branded product, is designed to fit any DSLR cameras within its interior dimensions of 10.5 x 7.5 x 7 inches, which includes DSLR cameras from Nikon along with those from Canon.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_912", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does this backpack offer comfort for extended all-day use?", "long_answer": "This backpack is widely regarded as comfortable for all-day use, featuring an ergonomic sling strap and a padded waist belt designed to enhance comfort during extended wear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_913", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the Canon PSC-85 case suitable for travel?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 case is favored by customers for travel due to its compact dimension and robust construction, which ensures the camera remains safeguarded while in transit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_914", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is the Digital D-Series pouch compatible with a telephoto lens up to 10 inches in length?", "long_answer": "The Digital D-Series pouch comes in larger sizes that can accommodate cameras with lenses measuring up to 10 inches in length. For compatibility, you should verify the exact size of your telephoto lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_860", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is it safe to immerse the camera case in water while transporting it across a river?", "long_answer": "The camera case material is not intended for complete submergence. It provides elementary water resistance, capable of withstanding slight dampness, but it cannot endure full immersion. To safely ford a river, a case crafted for such conditions or extra waterproofing measures would be necessary.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material do not have a function of complete waterproofing without additional treatments, as standard nylon provides only basic water resistance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_861", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is this case suitable for outdoor photography sessions in all types of weather?", "long_answer": "For outdoor activities, a nylon camera case is a practical option because of its robust construction and light weight. Yet, in situations where you expect to encounter extreme temperatures, consider that nylon doesn't provide the most effective insulation for such climates. In these cases, a camera case with improved thermal protection might be required for harsh weather conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material lack the capability to insulate against extreme temperatures as effectively as specialized thermal materials, which may be necessary in certain environmental conditions.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_915", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Does the case design facilitate one-handed quick access to the camera?", "long_answer": "The case is specifically designed for convenience, featuring a velcro closure that enables quick and easy retrieval and storage of the camera with just one hand.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_916", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack remain comfortable when carrying heavy gear over long periods?", "long_answer": "The backpack is designed to be comfortable with a removable waistbelt and adjustable sternum strap that help distribute weight. However, users report that comfort may decrease when the backpack is fully loaded with heavy gear, such as a tripod, during extended usage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_917", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Is the Pelican 1200 case suitable for storing and protecting delicate glass items?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1200 case is specifically designed with strong construction and customizable foam, making it a reliable option for storing and ensuring the protection of delicate glass items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_918", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "How many compartments for accessories does the bag have, and do users find them sufficient?", "long_answer": "The bag is equipped with three small compartments and one larger compartment for accessories, with most users considering these to be adequate for their storage needs.", "short_answer": "four, yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_919", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Fastpack 200 include built-in locks or specific anti-theft features?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 is equipped with zippers that can be concealed beneath the security flap, providing a minimum level of protection. However, it does not have integrated locks or specialized anti-theft attributes.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_658", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Look man, I need a damn camera case that has locks or velcro, and I won't be breaking the bank over it. Can you pick out the cheapest one you got for under 10 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"velcro\") AND price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('locks', 'velcro') AND price < 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_659", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I like keeping things simple and don't need a bunch of extra pockets. Give me a camera case either from OP/TECH USA or Ape Case that fits the bill.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Ape Case\") AND pockets < 1 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"OP/TECH USA\", \"Ape Case\") AND pockets < 1 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('OP/TECH USA', 'Ape Case') AND pockets = 0;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_920", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is there enough space in the bag to fit an additional SLR camera body?", "long_answer": "The bag is specifically designed to accommodate one SLR camera body with a lens attached. While it has extra space for additional lenses or a flash unit, fitting another camera body may be too tight and could potentially limit the space available for other accessories.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_921", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can I swiftly retrieve my camera from this bag, even with large lenses or hoods?", "long_answer": "The bag's hammock system is designed for quick camera access. Nevertheless, users with particularly large lenses or hoods have sometimes found it slightly more challenging to remove their camera smoothly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_660", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm going camping and need a camera case that can handle a bit of rain but also, can be opened and closed quickly. I prefer those with zippers or drawstrings. Help me find the cheapest one of those, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"yes\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_862", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Does this camera case come with an integrated feature that enables me to secure it to my tripod?", "long_answer": "Regrettably, the camera case does not include an integrated mechanism for direct tripod attachment. Should a tripod be critical for your photographic endeavors, you may have to look at alternative cases or employ an additional camera support system with this case.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment lack the capability to provide an integrated tripod mounting system, which may compel users to consider other forms of camera support if needed.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_922", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is the Pelican 1120 Case equipped with wheels for mobility?", "long_answer": "The Pelican 1120 Case is not designed with wheels. Instead, it includes a single folding front handle to facilitate carrying the case manually.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_923", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is the bag suitable for carrying a mirrorless camera system along with its accessories?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to be suitable for mirrorless camera systems, providing enough room not only for the camera but also for various accessories, which is facilitated by the compact size of mirrorless cameras.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_924", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Does the material of the Canon 200DG gadget bag offer protection against weather conditions?", "long_answer": "The Canon 200DG gadget bag is constructed with a durable, water-repellent nylon exterior, and it includes a weather-flap lid, which provides added protection for your equipment against various weather conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_863", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Will this case fit a 15 1/2 inches long lens? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit your 15 1/2 inches long lens perfectly. I have a Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens and it fits well. The size of your lens is similar to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the 15 1/2 inches long lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the 15 1/2 inches long lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_864", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is this backpack compatible with a Canon Rebel with a 55-200mm lens? ", "long_answer": "No, I'm afraid it wouldn't fit. I have a Canon 60D with a Sigma 17-55mm f2.8 and it just about fits. Your Canon Rebel with a 55-200mm lens is larger than that, so it would be too big for this backpack.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, and the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens has larger size than Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8, thus the Canon Rebel with 55-200 lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 60D with Sigma 17-55mm f2.8"}}
{"id": "search_qa_661", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I don't want to mess around with any fancy closures, just give me the cheapest camera case you have that either zips or locks.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('zipper', 'locks') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_662", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm a fan of USA Gear and I can't go over 30 dollars. Tell me about the case with the least number of pockets you have from them.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND price <= 30 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND price <= 30 AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"USA Gear\" AND price <= 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'USA Gear' AND price <= 30 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_663", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm only interested in OP/TECH USA brand for my camera case. And it has to have either a zipper or a drawstring closure. Give me the first product that matches these criteria.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_925", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Is this bag capable of fitting a full-frame DSLR camera?", "long_answer": "The bag is indeed capable of fitting full-frame DSLR cameras as reported by customers, although the available space may be constrained if additional gear is packed.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_926", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the bag suitable for carrying both SLR cameras and video cameras?", "long_answer": "The bag is tailored primarily for SLR cameras; however, it has the potential to hold video cameras and related accessories as well, contingent upon their size aligning with the bag's dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_927", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is there a built-in rain cover included with the Ape Case backpack?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case backpack features a built-in rain cover that enhances its water-resistance capabilities, allowing for easy access and use during inclement weather conditions, such as when the user is caught in a storm.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_664", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I have no use for extra pockets and I have a thing for orange. Get me the ID of an orange camera case with no pockets!", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND color = \"orange\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets < 1 AND color = \"orange\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'orange' AND pockets = 0;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_865", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is this case suitable for protecting my camera while engaging in high-movement activities, like cycling or jogging?", "long_answer": "For activities involving significant movement, using a camera case with a shoulder strap is not advised, as it fails to provide adequate protection from the impacts experienced. The camera remains vulnerable to motion and possible damage under these circumstances, making a more fixed solution the better option.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap cannot be used for circumstances where a rigid case is necessary due to extreme conditions or when full immobility of the equipment is required, as the mobility afforded by straps may not provide sufficient protection in these scenarios.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_928", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Does the ergonomic sling strap design of this backpack contribute to comfort for extended wear during hikes or tours?", "long_answer": "The backpack features an ergonomic sling strap that is specifically designed to enhance wearer comfort for extended periods, which is suitable for activities like hikes or tours. This design choice is supported by customer feedback suggesting that the backpack provides sufficient comfort for extended wear, even though individual comfort experiences may differ.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_929", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "How durable is the material used in the construction of the backpack?", "long_answer": "The backpack's material is specifically designed for durability, with customer feedback confirming its ability to withstand the typical wear and tear associated with photography outings and regular travel usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_930", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the Fastpack 200's side pocket accommodate a standard water bottle?", "long_answer": "The side pocket of the Fastpack 200, while snug due to its elastic design, can indeed hold a standard water bottle. However, it may require some effort to insert the bottle into the pocket.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_931", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the bag capable of accommodating a Tamron 150-600mm lens along with a full photography kit?", "long_answer": "The bag is designed to hold various photographic equipment; however, storing a very large lens, such as the Tamron 150-600mm, together with a full assortment of gear may prove difficult. To ensure that everything fits, thoughtfully strategize the arrangement of your equipment prior to packing.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_866", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Will this case fit a T3i/600D with a battery grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, it will. The T3i/600D with a battery grip is similar in size to the Nikon D90, which this case is designed to fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D90, and the T3i/600D with a battery grip has similar size with Nikon D90, thus the T3i/600D with a battery grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D90"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_932", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is a carrying strap included with the Canon PSC-85 camera case?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 camera case is not equipped with a carrying strap; instead, it is designed with a belt loop that allows it to be attached to a belt or strap for carrying.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_867", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Will this bag fit my Canon EOS Rebel T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it for my Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens and they fit nicely. Your Canon EOS Rebel T3 has similar dimensions to my camera so it will also fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_868", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can I use this case with my T2i that has a grip and an 18-130 lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have the Nikon D3500 which is a similar size to your T2i with grip and I did not encounter any problems.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the T2i with grip and an 18-130 lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_933", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Do the bag's dividers provide adequate protection for the contents stored within?", "long_answer": "The bag's dividers are padded and can be adjusted to ensure the secure placement of stored items, providing protection. It is important to arrange them properly to avoid the shifting of smaller items between compartments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_934", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the bag have dedicated compartments suitable for storing batteries and SD cards?", "long_answer": "The bag comes equipped with zippered mesh pockets located in both the top and main compartments, which are specifically designed to hold small accessories like batteries and SD cards.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_869", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon T3?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should work. The case fits my Canon L-series 100-400 perfectly and your Canon T3 is similar in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Canon T3 has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Canon T3 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_870", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I am searching for an elegant camera case to present as a gift; would this be suitable?", "long_answer": "If you seek a gift that radiates sophistication, take into account the aesthetic of the camera case. Crafted from nylon, it tends to have a more casual and practical appearance, potentially conflicting with the upscale, refined look you may desire in a present.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not suitable for those seeking a high-end, luxury aesthetic that materials like leather offer, as nylon is generally perceived to be more casual and utilitarian.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_871", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the d3300 fit into this case?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit because it has similar dimensions to the Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, which is known to fit perfectly into this case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the d3300 has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the d3300 fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "search_qa_665", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case in either yellow or orange, but it doesn't need to be waterproof. What's the cheapest option you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras` with asin: B005VTIMEQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"yellow\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"yellow\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN (\"orange\", \"yellow\") AND NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color IN ('yellow', 'orange') AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_935", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Is the outside pocket of the Canon PSC-85 case equipped with a zipper?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 case features an outside pocket that is secured with a zipper, providing a safe space for storing small accessories such as batteries or an extra memory card.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_666", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I ain't got time for flashy stuff. What's the cheapest black camera case you got in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"black\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"black\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'black' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_667", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm after a mica colored camera case, but I'm not looking to spend more than 50 dollars. Can you point me to the best fit?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag` with asin: B009GYIKHQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"mica\" AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'mica' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_668", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I'm off to a shoot and need to carry plenty of gear. Which OP/TECH USA camera case has the least amount of pockets? I can't deal with too many compartments.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)` with asin: B00009R9BF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'OP/TECH USA' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_669", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm quite particular about brands and only consider Canon and AmazonBasics. What's the cheapest camera case from these brands you've got in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"AmazonBasics\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"AmazonBasics\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Canon\", \"AmazonBasics\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Canon', 'AmazonBasics') AND price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases WHERE brand IN ('Canon', 'AmazonBasics') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_936", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 backpack considered comfortable by users when it is carrying a full load?", "long_answer": "According to user reviews, the ACPRO2000 backpack with its adjustable harness system and sternum strap is designed to distribute the weight evenly, making it comfortable to wear despite being fully loaded with gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_872", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Will a Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fit this bag? ", "long_answer": "Yes, it should work. I have the Nikon D3500 that fits well and your camera is similar in dimensions to mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_873", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can I keep the camera case with me while actively shooting on the move?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is equipped with backpack straps for comfortable back wearing, facilitating hands-free use. This feature enables greater freedom of movement, allowing you to concentrate on capturing images without manually holding the case.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with backpack straps are known for facilitating hands-free operation, thus enabling photographers to move more freely and focus on capturing images without the encumbrance of holding onto their case.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "backpack straps", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_670", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I ain't about to let my camera gear get wet, but I also need a case with a zipper or lock, while keeping my wallet intact. What's the cheapest option you have that checks all those boxes?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"locks\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = 'yes' AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'locks') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_671", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "I'm specifically looking for a Case Logic brand, orange colored camera case. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND color = \"orange\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND color = \"orange\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Case Logic\" AND color = \"orange\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Case Logic' AND color = 'orange' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_874", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a Nikon D7100 with a 55-300mm VR lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it can. It fits my Canon 70D with an 18-200mm lens perfectly, and the Nikon D7100 with a 55-300mm VR lens is roughly the same size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, and the Nikon D7100 + 55-300mm VR lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens, thus the Nikon D7100 + 55-300mm VR lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-200mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_937", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the ACPRO2000 camera backpack equipped with strapping that provides comfort for extended periods of carrying?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 camera backpack features padded shoulder straps, an adjustable harness system, and a sternum strap to enhance balance and carrying comfort. However, it should be noted that feedback from some users suggests that the hip strap could be better designed to improve support and comfort during prolonged use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_672", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I ain't swimming in cash and need a drawstring camera case under 30 bucks. Could you find me the one with the least pockets to keep it cheap?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND closure_type = \"drawstring\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND closure_type = 'drawstring' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_673", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "I'm a bit of a brand snob, and only trust \"Altura Photo\" or \"Lowepro\". Among these two, which camera case has the least amount of pockets?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack` with asin: B000YA33DC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Lowepro\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Lowepro\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Altura Photo\", \"Lowepro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Altura Photo', 'Lowepro') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_938", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can the sling design of this backpack provide quick access to camera equipment without removing it?", "long_answer": "The backpack's sling design facilitates rapid access to your camera gear as you can simply slide the bag to the front to reach your equipment, without needing to take the backpack off.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_875", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens?", "long_answer": "This case was designed to fit a Canon L-series 100-400 and I believe your Rebel xsi with a 55-250 mm long lens is larger than that size. So the case might not fit your camera setup.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens has larger size than Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Rebel xsi with 55-250 mm long lens do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_939", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Are the interior dividers of this bag customizable to accommodate various types of gear?", "long_answer": "The interior dividers in this bag are padded and can be adjusted, providing you with the ability to tailor the main compartment's layout to fit different pieces of gear. However, there is feedback from some users indicating that there may be limitations to the possible configurations, which could affect how you arrange your equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_876", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can I swiftly retrieve my camera from this case when I need to take a quick snapshot?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this camera case is crafted for enhanced accessibility, as it does not include complex sealing features such as waterproof zippers or intricate locks commonly seen in waterproof cases. This design facilitates rapid access to your camera, perfect for capturing spontaneous, swiftly emerging photo opportunities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_940", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Can the Ape Case Cubeze be comfortably accommodated inside a messenger bag or purse?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Cubeze is versatile and designed to fit into different types of bags, such as messenger bags, purses, and backpacks. However, one should verify that the dimensions of the Cubeze are compatible with the dimensions of the intended bag for a proper fit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_877", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Will this case fit my Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens?", "long_answer": "No, it likely won't fit. I have a Nikon D3500 that fits just right, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lens is larger than my camera.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense has larger size than Nikon D3500, thus the Canon EOS Rebel T3i with a long lense do NOT fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "search_qa_674", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I've had it with USA Gear and don't want anything fancy with too many pockets. Just give me the simplest camera case from a different brand that has two pockets or less.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND pockets <= 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Gear\" AND pockets <= 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'USA Gear' AND pockets <= 2 ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_675", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm sick of zippers getting stuck or broken. What's the cheapest camera case you have that uses either velcro or locks?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"locks\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"locks\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"locks\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('velcro', 'locks') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_878", "asin": "B00091S0WA", "question": "Is it possible to affix this camera case to the utility belt I use during my outdoor photography sessions?", "long_answer": "Regrettably, this camera case might not fit your utility belt if it's especially broad, given that the loop is tailored for belts of standard width, which may restrict your carrying choices when you're engaged in outdoor photography.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with a belt loop lack the capability to accommodate very wide belts if their loops are designed only for standard-sized belts, which could limit the options for how they are worn.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "belt loop", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_676", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm in the mood for something bright and cheery. Look up the cheapest yellow camera case you have in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'yellow' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_879", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the camera case intended for photographers who need to transition swiftly between locations?", "long_answer": "Certainly, our camera cases are designed for photographers on the move, requiring swift transitions between sites. The lack of a tripod attachment feature ensures a seamless experience, facilitating rapid packing and unpacking of your camera equipment without additional procedures.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_880", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Will this case withstand daily use in a professional photography environment?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the camera case is designed to endure the rigors of everyday use, particularly in professional environments. The nylon fabric provides superb resistance to wear and tear, ensuring it retains its structure and safeguards your camera through regular use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are known for their resistance to abrasion, serving users well in environments where the case may be subject to frequent friction or rough handling.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_941", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Is the sling-style backpack capable of standing upright on its own when fully loaded?", "long_answer": "The sling-style backpack's design does not support it standing upright on its own when it is fully loaded, even though it does have rubber feet that can reduce wear on the bag.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_942", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is a shoulder strap included with this bag for carrying purposes?", "long_answer": "The bag does come with a shoulder strap, which is designed to facilitate easy and comfortable transportation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_677", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I don't want to spend more than $30, and I hate clutter, so find me a camera case with less than two pockets. Make it the cheapest one you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND pockets < 2 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND pockets < 2 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND pockets < 2 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_678", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Look, I can't splash more than 30 greenbacks on a camera case. But I still want it to be stylish. Can you find me one in either teal or mica?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND color IN (\"teal\", \"mica\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price < 30 AND color IN (\"teal\", \"mica\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND (color = 'teal' OR color = 'mica');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_943", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can I quickly swap lenses on my camera while using the Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag?", "long_answer": "The Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag is specifically designed for quick retrieval of your camera equipment, facilitating swift lens changes when you are mobile. Despite the convenience, the design of the bag might expose your gear to bystanders, so it is recommended to take caution and be vigilant of your surroundings during the exchange to ensure the security of your equipment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_679", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "I'm after a Pelican brand camera case, but my wallet can only take up to 50 bucks. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Pelican\" AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand='Pelican' AND price<=50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_881", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I require a case that can withstand the demands of fieldwork and accommodate all my photography gear. Would this be an appropriate selection?", "long_answer": "The camera case might not be adequate for rigorous fieldwork involving the use of diverse equipment since it is missing the essential tripod attachment feature. This is crucial for the secure transport and swift setup of widely-used professional photography gear such as tripods and external lights.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment fail to meet the requirements for professional settings where equipment like external flashes, reflectors, and tripods are essential for optimal lighting and image stability.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_944", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the ACPRO2000 backpack have sufficient padding in the laptop compartment for protection?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 backpack features a padded laptop compartment, offering protection predominantly at the bottom edge, but for situations involving potential long drops or rough treatment, extra protective measures are recommended to ensure laptop safety.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_882", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "Is this case designed with fewer complex components that might break or require maintenance?", "long_answer": "Indeed, because this camera case is not intended to be waterproof, it typically lacks intricate seals or locks, resulting in fewer components that may wear out or need upkeep as time goes on.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with the attribute of not being waterproof are known for easier accessibility to the camera, as they generally do not have elaborate sealing mechanisms like watertight zippers or locks that are common in waterproof cases.", "feature_name": "Waterproof", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_945", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Can the upper compartment of the bag accommodate personal items such as a wallet and keys?", "long_answer": "The upper compartment of the bag is sufficiently spacious to hold personal items including a wallet, keys, snacks, and a small jacket. It offers enough room for these items, but may not be suitable for larger items which could exceed the available space.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_946", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is the holster material described as flexible?", "long_answer": "The holster material is high-quality and tends to be on the stiffer side, lacking flexibility or stretchiness akin to neoprene, as users have not reported it to be particularly flexible.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_680", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Got any camera cases from Pelican or Altura Photo that use a velcro or drawstring closure on them? Show me something like that.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Altura Photo\") AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"Pelican\", \"Altura Photo\") AND closure_type IN (\"velcro\", \"drawstring\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (brand = 'Pelican' OR brand = 'Altura Photo') AND (closure_type = 'velcro' OR closure_type = 'drawstring');"}}
{"id": "search_qa_681", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I dislike black camera cases and I don't want one with locks. Find me the cheapest alternative, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND NOT color = \"black\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND NOT color = \"black\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT closure_type = \"locks\" AND NOT color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'black' AND closure_type != 'locks' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_682", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "I can't stand yellow, it's just not my thing. What's the cheapest non-yellow camera case you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"yellow\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color <> 'yellow' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_947", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the Ape Case Pro ACPRO2000 backpack too large for carrying just a few camera gear items?", "long_answer": "The Ape Case Pro ACPRO2000 backpack is tailored towards professionals or avid enthusiasts who require a bag to carry a substantial amount of camera equipment. Consequently, for those who possess merely a few items, it would likely be excessively spacious.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_948", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is the bag capable of comfortably fitting a camera, two lenses, and various additional accessories?", "long_answer": "The bag is structured to hold a camera and two lenses; however, incorporating additional accessories might result in a snug fit. It's recommended to prioritize essential items to make certain that all necessary equipment can be securely carried within the bag.", "short_answer": "possibly tight fit", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_949", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can the foam lining inside the case be modified with ease for custom fitting?", "long_answer": "The Pick N' Pluck foam lining inside the case is found by customers to be reasonably easy to modify, allowing for the accommodation of various specific items. Nonetheless, a desire for greater customization has been expressed, with some customers wishing for the ability to pluck the foam at half-height increments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_883", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Can I fit a Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom in this bag? ", "long_answer": "Yes, this product should fit a Canon 70D with a 135mm zoom. I have a Canon 70D with a 70-250mm lens and it fits well. The size of your configuration should be similar.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, and the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom has similar size with Canon 70D with 70-250 lens, thus the Canon 70D with 135mm zoom fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 70-250 lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_950", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "What is the overall build quality and durability of the Lowepro Flipside 300 camera bag as reported by customers?", "long_answer": "According to customer feedback, the Lowepro Flipside 300 camera bag is recognized for its sturdy construction and long-lasting durability, which holds up well over time even with frequent use.", "short_answer": "well-constructed and durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_951", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "Is a warranty included with the purchase of the gadget bag?", "long_answer": "According to the product's metadata, the gadget bag is expected to come with warranty information. To confirm the existence of a warranty, customers are advised to review the warranty details found on the packaging upon receiving the item.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_884", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Can I use this case with my Nikon D7100 with Sigma 18-250 attached?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I have a Canon L-series 100-400, and the case works well for us. Your Nikon D7100 with Sigma 18-250 attached and my camera have similar sizes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the Nikon D7100 with Sigma 18-250 attached has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the Nikon D7100 with Sigma 18-250 attached fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "search_qa_683", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "I'm a fan of Ape Case but I hate clutter. Display the most affordable option they got with zero pockets.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = \"Ape Case\" AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Ape Case' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_952", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can the Canon PSC-85 camera case fit inside a soft-sided carry-on bag for air travel without issues?", "long_answer": "The Canon PSC-85 camera case is designed to fit comfortably within a soft-sided carry-on bag, as indicated by customer experiences, and provides adequate protection suitable for air travel.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_684", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I hate clutter and extra pockets on my stuff. Help me find a camera case with a zipper and no pockets, and make sure it's the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"zipper\" AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type='zipper' AND pockets=0 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_685", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Look, I'm not a fan of Altura Photo and I want either a zipper or velcro closure type for my case. Hook me up with the first product that satisfies these particulars.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"velcro\") AND NOT brand = \"Altura Photo\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'Altura Photo' AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'velcro') ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_686", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I'm fed up with products that can't stand a drop of water! Give me a waterproof camera case with the fewest pockets from Case Logic or Pelican.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Pelican\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Pelican\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Case Logic\", \"Pelican\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Case Logic', 'Pelican') AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_885", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Can this bag accommodate a 6D w/24-105mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it can. I have a Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens and it fits well. Given the 6D w/24-105mm lens has a similar size as mine, you shouldn't have any issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, and the 6D w/24-105mm lens has similar size with Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens, thus the 6D w/24-105mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon 70D with 18-55mm lens"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_953", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "Does the Fastpack 200 come with dedicated straps for tripods?", "long_answer": "The Fastpack 200 lacks dedicated straps specifically designed for carrying tripods, necessitating users to look for other carrying methods or consider alternative backpack models if they need to transport a tripod.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_954", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does this backpack include a dedicated compartment for personal items in addition to camera gear?", "long_answer": "The backpack, which is primarily designed to carry camera equipment, does incorporate some limited space for carrying small personal items alongside the photographic gear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_687", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "I'm not messing around, I need a camera case with a lock on it and I'm not gonna drop more than 50 dollars on it. What do you got for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = \"locks\" AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type = 'locks' AND price <= 50;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_688", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I've got a thing for green. What's the cheapest green camera case you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG` with asin: B00004WCGF", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_955", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Is a Pelican case buoyant when placed in water?", "long_answer": "Pelican cases are engineered to be buoyant, allowing them to float in water. The level to which they can remain afloat is influenced by the weight of the items contained within the case. Consequently, it is advisable to perform a buoyancy test under safe and controlled conditions to verify the extent of flotation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_956", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Would the ACPRO2000 backpack be comfortable for individuals with a smaller body frame?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 may be cumbersome for individuals with smaller body frames, especially when the backpack is fully loaded. Although the straps are fully adjustable, the overall size of the backpack should be taken into account by someone with a smaller frame in order to ensure a comfortable fit.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_957", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Is it possible to use a lens filter or cap with the camera lens while it's stored in this pouch?", "long_answer": "The pouch design permits the use of lens filters or caps on your camera lens; however, it is essential to verify that the additional dimensions from the filter or cap do not compromise the fit inside the pouch.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_886", "asin": "B0014D47RY", "question": "Would this case fit a Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. I use it for my Nikon D3500 and your camera has similar dimensions with mine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon 5D2 with a mounted 24-105/4 or fast prime fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_958", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the bag's material possess inherent weather-resistant qualities?", "long_answer": "The product's specifications do not explicitly mention weather resistance; therefore, although it might provide limited defense against minor moisture exposure, it is advisable to utilize extra protective measures in adverse weather conditions to ensure the bag's contents remain unharmed.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_689", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I don't need all those extra pockets and certainly don't want a black one. Find me the most affordable camera case with one pocket or less and any color but black.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT color = \"black\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT color = \"black\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND NOT color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 1 AND color != 'black' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_959", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Does the backpack have water-resistant features?", "long_answer": "The backpack has been designed with water resistance as a consideration, particularly with the zippers positioned under a protective flap to shield against moisture. Nonetheless, in cases of heavy rain, the manufacturer suggests the utilization of extra protection, like a rain cover, to ensure the contents remain dry.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_690", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I'm a simple man with a $10 bill. What's the cheapest camera case you got with a zipper or drawstring?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case` with asin: B00DUGZDJ4", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"zipper\", \"drawstring\") AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 10 AND (closure_type = 'zipper' OR closure_type = 'drawstring') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_691", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "I'm not dealing with any wet conditions, so forget about water resistance. Just get me a camera case with either a drawstring or a zipper. What's the first one you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009GA6CAW", "title": "Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)"}, {"asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "title": "AmazonBasics Sling Backpack for SLR Cameras"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Ape Case Cubeze 37, Camera Insert, Black/Yellow, Interior Case For Cameras (ACQB37)` with asin: B009GA6CAW", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND closure_type IN (\"drawstring\", \"zipper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE (closure_type = 'drawstring' OR closure_type = 'zipper') AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_887", "asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "question": "Is this case a suitable option for professional photographers requiring robust support for their equipment?", "long_answer": "Professional photographers typically need robust support for their equipment to avoid damage. Given nylon's inherent pliability, this camera case might not provide the solid structure commonly sought to guarantee the protection of professional photographic equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material are not recommended for situations that necessitate a rigid form for the camera equipment, as the natural give of the fabric might not provide the structural stability desired.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_960", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Where is the Soft Pouch Digital D-Series manufactured?", "long_answer": "The Soft Pouch Digital D-Series is manufactured in the United States, as asserted by the OP/TECH USA brand.", "short_answer": "USA", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_692", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm trying to save some cash and am limiting my spending to 30 dollars for a camera case. But I'm not compromising on the brand, so find me something from Altura Photo.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= 30 AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND price <= 30;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_888", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "Does this camera case aid in streamlining the photography workflow?", "long_answer": "Undoubtedly, the D-ring or clip attachments that are an integral part of this camera case provide seamless convenience, allowing for easy attachment of your tripod. This proves particularly beneficial for photographers aiming to reduce the interval between transitioning from one location to another and taking stationary shots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with d-ring or clip attachments for tripod attachment typically mean that photographers can expect enhanced convenience by having an easy, swift way to secure and release their tripods, enabling quick transitions between mobile and stationary photography setups.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "d-ring or clip attachments", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_693", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "I'm not a fan of teal and I only buy Altura Photo brand. Find me a camera case from them that's any color but teal.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "title": "Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Altura Photo Camera Sling Backpack for DSLR and Mirrorless Cameras (Canon Nikon Sony Pentax)` with asin: B00PV0IEDY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"teal\" AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"teal\" AND brand = \"Altura Photo\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand = 'Altura Photo' AND color != 'teal';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_889", "asin": "B000YA33DC", "question": "Is it possible to swiftly deploy my tripod when I need to photograph unexpected motions or incidents with this camera bag?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this camera case features a specialized tripod pocket that enables quick and easy attachment and detachment of your tripod. This is particularly beneficial when you must promptly set up for a shot, such as photographing moving subjects or fast-paced scenes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a dedicated tripod pocket are known for their convenience in allowing for quick attachment and detachment of tripods, which is particularly beneficial in dynamic shooting situations where setting up the shot swiftly is crucial.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "dedicated tripod pocket/compartment", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_890", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Will this case fit my A-99 with vertical grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should. I use it for my Canon L-series 100-400, which seems to be a similar size to your A-99 with vertical grip.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the A-99 with vertical grip has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the A-99 with vertical grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "search_qa_694", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm not a fan of OP/TECH USA, so show me a different brand's camera case with the fewest pockets, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"OP/TECH USA\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand <> 'OP/TECH USA' ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_961", "asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "question": "Is the weight distribution of the sling comfortable for extended periods of wear?", "long_answer": "User reviews largely suggest that the sling is designed to distribute weight effectively, thereby providing comfort even when worn for extended durations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_695", "asin": "B009GA6CAW", "question": "I've got a thing for green, but not too many pockets. What's the first green camera case you have with fewer pockets than average?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"green\" AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'green' AND pockets < (SELECT AVG(pockets) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_891", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Can this bag accommodate my A-99 with a vertical grip?", "long_answer": "Yes, I believe it should fit. The bag fits a Canon L-series 100-400, and the A-99 with vertical grip has a similar size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Canon L-series 100-400, and the A-99 with vertical grip has similar size with Canon L-series 100-400, thus the A-99 with vertical grip fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Canon L-series 100-400"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_892", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "Can this case accommodate a Canon T31 with a 250mm lens?", "long_answer": "Yes, it should fit. The case is designed for a Nikon D3500, which is similar in size to your Canon T31 with a 250mm lens.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "The product fits with Nikon D3500, and the Canon T31 with 250mm lens has similar size with Nikon D3500, thus the Canon T31 with 250mm lens fits with the product.", "feature_name": "compatibility_attributes", "feature_value": "Nikon D3500"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_962", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Can you purchase additional foam inserts for this case?", "long_answer": "If you're looking to reconfigure the interior of the case to accommodate different equipment, extra foam inserts are indeed available for purchase to meet your needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_963", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "Can the internal dividers in the main compartment be adjusted to fit specific camera gear?", "long_answer": "Yes, the internal dividers in the main compartment offer flexibility and can be adjusted to accommodate the size and shape of your specific camera equipment, providing a tailored fit for various configurations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_964", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is a rain cover included with the purchase of an ACPRO2000 camera bag?", "long_answer": "The ACPRO2000 camera bag comes with a built-in rain cover to enhance water resistance, providing protection for the contents of the bag during on-location shoots where rain may be a concern.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_965", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the zipper on this case known for its durability?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback suggests that the zipper on the case is generally considered durable and is appropriately sized to facilitate easy use. The lifespan of the zipper may differ depending on how often it is used and the manner in which it is handled.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_966", "asin": "B00PV0IEDY", "question": "Does the bag's external design help to conceal the fact that it is carrying expensive equipment?", "long_answer": "The external design of the bag is considered nondescript by most users, effectively preventing it from drawing attention to the expensive equipment being carried within, thus adding a layer of discretion and security.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_967", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Does the camera case maintain the camera's slim profile when used?", "long_answer": "The case is specifically designed to remain slim and lightweight, ensuring it adds only a minimal amount of bulk to the camera while offering protection.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_968", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "Is the internal padding of the case considered adequate for protecting the camera?", "long_answer": "The case features interior padding that customers generally regard as suitable for everyday use, providing protection against standard wear and tear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_969", "asin": "B005J09OXU", "question": "Can the camera compartment accommodate multiple camera bodies and lenses simultaneously?", "long_answer": "Yes, the camera compartment is designed to be quite spacious, allowing users to fit several camera bodies and lenses inside it. The space can be efficiently organized to hold this equipment securely due to customizable dividers that can be adapted to the size and shape of the cameras and lenses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_696", "asin": "B005VTIMEQ", "question": "I don't need any fancy water resistance features, just give me the cheapest camera case from Canon or Pelican.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Pelican\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Pelican\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance = \"no\" AND brand IN (\"Canon\", \"Pelican\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN ('Canon', 'Pelican') AND water_resistance = 'no' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_697", "asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "question": "I'm not a fan of AmazonBasics stuff. Find me your cheapest camera case from a different brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT brand = \"AmazonBasics\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand != 'AmazonBasics' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_698", "asin": "B00009R9BF", "question": "I don't have time for fancy brands. Just give me the cheapest case from USA Gear or Canon.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WQ21SQ", "title": "Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon PSC-85 Deluxe Soft Case for Canon Powershot A650IS and A720IS` with asin: B000WQ21SQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Canon\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Canon\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Gear\", \"Canon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price = (SELECT price FROM camera_cases WHERE brand IN ('USA Gear', 'Canon') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_893", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Is the camera case intended for photographers requiring swift location changes?", "long_answer": "Certainly, our camera cases are designed for on-the-go photographers who require swift transitions between various locations. The lack of a tripod attachment feature ensures a smooth experience, facilitating rapid packing and unpacking of your camera equipment without additional complications.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_970", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the backpack come with a built-in mechanism to lock the zippers?", "long_answer": "The backpack does not include a built-in locking mechanism specifically for securing the zippers. Nevertheless, it's possible for users to adapt the zippers to attach a TSA-approved lock, although this might need a bit of creativity or DIY effort.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_699", "asin": "B00004WCGF", "question": "I don't need a bunch of extra pockets or a zipper closure. Just get me the cheapest camera case that fits the description.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets <= 2 AND NOT closure_type = \"zipper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type != 'zipper' AND pockets = 0 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_971", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Are the side compartments of the camera bag large enough to store extra lenses?", "long_answer": "The two large cylindrical side compartments were specifically designed to hold extra lenses or other camera accessories. While they can indeed accommodate additional lenses, the fit might be tight for larger lenses.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_700", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "I'm not into fussy stuff and don't need extra pockets. Just get me a simple, no-pocket camera case with either a lock or a zipper, and make sure it's the cheapest thing you got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") AND pockets < 1 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") AND pockets < 1 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") AND pockets < 1 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE pockets = 0 AND (closure_type = 'locks' OR closure_type = 'zipper') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_701", "asin": "B000YIWOSY", "question": "I'm a sucker for all things yellow, and I need a camera case that'll stand up to the rain. Can you find me a product like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)` with asin: B000WH86BQ", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = \"yellow\" AND water_resistance = \"yes\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color = 'yellow' AND water_resistance = 'yes';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_894", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Are these camera cases designed for photographers who favor minimalist gear setups?", "long_answer": "Indeed, they do. Our camera cases are designed for photographers who favor minimalism. By forgoing a tripod attachment feature, the case provides a straightforward and rapid means to store and access your camera, ideally suiting a simplified gear configuration.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with no tripod attachment feature streamlined access to the camera, allowing for quicker retrieval and storage without the need for detaching ancillary equipment like a tripod.", "feature_name": "Tripod Attachment", "feature_value": "none", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_895", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm concerned that my camera case may deteriorate rapidly—can this particular case withstand substantial wear and tear?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the nylon fabric of this camera case bestows it with outstanding durability against wear and tear. It is designed to preserve its condition, even through frequent intensive use, thanks to the material's sturdiness.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera case with nylon material typically means that the case will be valued for its high tensile strength, making it resistant to tears and stretching over the life of the product.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "nylon", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_702", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "I'm looking for a camera case but I got to have either a lock or zipper closure, and not too many pockets. Give me the one with the least amount of pockets fitting these specs.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)` with asin: B0014D47RY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN (\"locks\", \"zipper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE closure_type IN ('locks', 'zipper') ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_703", "asin": "B0002INQT2", "question": "Look, I don't want to pay more than the average price for a camera case. And I don't need a ton of pockets. Show me the one with the least pockets that won't break my wallet.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) ORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) AND pockets = (SELECT MIN(pockets) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM camera_cases) \nORDER BY pockets ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_896", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "Is this camera case dependable enough to protect my gear in congested areas?", "long_answer": "Camera cases are quite handy for transport, particularly with their shoulder straps, but in crowded areas where the risk of damage or theft is greater, considering a more secure alternative such as a hard case with locks might be wise.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap lack the capability to offer the same level of security as a locked carry-on or hard case, so they might not be the primary choice for transporting extremely valuable or sensitive equipment.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_972", "asin": "B0078IL6K0", "question": "Is it possible to replace the velcro closure of the holster with a magnetic or zipper closure?", "long_answer": "The holster is manufactured with a velcro closure, and the manufacturer does not provide any alternative closure options such as magnets or a zipper.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_973", "asin": "B000WH86BQ", "question": "Does the Hi-Vis yellow interior of the backpack help in locating small accessories more easily?", "long_answer": "The bright Hi-Vis yellow color of the backpack interior is designed to aid in the visibility of small accessories, particularly in low light situations. The contrast it creates against various types of equipment makes locating items within the backpack more convenient.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_974", "asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "question": "Is the bag susceptible to color fading over time when exposed to direct sunlight?", "long_answer": "The bag's exterior is constructed from quality materials that are designed to preserve the original appearance. Nevertheless, prolonged exposure to direct sunlight could potentially lead to color fading. Therefore, to maintain the bag's color, it is advisable to store it away from direct sunlight.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_704", "asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "question": "I don't want any purple cases, and it's got to be water resistant. Give me the first product you got that meets these terms.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0002Y5WZC", "title": "Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black"}, {"asin": "B00004WCGF", "title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 100EG"}, {"asin": "B00WUIIH8W", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-205 SLR Camera Sling (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0002INQT2", "title": "Pelican 1200 Case With Foam (Black)"}, {"asin": "B0014D47RY", "title": "Pelican 1120 Case With Foam (Desert Tan)"}, {"asin": "B00DUGZDJ4", "title": "AmazonBasics Medium Point and Shoot Camera Case"}, {"asin": "B001I3X3HU", "title": "Canon SLR Gadget Bag For EOS or Rebel Cameras"}, {"asin": "B00009R9BF", "title": "OP/TECH USA Soft Pouch Digital D-M 4/3 (Black)"}, {"asin": "B005J09OXU", "title": "USA GEAR Digital SLR Camera Backpack w/15.6&quot; Laptop Compartment featuring Padded Custom Dividers, Tripod Holder, Rain Cover. Long-Lasting Durability &amp; Storage Pockets - Compatible w/Many DSLR"}, {"asin": "B000YA33DC", "title": "Lowepro Flipside 300 DSLR Camera Backpack"}, {"asin": "B009GYIKHQ", "title": "Lowepro Passport Sling DSLR Camera Bag"}, {"asin": "B001TZWNF0", "title": "Case Logic SLRC-202 Medium SLR Camera Bag (Black)"}, {"asin": "B000YIWOSY", "title": "Lowepro Fastpack 200 -Black"}, {"asin": "B000WH86BQ", "title": "Ape Case, ACPRO2000, Large backpack, Laptop compartment, Padded, Rain cover included, Adjustable straps, Camera Backpack, Equipment bag, Black (ACPRO2000)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Canon 200DG Digital Camera Gadget Bag -Black` with asin: B0002Y5WZC", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT color = \"purple\" AND NOT water_resistance = \"no\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE color != 'purple' AND water_resistance = 'yes' ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_705", "asin": "B001I3X3HU", "question": "I've ruined enough gear with water damage already. I don't need a water resistant case, just get me the cheapest one you have that isn't water resistant.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00091S0WA", "title": "Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras"}, {"asin": "B0078IL6K0", "title": "Case Logic SHC-101 DSLR Day Holster"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Sony LCS-CST General Purpose Soft Carrying Case for Slim Cybershot Digital Cameras` with asin: B00091S0WA", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `camera_cases` WHERE NOT water_resistance = \"yes\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `camera_cases` WHERE water_resistance='no' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_897", "asin": "B001TZWNF0", "question": "Is this camera case suitable for me when I aim to reduce motion and sound while filming in tranquil settings?", "long_answer": "In environments requiring silence, where minimizing movement and noise is key, a camera case designed for hand carrying or that secures snugly to your body without dangling straps is preferable to one with a shoulder strap, which could swing and generate sound.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "camera cases with a shoulder strap are not recommended for situations where stealth is necessary, as the motion of a dangling strap might draw unwanted attention or noise, unlike a case that is carried by a handle or secured closer to the body.", "feature_name": "Carrying Options", "feature_value": "shoulder strap", "type": "experience"}}
